[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
A
а
Thank you. Have a nice trip. We are waiting for you.
Благодарю вас Счастливого пути ждём вас
hello again diesel to full Seventh
снова привет дизель до полного Седьмая
diesel speakers up to
колоночки дизель до
full katr make a check neh service a
полного катр сделай чеку нех службу а
while the people
пока народа
no, you look, yes, some kind of game
нет смотришь да игра какая-то
three mouths one blindfolded
три уст у одного завязаны глаза у
another has the ears of a third
другого уши у третьего
the mouth shows the picture to the mute and
роть типа немому показывает картинку и
he has to explain what's on it to the deaf person
он должен объяснить что на ней глухому
Well, you can only understand gestures, you're deaf.
Ну только жестами понимаешь глухой
In short, I should retell you the gestures
короче должен пересказать ти жесты
then he unties the eyes of the blind man
слепому потом слепому развязывает глаза
they show three similar pictures and here I am
показывают три похожих картинки и я вот
must choose the one that was shown
должен выбрать ту которую показывали
nothing Well, in general I figured it out somehow
нече Да в общем как-то так я разобралась
I hate it myself but for some reason I look at what kind of
сама бесит но смотрю зачем-то какие же
morons make all this up
[__] это всё придумывают
[music]
[музыка]
And what kind of morons watch this for people?
А какие [__] это смотрят людям
like it Judging by the ratings why is it
нравится Судя по рейтингам почему это
looks I don't understand What do you mean Andrey
смотрит Я не понимаю В смысле Андрей ты
I bought this program in Bulgarian myself
же сам купил эту программу на болгарском
TV and asked us to remake it for
ТВ и попросил нас переделать её под
I bought Russia because I don't know anything
Россию я купил это потому что я ничего
idiot didn't see this on the mu box
дебильное этого не видел на ящике му
not even enough
недостаточно даже достали
Andryusha, I don't understand something, Aleja
Андрюша я чего-то не понимаю алежа
Apparently yes, look at these letters T SV it is
Видимо да посмотри на эти буквы т СВ это
the name of our channel is T Terekhin
название нашего канала Т Терёхин с
Simonov V Velman Semyon this little
Симонов В вельман Сёма этот маленький
we created the channel yes and what part of it
канал создали мы да А какой частью его
we each own 10% of the shares, 70%
мы владеем по 10% акции у каждого 70% у
investors Is it fair now? We are
инвесторов А честно ли это сейчас мы же
we can't buy back these 70%
не можем выкупить эти 70%
We don't have that much money at the current rate
у нас же нет столько денег по текущей
stock price No you want us to start
цене акции Нет ты хочешь чтобы мы начали
show something that no one will watch
показывать то что никто смотреть не
the shares will become cheaper and we will buy them up
будет акции подешевеют и мы их скупим
completely and then we will return everything to its place
полностью и потом вернём всё на место
Absolutely right, only the channel will already be there
Совершенно верно только канал уже будет
belong to us not 30 but 100%
принадлежать нам не на 30 А на все 100%
Well, it doesn't work that way, you buy it
ну не получается же ты покупаешь
bulgarian programs old reality shows
болгарские передачи старые реалити шоу
reruns of old TV series people VS equal
повторы старых сериалов люди ВС равно
They are watching So we need fresh blood
смотрят Значит нам нужна Свежая кровь
someone who can create chaos in the airwaves
тот кто может создать в эфире хаос
A person capable of creating such a product
Человек способный создать такой продукт
which will be hated by all viewers
который будет ненавидеть Все зрители Нам
need a new CEO colleagues
нужен новый генеральный директор коллеги
We must find it as soon as possible
в кратчайшие сроки Мы должны найти
the most complete idiot in the media
самого конченного долбоёба в медиа
business Hello Andrey Hello This is Velman
бизнесе Алло Андрей привет Это вельман
listen just met with
слушай только что встретился с
while he was working on TV series on one of
поком он занимался сериалами на одном из
the federal government destroyed everything there with a bang
федеральных всё там развалил с треском
I flew out pretty well, another year without work
вылетел неплохо год без работы ещё
it's better to really require a big advance and
лучше правда требует большой аванс и
option agreement
договор с опционам
and not smart Pavlo Ishi
а не умный Павло Ищи
then I think I found everything we needed
дальше я кажется нашёл всё что нам
need an aunt 10 years made a reality show
нужно тётка 10 лет делала реалити-шоу
She's gone crazy and now she's in a mental hospital
крыша съехала начи она теперь в дурке
censer Wait now doctor
кадит Сейчас подожди доктор
we won't let her out here listen to her no
здесь мы е не выпустим слушай её не
they release Come on, we'll pay her
выпускают Да брось мы заплатим она нам
needed Listen Andryusha is not an option she
нужна Слушай Андрюша не вариант она
She threw her husband out of the window screaming
своего мужа выбросила из окна с криком
Get out of here
Уходи из
project so it seems I found what we need
проекта так кажется я нашл то что нам
the guy needed to be a director before
нужно парень раньше был режиссёром потом
was in charge of some channel on satellite
руководил каким-то каналом в спутниковом
the package then filmed the series with hidden cameras
пакете потом снял сери скрытыми камерами
Dest
дест
and put it in efi I heard about it
и поставил Это в эфи Я слышал про него
just do you know what happened to the channel later
только знаешь что потом с каналом стало
they closed it, [ __ ]
его закрыли [__] это
[music]
[музыка]
it's too much, you'll have to give it up
перебор придётся отказаться от него
It's a pity, the guy was promising.
жалко паренк был перспективный Мне
It seems we are something
кажется мы что-то
we will miss out on it all the time or
упускаем у нас на всё время будет или
enumeration or
перебор или
shortage All idiots are careful And everyone is crazy
недобор Все идиоты осторожны А все псих
dangerous maybe somewhere else
опасны пра може ещё где-то
search
поискать
[music]
[музыка]
Oh, with us, fight or life, pack dog Jump
Ох с нами бой чи жизнь стай пес Прыгай
up and down
вверх и вни
[music]
[музыка]
I think I have
при кажется у меня есть
candidate I apologize, I didn't understand this myself
кандидат Извиняюсь это само я не понял к
General Director of the TV channel
генеральным директором телеканала
tsv This is some kind of joke yes I bought it
тсв Это прикол какой-то да Я откупил
you from the police ex
тебя от полиции бывшего
employer for fun what
работодателя ради прикола что
or I will return you to them for
ли или я тебя верну к ним для
proceedings or you go to work for
разбирательства или ты иди работать на
me
меня
for such a salary
вот за такую зарплату
Why me? You saw what happened there.
Почему я Вы же видели что случилось там
That's exactly why I need you
именно Именно поэтому Ты нужен мне
Vladislav you
Владислав ты
a simple, very simple man of the people
простой очень простой человек из народа
who is not afraid of the Brave
который не боится Смелых
solutions to highlight
решений подсветить
[ __ ] tank with a lighter this is very bold
[__] бак зажигалкой это Очень смело
she's a dangerous [ __ ]
опасно [__] она
someone might boldly say that this is stupid
смело кто-то может скажет что это глупо
as you know on Channel One Let
как на Первом канале знаешь Пусть
[laughter]
[смех]
They say it's dangerous but bold Sorry
говорят опасно но смело Извините
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
was at someone's graduation, but here he is mine
ком то на выпускном был А вот он мой
suit
костюмчик
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Vladislav Viktorovich what is my name Sasha
Владислав Викторович что меня зовут Саша
I am your driver, order to work and
Я ваш водитель распоряжение на работу и
from work only on this
с работы только на этой
car and you will have to change clothes
машине и вам придётся переодеться
[music]
[музыка]
doors
двери
I'm closing
закрываю
Hello, this is the very thing for me
Здравствуйте это самое Мне вот
Hello there Marina this is Vladislav
там здравствуйте Марина это Владислав
Polikov is your new CEO
поликов ваш новый генеральный директор
oh sorry i was just looking for your photos in
ой Извините я просто искала ваши фото в
I didn't find Vlad on the Internet; he worked little in
интернете не нашла Влад мало работал в
Russia You understand this is international
России Ты же понимаешь это международный
level How is the meeting, everyone gathered
уровень Как там совещание все собрались
Of course we'll go to the meeting
конечно совещание пойдём
I'll show you right away in battle And I know how you wanted it
покажу сразу в бой А как ты хотел я знаю
what does this need
что нужно этому
kana is exactly his own series
кана именно свой собственный серий
straightaway
сразу
I
я
You're stunned, but I've never done this before.
обалдели а Я же никогда не делал
there is no need to make TV series that are just lovely
сериалов прелесть делать не надо просто
you're in charge, you're watching TV, well, that's it
руководи ты телик смотришь Ну вот и
tell them what you want them to see
говори им то что ты хочешь увидеть они
will fulfill I give you
будут выполнять даю тебе
Karlan, what are you telling me?
карлан че Вы мне
let me create any [ __ ]
дадите Твори любую херню
[music]
[музыка]
With
с
Anya This is just awful I don't understand at all
Аня Это просто ужас Я вообще не понимаю
what am I doing here I sat and listened for an hour
что я тут делаю Я целый час сидел слушал
about some kind of channel policy about broadcasting
про какую-то политику канала про эфирную
grid about budget and about ratings about
сетку про бюджет и про рейтинги про
program committee whatever it is and
программный комитет чтобы это ни было и
about the fact that I am now taking over production
про то что я теперь увожу производством
series and one person even fainted
сериала а один человек вообще в обморок
fell down You have confused me with someone else
грохнулся Ты меня ни с кем перепутал
Vlad I am your ex-wife Why tell me
Влад я твоя бывшая жена Зачем мне скажи
Vlad
Влад
was to listen So who else should I call?
было слушать Так кому мне ещё звонить а
it was that now there was a claim I didn't
это что сейчас претензия была Я не
I understand. Well, don't be a sheep. Don't call.
поняла А ну не будь овцой ты ну не звони
more here
сюда больше
[ __ ] Hello, I'm Masha, the secretary
[__] Да здравствуйте я Маша секретарша
your oh
ваша ой
poems Well Remember I'm here at the door
стихи Ну Помните я тут у двери
I'm sitting here A yes I remember Sorry mate
сижу А да Припоминаю Извини мато
all the ponies piled up
навалилось всего пони
I'm fine And I mean there
у меня всё в порядке А я в смысле там
scriptwriters came up with ideas for TV series
сценаристы пришли идеи для сериалов
will be
будут
to imagine this is what is called
представлять это и называется
pitching Hello, my name is Oleg
питчинг Здравствуйте меня зовут Олег
Zotov I worked in a team of authors on
Зотов Я работал в команде авторов на
in such series as Crime Experts
таких сериалах как криминал эксперты
victim and killers Crime 2 I have
жертва и убийцы Криминал 2 У меня есть
series concept
концепция сериала
which I saw all this This is hellish
который я всё это видел Это адское
I'm crossing out the crap Well, he hasn't yet
говнище вычёркиваю Ну он же ещё не
told his
рассказал свою
the idea of compulsory
идею обязательного
listen Probably not
слушать Наверное нет
Well, I worked on the comedy Hospital
Ну а я работал над комедия больница
institute restaurant hotel Torosyan
институт ресторан гостиница Торосян
funny
смешные
[music]
[музыка]
I cross out all the stupid heroes
вычёркиваю все герои тупые
jokes
шутки
[music]
[музыка]
idiot women
дебильные баба
scary guy wild
страшная мужик диковатый
[music]
[музыка]
oh sorry Valery we're just looking
а извините Валерий просто мы ищем
screenwriter for the series And you
сценариста на сериал А у вас
There is only one line in the filmography and that is it
фильмографии только одна строчка и та
cartoon
мультфильм
Well, I'm going. Yeah. And what cartoon is Cat?
Ну я пошёл Угу А какой мультфильм Кот
Coconut and its
Кокос и его
friends cat
друзья кот
Coconut cat
Кокос кот
Coconut you invented the cat
Кокос вы придумали кота
coconut Well yes he is, yes I grew up on it
кокоса Ну да он бо да я вырос на этом
cartoon What are you talking about Coconut Funny cat
мультфильме Да вы что Кокос Весёлый кот
everyone knows it, it will save you from worries
это знают все он избавит от забот
adults and children y Yes, I watched it
взрослых и детей й Да я же смотрел я
I know the Supreme Court by heart, we know you
знаю ВС наизусть мы вас
[music]
[музыка]
let's take it Dasha you don't understand something about this
берём Даша ты что-то не понимаешь это
this man is a genius he invented the cat
этот человек гений он придумал кота
Coconut
Кокос
It's me Masha, okay, I understand, there is a scriptwriter
Это я Маша ну окей поняла сценарист есть
[music]
[музыка]
Yes, Ladislav Viktorovich, this is Masha at all.
Да ладислав Викторович это Маша совсем
I forgot there. I left it with your driver.
забыла я там У вашего водителя оставила
flash drives with short film flash drives with
флешки с короткометражка флешки с
short film Well, yes, it's kind of like that
короткометражка Ну да это как бы
short
короткие
I know what the film is
филь знаю я что та
short films you start that Sorry
короткометражки начинаешь ту Извините
guilty yes of course In general you need them
виновата да конечно В общем вам нужно их
OTC on the subject of directing what to choose
ОТС на предмет режиссура что ну выбрать
one of the directors who will be
одного из режиссёров который будет
film our series
снимать наш сериал
A
А
you killed mine
ты убил Моего
partner And now I'm about
напарника И теперь я о
I trample This is for Yegor
топчу Это тебе за Егора
in some kind of geek
в гик какой-то в
geek directors these I don't have anything in this
гик режиссёры эти Ничего я в этом не
Understand
понимаю
directors
режиссёры
coconut come here where
кокос иди сюда где
you oh
ты ой
Coconut Where are you go
Кокос Где ты есть иди
oh your name is can't you hear or something
ой тебя зовут Ты что не слышишь что ли
Come here and help me become a better director.
Иди сюда поможешь мне лучшего режиссёра
choose well come on
выбрать ну-ка давай
work work
работай работай
work Yeah and Igor gets an Oscar from us
работай Ага и Оскар у нас получает Игорь
Nice to meet you, I've heard a lot about you
Приятно познакомиться очень наслышан на
you in a professional environment yes yes okay
вас в профессиональной среде да да ладно
interesting Vlad and Valery Yes we are
интересно Влад и Валерий Да мы
we met while we were waiting for you, we managed to
познакомились пока вас ждали успели м
talk I heard you looked at my
поговорить Я слышал вы посмотрели мою
short film and how do you like it
короткометражку и как вам
delicious Very delicious Thank you very much
вкусно Очень вкусно благодарю очень
there are many favorite places Beginning beginning
большо есть любимые места Начало начало
strong end end just tore
сильное конец конец просто порвал
Well, it wasn't me who broke the end, but the end broke me.
Ну не я порвал конец а конец порвал меня
of course I'm the end I didn't tear myself to pieces
конечно я конец меня конец не рвал в с
Well, in SS, that is, in the sense of the end, the end
Ну в СС то есть в смысле конец конец
end of the movie and tore it up
конец фильма Да и порвал
Here
вот
yes yes what did you want tea coffee something
да да что ты хотела Чай кофе что-нибудь
yes If you need coffee America And can I
да Если нужно кофе Америка А мне можно
viri 150
вири 150
and me then too Yes, [ __ ] coffee then too
и мне тогда Да нахер кофе тогда и мне
bring a bottle right away
принести сразу бутылку
Yes Oh listen How great it is here
Да Ой слушайте Как у вас здесь Здорово
This is my first time on the whiskey channel
мне вообще Впервые на канале виски
offer So look Vladislav we
предлагают Значит смотрите Владислав мы
We consulted with Valera while he was here
с Валерой посоветовались пока его здесь
there was no money because I know a little bit
не было поскольку денег знаю Немного то
our cinema it will be pavilions
наше кино оно будет павильоны
Well, in the scenery Well, that is, we will build
Ну в декорациях Ну то есть мы построим
decorations so that you don't go out at all
декорации чтобы вообще не выходить на
street A by genre melodrama only actors
улицу А по жанру мелодрама только актёры
talk screams tears nothing
разговоры крики слёзы никаких
special effects fight chases
спецэффектов Драк погонь
other things are reasonable Well yes Yes Yes Well here we are
прочего разумно Ну да Дада Ну вот и мы
So Valera and I came up with this idea
значит с Валерой накидали такую идею
look it's called
смотрите называется
triangle So there is a girl and two
треугольник Значит есть девушка и два
the guy they have been friends since childhood then
парня они дружат с детства потом
first feelings awaken girl
просыпаются первые чувства девушка
meets one of them But in Ta no
встречается с одним из них Но в Та не
loves the second one This second one leaves the army and
любит второго Этот второй уходит армию а
accordingly his friend marries this
соответственно его друг женится на этой
to the girl and then it turns out that the girl
девушке и потом оказывается что девушка
from him pregnant from whom from the second it is
от него беременна от кого От второго это
which husband no which in the army but she
который муж нет который в армии но она
She doesn't tell her husband. He thinks it's his.
мужу не говорит Он думает что это его
child Well then 20 years pass boy
ребёнок Ну потом проходит 20 лет мальчик
he's already grown up but his father doesn't know that he
уже вырос но его отец не знает что он
his father is the one in the army No no
его отец это тот который в армии Да нет
In which army has it been 20 years? He has long been
В какой армии уже 20 лет прошло Он давно
idiot him his business And here is the boy
дебильную него свой бизнес И вот мальчик
gets sick and needs to donate a kidney and
заболевает и нужно жертвовать почку и в
at this moment we understand who is real
этот момент мы понимаем кто настоящий
Father I understood this and
отец Я понял это и
a Sorry for interrupting Vladislav
а Извините что прерываю Владислав
Viktorovich is there to see you.
Викторович там к вам
Guide I am now
руководство Я сейчас
I'll be back, I came to see how ours are doing
вернусь пришёл проведать те как тут наша
Media
Медиа
star then proceed to production
звезда тогда приступаете к производству
I already feel like putting this masterpiece in
уже как-то хочется поставить шедевр в
broadcast And we are discussing it right now
эфир А мы как раз вот сейчас обсуждаем
plot a Well, please me there in general There
сюжет а Ну порадуй меня там в общем Там
girl and two guys Here she loves one
девушка и два парня Вот она любит одного
she's getting married to someone else, that's who
замуж выходит за другого вот того кого
loves him they take him into the army and that's why she's from
любит его забирают в армию вот и она от
he is pregnant Here then means well there
него беременна Вот Потом значит ну там
the son grows up and something happens there and
сын вырастает вот там что-то случается и
a kidney is needed there
там нужна почка
and stop what is this
и Стоп Это что
such What is this somehow too somehow
такое Что это как-то слишком както
ok but somehow banal like everyone else
хорошо да как-то банально Как у всех это
it doesn't look like i'm you
не похоже на то что я тебя
I'm waiting for you to do it yourself
жду Ты сам это
I came up with it, yes, tell it like it is, no, that's it
придумал да говори как есть нет это
scriptwriter director we suggested
сценарист режиссёр предложили мы
we are discussing it now and you with this
обсуждаем сейчас и ты с этим
I agree I don't know I understand I just
согласен я не знаю я поймите я я просто
I've never done this you want this
я никогда этого не делал ты это хочешь
I can see it on TV I can find it on
на телике видеть Я такое могу найти на
on any channel if you need it in Russia, here it is
любом канале если надо по России вон это
they play it from morning till night What are you talking about?
крутят с утра до ночи Ты что
Vlad, there's an advance on salary
Влад те там аванс по зарплате
transferred see SMS from the bank
перечислили посмотри СМС из банка
pieces zero
штук нули
[music]
[музыка]
recalculate if you don't want that
пересчитай вот если ты не хочешь чтобы
this is what the salary became
вот эта зарплата стала
last one Go there and make them do it
последней Иди туда и заставь их сделать
such
такой
Tai You've been dreaming about your whole life
Тай О котором ты мечтал всю свою жизнь
the word impossible does not exist for you
слово невозможно для тебя не существует
how long will they tell you what and how
сколько тебе будут указывать что и как
You should watch People put you here
должны смотреть Люди тебя поставили сюда
because you are the voice of the people you are the boss of no one
потому что ты Глас народа Ты босс никого
I'm not listening, you don't depend on anyone
не слушаю ты ни от кого не зависишь
Now they are [ __ ] gas station attendants And you are a [ __ ]
Теперь они бля заправщики А ты [__]
the director is [ __ ] stupid
директор это ёбаная без за колонки
go go make everything beautiful
иди Иди сделай всё красиво
[music]
[музыка]
So
так
friends the concept of our series
друзья концепция нашего сериала
two guys change girl It's already in
меняется два парня девушка Это уже в
in the past we will have two girls and one
прошлом у нас будут две девушки и один
let's say the guy suffers from loss alone
парень допустим одна страдает потере
the second memory was thrown into the child
памяти вторую в детстве подбросили в
shelter still guy son of a criminal
приют ещё парень сын криминального
authority himself is good both of His very
авторитета сам хороший обе Его очень
they love and want it very much, he doesn't want it and doesn't
любят и очень хотят он не хочет и не
loves no one but that's first later
любит никого но это сначала потом
penetrates into the one who has losses
проникается к той у которой потери
memory and helps her remember who she is
памяти и помогает ей вспомнить кто она
in fact and in fact she
на самом деле а на самом деле она
the missing millionaire who crashed
пропавшая миллионерша которая разбилась
on a plane over the taiga Over what taiga
на самолёте над тайгой Над какой тайгой
over the thick Well, somehow I survived and got out
над густой Ну выжила как-то выбралась и
since then she lives without knowing who she is
с тех пор вот живёт не зная Кто она а а
how did she end up in Moscow Valera I don't
как она оказалась в Москве Валера я не
I know how she ended up in Moscow, I know
знаю как она оказалась в Москве я я же
Just
просто
throw in write down Here it is all
накидывают записывайте Вот она всё
I remembered and found a state and then
вспомнила обрела состояние и тут
This second Foundling appears. And
появляется вот эта вторая Подкидыш А у
her with a guy love sex cheating passion
неё с парнем любовь секс измены страсть
and then it turns out that his
и потом выясняется что его
his father his father is a criminal element
отец его отец криминальный элемент
once ordered her parents and they were killed
когда-то заказал её родителей и их убили
But all this With all due respect
Но всё это При всём моём уважении
it's a little different from our previous one
немного расходится с нашей прошлой
concept I don't care here I
концепцией А мне плевать здесь я
director of this [ __ ] column And you [ __ ]
директор этой ёбаной колонки А вы [__]
refuellers what what
заправщики что Что
incomprehensible
непонятного
what are mine
что мои
refuellers I mean yes we refuel it
заправщики В смысле Да заправляем это
the product of our life with energy Well yes
произведение нашей жизнью энергией Ну да
we are of course great so here are the parents
это мы конечно отлично так вот родители
they knew they would be killed and got a tattoo
знали что их убьют и сделали татуировку
on his daughter's back with a map
на спине своей дочери с картой
I don't understand anything about hidden treasures
спрятанных сокровищ ничего не понимаю
what treasures Gold of the party Her father was
каких сокровищ Золото партии Её отец был
party treasurer and now she too
партийный казначей и теперь она тоже
rich even richer than that first one If
богатая даже богаче чем та первая Если
will be able to find
сможет найти
treasure and the guy needs to decide who he's with
сокровище а парню надо решить с кем он
will be And who will he help And her
будет И кому он будет помогать А ей
come to terms with the fact that his father is guilty
смириться с тем что его отец виновен е
Give birth or just take the opposite and
Родите или просто взять наоборот и
take revenge
отомстить
name triangle
название треугольник
we leave
оставляем
it's boring No
это скукотища Нет
this this will be
это это будет
be called [ __ ] Yeah
называться [__] Ага
No bloody
Нет кровавые
[ __ ] at
[__] у
no bloody
нет кровавые
[ __ ] in the pit
[__] в яме
bloody
кровавые
[ __ ] in
[__] в
in the pit
яме в
[music]
[музыка]
pit
яме
great, need to go out
прекрасно надо выйти
Stop Stop
Остановите Останови
watch the next episode And I'm out
смотрите в следующей серии А я же вон
now the head of the TV channel in
теперь во руководитель телеканала в
Last time I wasn't really impressed
прошлый раз меня как-то не очень
pleased with everything spent here always should
порадовал всё провел здесь всегда должно
be beer new broom sweeps in a new way A
быть пиво новая метла по новому метёт А
I'm not talking about the rest of the quirks
я не говорю про остальные закидоны на
at work I have to smile like I
работе мне приходится улыбаться типа я
I accept everything calmly and with joy
такая Всё спокойно принимаю и с радостью
I do, I implement ideas. Yes, of course, everything.
делаю воплощает идеи Да конечно всё
nonsense I'll give you such an operator
ерунда Я приведу вам такого оператора
that will just blow your mind. And also
что у вас просто крышу снесёт прям А ещё
It's time to start casting, what kind of actress is she?
Пора начинать кастинг а что за актриса
where did you study, I have a diploma, but I don't have a diploma
где училась диплом есть а я дипломом не
take it under no circumstances I will not take it under no circumstances
бери ни в коем случае не беру ни в коем
in her case That's just it
случае У неё Вот как раз
no earlier in
нет ранее в
series do you want us to start
сериале ты хочешь чтобы мы начали
show something that no one will watch
показывать то что никто смотреть не
the shares will become cheaper and we will buy them up
будет акции подешевеют и мы их скупим
We need a new CEO in full
полностью Нам нужен новый генеральный
director of the seventh column diesel
директор седьмая колоно дизел
create a product that Booth
создать такой продукт который Бут
hate everything
ненавидеть Все
[music]
[музыка]
viewers who will i become general
зрители кем я стану генеральным
director of the TV channel
директором телеканала
tsv ri any crap And this is just awful I
тсв ри любую херню А это просто ужас Я
I don't understand at all what I'm doing here
вообще не понимаю что я тут делаю не
call here again [ __ ] I'm Masha
звони сюда больше [__] я Маша
your secretary And you
секретарша ваша А у вас
fiya lzya
фия льзя
Igor Zhmykh will be filming our series
будет снимать наш сериал Игорь жмых
Nice to meet you It will be
Приятно познакомиться Это будет
be called bloody
называться кровавые
[ __ ] in
[__] в
poison cat make a check as before
ядне котк сделай чеку как раньше так
I wanted to all the time
хотелось всё время
straight Vlad
пря Влад
Hello Hello my dears Hello
привет Здравствуйте дорогие мои Привет
Uncle Dim Great, great Oh, something like that
дяд Дим Здорово здорово Ой что-то так
I missed you so much I don't know
соскучился по вам прямо вот не знаю вот
decided to stop by with new friends now
решил заехать с новыми друзьями сейчас
not really And we thought you were in jail Yes
не особо А мы думали тебя посадили Да
after you burned the car Yes, it's the Supreme Court
после того как ты машину сжёг Да это ВС
little things are nonsense, but now I'm in
мелочи ерунда Я же вон теперь во
the head of this TV channel
руководитель телеканала вот этого
this is your car Yes, with a driver And how
вот это твоя машина Да с водителем А как
that's how it happened Vlada
это так ВС это вышло-то Вла пое
some people are just created for success
некоторые люди просто созда для успеха я
I've been fighting for this my whole life
вот всю свою жизнь к этому шёл боролся
for every step And here I am at the top You are the same
за каждый шаг И вот я на вершине Ты же
you were always drinking, that's why your wife left you
бухал всегда жена тебя бросила поэтому
so that you understand this Kat, well this is
чтоб ты в этом понимала Кать ну это же
path of life challenges series of motivations
путь жизненных вызовов череда мотиваций
Tony Robins
Тони робинс
So we are we are happy for you
ёпта Так мы это мы рады за тебя мы
We Okay, why did I stop by here?
мы Ладно я что заехал то тут
I thought about it
подумал вот
that's what
вот что
trip to the Maldives I remember you
путёвка на Мальдивы Я же помню тебя
the picture is on the phone's screensaver
картинка там на заставке в телефоне
you were standing there, you wanted to save up for your old age, here
стоял ты на старость хотела накопить вот
now you'll fly and have a rest, young
сейчас полетишь отдохнёшь молодая
I don't understand what the hell you're doing
я Нихрена не понимаю чем ты занимаешься
in life and what do you love
по жизни и что ты любишь
so just go ahead and make some money
поэтому вот тебе просто бабку и делай
whatever you want
что хочешь
[music]
[музыка]
on
на
see you
увидимся
It's unreal where he got everything from
нереально откуда у него всё
someone is drilling into his hollow
это кто-то долбит его в дупло
[music]
[музыка]
you can go crazy, you understand, I just
это можно сойти с ума понимаешь я только
only now only now I realized that
только теперь только теперь понял что
they all have to listen to me. And where?
они все все должны меня слушаться А где
beer beer Well, we don't keep it here
пиво пиво Ну мы так-то не держим здесь
there should always be beer very cold
всегда должно быть пиво много холодное
light dark don't give a [ __ ] and chips Chips too
светло Тёмное похуй и чипсы Чипсы тоже
I don't give a [ __ ] how fast you learn and I do
похуй какие ты быстро учишься и мне
nobody nobody can do anything I
никто никто ничего не может сделать я
I can act like a deputy
могу себя как замм
the indicators have improved significantly in
показатели существенно улучшились в
Prime and pre
Прайм и пред
Prime disla Viktorovich yes yes I am with you
Прайм дисла Викторович да да я с вами я
I hear everything, for example, yesterday I
всё слышу вот например Вчера я я
scanned mine
отсканировал свою
the ass even came out a little with bells
жопу даже немного с бубенцами получилось
made me print this on
заставил распечатать это на
The canvas said that this is the work of a fashionable
холсте сказал что это работа модного
the artist called the eight symbol
художника называется восьмёрка символ
infinity And hung straight
бесконечности И повесил прямо
to the office
в офи сть
enjoy class native will flow and
наслаждаются класс родной литься будем а
then time goes by And I also made for each
то время идёт А ещё я заставил за каждую
if an employee is late for a minute, he has to stand for an hour
минуту опоздания сотрудника стоять час
on
на
knees It's simple
коленях Это просто
fire
огонь
say
гови
I put a small list of moments here
моментов ставил тут небольшой список
The guys from V Geek are all very smart
ребят из в гика все очень толковые
some are even TV series
некоторые уже даже сериалы
they're filming it all nonsense I'll give you
снимают это всё ерунда Я приведу вам
such an operator that you just go crazy
такого оператора что у вас просто крышу
it will blow you away, fum I have a question Yes, the thing is
снесёт прям фум У меня вопрос Да дело в
that I'm a retrograde Valery Please
том что я ретроград Валер Пожалуйста
please I don't like it very much I
прошу тебя я не очень это люблю Мне в
in principle, by and large, it doesn't matter who
принципе по большому счёту всё равно кто
who [ __ ] but when he [ __ ] old women
кого трахает но когда долбит старушек
it's somehow
это как-то
disrespectfully Vladislav Yes old ladies
неуважительно Владислав Да старушек
they're hammering NFI
долбят нфи
a retrograde is an opponent of progress
ретроград - это противник прогресса
and Rotten
а Трухлявый
so I write the script only by hand
так вот я пишу сценарий только от руки
I don't use a typewriter or a computer
ни машинкой ни компьютером не пользуюсь
so i did just a caucus of kos Funny cat
так я делал всего кокус кос Весёлый кот
everyone knows it, it will save you from worries
это знают все он избавит от забот
adults and
взрослых и
children every day
детей каждый ть
so she quickly prints it all out
тек она быстренько всё это распечатывает
everything is on the computer, but I was so freaked out by lunchtime
на компе всё да я же охренел к обеду что
this proverb is not about that, I don't give a [ __ ] what we have
это пословица не об этом похуй что у нас
still there It's time to start casting We have two
ещё там Пора начинать кастинг У нас две
the main female roles are one male and
главные женские роли одна мужская и у
I have an ideal candidate
меня есть идеальный кандидат
A
А
nepotism well here are our wonderful
кумовство ну вот наши замечательные
the artists will now act out a scene from
артисты они сечас разыграют сцену из
first
первой
series which I wrote specifically for
серии кою писал собственно для
sample this is interesting yes yes guys
проб это интересно да да ребят
ready
готовы
And
и
I started, I'm not afraid
начали я не боюсь
[laughter]
[смех]
the end is not a joke
конца это раз не шутка
was
была
keep going guys Let's do it one more time and
продолжайте ребят Давайте Ещё разочек и
I started, I'm not afraid
начали я не боюсь
the end is not as scary as I thought
конца конец не так страшен как я его
to yourself
себе
I imagined it but I'm afraid to bow down before
представляла но я боюсь склониться перед
end Violetta I don't want you
концом Виолетта Я не хочу чтобы ты
bowed before the end the end awaits us
склонялось перед концом конец ждёт нас
all
всех
[music]
[музыка]
What is this, I even shed a tear like that
Что такое я даже слезу пустила меня так
this text breaks through Katya Don't pay attention
этот текст пробивает Катенька Не обращай
he just doesn't understand anything about attention
внимания он просто ничего не понимает в
strong modern dramaturgy still has power
сильной современной драматургии още силу
the text does not feel about the World Cup
текста не чувствует о ЧМ
y
й
oh my god something just tore right into the closet
госпо ой что-то прям разорвало пря в кло
Sorry, the joke is funny
Извините анекдот смешной
I remembered the director there Come on
вспомнил режиссёра там А ну давайте
let's listen Well, let's listen to one actress
послушаем Ну ну давайте одна актриса
says another imagine what it's like for me
говорит другой представляешь что мне
said this stupid director approved on
сказал этот тупой режиссёр утвердил на
Roles says What does it say I approve of you
роли говорит Что говорит я вас утверждаю
But I naturally gave him a role without words right away.
Но роль без слов я ему естественно сразу
laughed in
рассмеялась в
eggs Why are you crying this is it
яйца Почему вы плачете это же это
anecdote is a joke It's not about you Yes
анекдот это же шутка Это не про вас Да
why are you doing this to me? I am a graduate of GITIS
что вы так со мной Я выпускница гитиса
Katya, that's not what he meant, that's not what I meant.
Катенька он не это имел в виду я не это
meant
имел в виду
Katya, I just need Vladislav now
Катенька я просто Владислав надо сейчас
urgently do something you understand that
срочно что-то делать вы понимаете что
actresses are people with unstable psyche
актрисы они люди с расшатанной психикой
you understand if after such an insult
понимаете если после такого оскорбления
If she doesn't get the role, it's all suicide
ей не дать роль это всё суицид
and dead ones
а дохлые
butter and then later they are journalists
маслят а потом потом ещ журналисты они
they will start digging up all this, what and why
начнут всё это раскапывать что почему
all this will come out to us, it's not at all
это всё выйдет наружу нам это вообще не
I need everything
надо Всё я
I am Katya Katya I ask you again
я Катя Катя я ещё раз прошу у вас
sorry This was a joke this is a joke
прощения Это это был Анекдот это шутка
to cast you in the role and
чтобы взять вас на роль и
it's all true, it's true, we'll take you
всё правда правда мы вас берём надо
approve all three so that no one
утвердить всех троих чтобы никто не
he blabbed so we take everyone we take everyone
проболтался так мы всех берём мы всех
we claim that we can do this no more
утверждаем можно к этому больше не
please come back Thank you Yes
возвращаться пожалуйста Спасибо Да
of course he is a loser
конечно вот он лошар
I bought it Katya, you're just awesome
купился Катя ты Ты просто классная
actress guys we are all great Igor
актриса ребята мы все Молодцы Игорь
thanks for the debt to you old roles
спасибо долгу перед тобой стари ролей
not at all yes yes of course in debt and
совсем нет да да конечно в долгу и
remember everything about the debt size of 15%
помним все о размере долга 15% от
fee
гонорара
each Well what Vladislav next a
каждый Ну что Владислав следующих а
next Why not
следующих Зачем не
we need to start from the very first yes the very first yes
надо с самых первых да самых первых да
Well, maybe you should watch Why Mash, well, under
Ну может вых смотреть Зачем Маш ну под
a lying stone and no water flows Yes And what about it
лежачий камень и вода не течёт Да Причём
here it is uh the proverb is not about that
здесь это э пословица не об этом она
inaction do nothing do nothing
бездействии ничего не делать ничего не
it will work out you had to become
получится тебе нужно было становиться
obstetrician what do you like to get
акушером чего Любишь доставать
people ladies and gentlemen casting as if
людей дамы и господа кастинг как бы
finished and in general sorry moth I won't
окончен и в общем Извините мот я не буду
I'm already ashamed
Мне и так стыдно
[music]
[музыка]
the picture he made
картина которую он заставил
hang it up his ass AK Serena and
повесить это его [__] АК Серена и
transferred to canvas covered with varnish and I
перенесённая на холст покрытая лаком и я
presented it to the team
её презентовала перед коллективом
and she hangs there and every time I
и она там висит и каждый раз как я
I'm going through it
прохожу её
I see
вижу
Maria Maybe because
Мария Может быть из-за
accumulate you perceive everything a little
накапливают вы всё воспринимаете немного
otherwise
иначе
Well, modern paintings are sometimes like that
ну современные картины иногда так
written What is difficult to say what it is
написаны Что трудно сказать что это
abstraction She is the ass doctor ass
абстракция Она же это [__] доктор [__]
ass buns point bottom lower floor
срака булки точка днище нижний этаж
Bumper understood everything
бампер понял всё
did you understand?
понял вы
Calm down
Успокойтесь
exhale Or maybe it's not his memory Yes
выдохните А может быть это не его пам Да
What the hell difference does it make? It doesn't matter to me
какая нахер разница Мне от этого не
easier And I'm not talking about the rest
легче А я не говорю про остальные
I have quirks at work too
закидоны и на работе мне приходится
smile like I'm like this Everything is calm
улыбаться типа я такая Всё спокойно
I accept and do it with joy. And he also tells me
принимаю и с радостью делаю А ещё он мне
gave this scriptwriter into slavery
отдал в рабство этому сценарист который
Filin writes by hand and only at night
от руки пишет и только по ночам Филин
[ __ ] hell and today I have to go and
[__] и сегодня мне идти и
decipher into writing quietly quietly
расшифровывать на писанину тихо тихо
calm calm quiet quiet quiet quiet
спокойно спокойно тихо тихо тихо тихо
sit down everything is fine everything is fine
садитесь всё хорошо всё хорошо
we'll give you some pills to drink pills A
таблеточки дадим вам попить таблеточки А
here you calm down in the process of work
вот успокаиваться в процессе работы вам
necessary
надо
learn Now tell me what gives you pleasure
научиться Вот скажите что доставляет вам
It's a joy, I don't do this at work
радость этим я на работе заниматься не
Can I talk about hobbies?
могу я про хобби а
Well, I'm a science fiction writer.
Ну я фантастику
I love all sorts of books about parallelism
люблю книжки там всякие про параллельное
The Universe even tries its own
Вселенная даже вот свою пытаюсь
write nonsense there of course But here it is
писать глупости там конечно Но вот и
great as soon as it starts rolling in
прекрасно как только начнёт накатывать
stress immediately go and write your book
стресс сразу идёте и пишете свою книгу
just feel that you let go and
только почувствуйте что отпустила и
return to
возвращаетесь к
work of the wheel Give Dada of course
работе колёса Дайте Дада конечно
oh oh how good I am
ой ой как я хорошо
worked all home home home home
поработал всё домой домой домой домой
home
домой
Hello Who are you I am Sveta And I am Sveta
Здравствуйте Ты кто Я Света А Света я
the actress came to audition today a a
актриса на пробу сегодня приходила а а
Are you one of those? So they all left.
ты из этих что ли Так они ушли все
something remained so I didn't
что-то Осталась так я же так не
I tried And you I suppose Vladislav
попробовала А вы Я полагаю Владислав
Viktorovich, you are the boss here, yes, yes
Викторович Вы здесь главный да Да
Try me and you will see I am perfect
Попробуйте меня вы убедитесь я идеально
I'm coming Naro Try it already taken
подхожу Наро Попробуйте уже взяли
Naro 10 minutes I will demonstrate everything
Наро 10 минут я продемонстрирую весь
your talent there and where
свой талант туда да куда
Yes
Да
Yes, but I don't have a partner, you'll have to give me one
да только партнёра нет вам придётся мне
play along No, I don't know the lyrics
подыграть Не а я не знаю текст слова у
he has no words it's love
него нет слов это любовная
scene understand Herman my love for you
сцена пойми Герман Моя любовь к тебе
will be eternal as a series of cherry blossoms
будет вечной как череда цветение сакуры
at the foot
у подножья
Fujiyama My love for you is so strong
фудзиямы Моя любовь к тебе так сильна
that I'm ready to suck myself right here
что я готова отсосать себя прямо здесь
Holy [ __ ], we had such words there.
Нихера себе у нас такие слова там были
This
это
improvisation here you go
импровизация держите
please river for
пожалуйста река за
lure for you
люре за ти
Who's there?
Кто там
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Yes Vladislav Hello Igorek is with me
ещё Да Владислав Алло Игорёк у меня для
you are bad
тебя плохие
news
новости
[music]
[музыка]
How do you manage to write a sheet of paper with your hand?
сти Как вы рукой успеваете написать лист
faster than I can type for decades
быстрее чем я печатаю десятки лет
practices But here I dont understand your handwriting
практики А вот тут не пойму у вас почер
such Herman I don't understand your feelings in
такой Герман Я не понимаю твоих чувств в
my side Violetta comes out loud
мою сторону Виолетта выходит громко
slamming the door it seems you 5
хлопнув дверью кажется кажется вы 5
minutes ago they wrote well this is my handwriting
минут назад написали ну почерк такой я
I don't always understand him, awesome. And I
его не всегда понимаю зашибись А я-то
how should Mashenka's daughter understand him?
как должна его понять Машенька дочка не
make noise and work for now and I'll go have some tea
шуми поработай пока А я Пойду чайку
I'll brew it with buns, I need others now
заварю с плюшками мне сейчас другие
You'll need some goodies
плюшки понадобятся Какие никакие
Sorry, I'll work.
Извините я поработаю
[music]
[музыка]
as soon as stress starts to roll in
как только начнёт накатывать стресс
go straight away and write your own
сразу идёте и пишете свою
book
книгу
Violetta comes out loud
Виолетта выходит громко
slapping
хлопнув
the door but then
дверю но потом
Violetta is back
возвращается Виолетта
Herman And you?
Герман А ты
have you heard anything?
слышал что-нибудь
O
о
parallel universes
параллельных вселенных
Herman No, what is this?
Герман Нет а что это
[music]
[музыка]
Violetta o
Виолетта о
My love, I am everything to you now
Любимый я тебе сейчас всё
in Vladislav Sorry, just here
в Владислав Извините вот тут просто
appeared
появились
such
такие
fantastic elements of what Well, well, well
фантастические элементы чего Ну ну вот
For example
например
it turns out that Violetta is a double from
оказывается что Виолетта - это дубль из
parallel universe where the war is going on
параллельной вселенной Где идёт Война
corgis and the fleet fleet
коргов и флоту флоту
fleet you know Well I mean that in
флоту понимаете Ну я имею в виду что в
original concept of [ __ ] in my opinion
оригинальной концепции шлюх по-моему
this is not
этого не
Well, Valery probably knows that he
было Ну Валерий наверное знает что он
he does it, he wrote the cat ko kosa and you
делает он же написал кота ко коса а вы
remember what a powerful story you have there
помните какая там сильная история ты
[ __ ], Igor, you're [ __ ] awesome, you're a well-deserved person
охуел Игорь ты охуел заслуженный человек
he writes us a script, it's a miracle that we are
пишет нам сценарий чудо вообще что мы
we persuaded him to work with us, listen
уговорили его с нами работать слушайте
It's a miracle that this man is alive.
чудо вообще что он жив Этот человек
Age is not an indicator of professionalism
возраст не показатель профессионализма
Igor Von, Uncle Dima is at our gas station
Игорь Вон у нас на заправки дяд Дима
electrician he is almost 70 he can wi-fi
электрик ему под 70 он может wi-fi
set up for which gas station what the [ __ ]
настроить на какой заправки какая хуй
What difference does it make at which gas station?
разница На какой заправке это вобще еть
Not
не
should So let's get down to business then if
должно Так давайте к делу значит если
Valera wrote it, so that's how it should be
Валера написал значит так оно и нужно
Only with him we can break the bank Oh
только с ним и сможем сорвать банк Ой
They write here that Simonov, the shareholder, will arrive
тут пишут что Симонов акционер прибудет
in 10 minutes sit down quickly
через 10 минут ный рот сиди быстро
get into the script
вникай в сценарий
I don't like science fiction
ял не любите фантастику
No, I don't like it
Да нет не люблю
I am very glad to see you, everything is very good
Я очень рад вас видете очень всё хорошо
I don't know about you Vlad Yes, tell me
у вас не знаю Влад Да ты мне скажи в
Last time I wasn't really impressed
прошлый раз меня как-то не очень
made me happy And I probably fixed everything
порадовал А я всё исправил наверное
embodies must warn you there is
воплощает должен вас предупредить есть
some administrative innovations
некоторые административные нововведения
Well, for example, punishment for being late.
нука Ну например наказание за опоздание
there you have to stand on your knees for a new broom
там на коленях надо стоять о новая метла
in a new way
по-новому
sweeps And also still more
метёт А ещё ещё
There are still new paintings hanging in the office, but I
там ещё картины новые в офисе висят но я
I was thinking of taking them off before your arrival, you never know
думал их снять к вашему приезду мало ли
you won't like it because it's about talking
вам не понравится потому что о говори
they look like ass but it's not ass
они на жопу похожи но это не [__] Это
contemporary art Vlad is great
современное искусство Влад молодец надо
build everything for yourself Thank you, the movie has started
всё строить под себя Спасибо начал кино
re-watch Well, what to be in the topic Here
пересматривать Ну что в теме быть Вот
Gladiator looked great what he introduced
гладиатора посмотрел прекрасно что ввёл
on the channel a new form of welcome
на канале новую форму приветственного
qualities that go to death are welcomed
качества идущие на смер приветствуют
you
тебя
It's [ __ ] awesome that there's no one else
Заебись что никого больше не
found there were two more but I removed them
нашли там было ещё двое но я их убрал а
what kind of actress is this, where did she study, do you have a diploma?
что за актриса где училась диплом есть а
I don't take it with a diploma under any circumstances
я с дипломом не бери ни в коем случае не
I will not remove it under any circumstances. That's exactly what she has.
уберу ни в коем случае У неё Вот как раз
no great Well what the hell do we need this for
нет отлично Ну какой Чёрт нам это
Education is like blinders on our eyes
образование это же шоры на глазах нам
everything needs to be new. What did you take and what was the sample?
нужно всё новое А что взяли что проба
was good no no just say it there
была хорошая нет нет просто там говори
as it is as it is well well speak [ __ ]
как есть как есть ну ну Говори [__]
she sucked me
сосала она мне
no Vlad Yes, you're just Well, you're just
нет Влад Да ты просто Ну вот ты просто
you made me happy today you will get a bonus
ты меня сегодня порадовал получишь бонус
work as before, only faster
работай как прежде только быстрее
The script for the first episodes is already ready. It's necessary already.
сценарий первых серий уже готов Надо уже
I understand everything when I shoot No, everything is written
снимать то я понимаю всё Нет всё пишется
everything will be soon but they appeared there
всё скоро будет но там появились
fantastic
фантастические
notes No it's a melodrama Yes but
нотки Нет это мелодрама Да но
there is a bit of a parallel universe there
там есть немного параллельной вселенной
war of the corgis and
война коргов и
fleets it's simple
флотов это просто
Wonderful
прекрасно
Hello Hello, are you
здравствуйте Здравствуйте вы к
Vladislav Viktorovich, he is busy now
Владиславу Викторовича он сейчас занят
Yes
да
I'll wait Vasily chicken operator
подожду Василий куриной оператор
and Vlad spoke about you, he praised you very much
а Влад про вас говорил очень вас хвалил
Well, while he's free, let's go, I'll tell you.
А ну пока он освободится Пойдёмте я вас
with the director
с режиссёром
I'll introduce you Dad I don't know what to do I I
познакомлю Пап я не знаю что делать я я
I'm afraid to give you the last name. I'm serious.
боюсь передать фамилию Я тебе серьёзно
I say the director's dynasty of Zhmykhov
говорю режиссёрская династия жмыхов
won't stand for this
этого не вытерпит
Dad dad I understand that you have a Land Cruiser
Папа пап Я понимаю что у тебя Крузак в
credit but how can I withdraw it You
кредите но как я могу это снимать Ты
do you know what they wrote here
знаешь что они тут написали
and you listen I'll read it to you now here
а ты послушай Я тебе сейчас прочитаю тут
that the scene does not take for example
что сцены не возьми например
first the heroes kiss and then she
вот сначала герои целуются потом она
goes out to the bathroom and comes back already
выходит ванную а возвращается уже
infected
заражённая
food food nothing And who dad food corgi -
корм корм ничем А кем папа корм корги -
this is ra from a parallel universe that
это ра из параллельно Вселенной которы
settles inside people with his own
селится внутри людей зарах своим
destructive thinking through absorption
деструктивным мышлением через поглощение
spinal cord This is the pa
спинного мозга Вот это па
ta SN in not remember such plot twists
та СН во не пом таких сюжетных поворотов
this is super everything I can't talk about kissing
это супер вс не могу говорить по целую
Let's
давай
I'll call you back Meet Igor Zhmykh ours
перезвоню Знакомьтесь Игорь жмых наш
director And this is Vasily Kurey, cameraman from
режиссёр А это Василий курей оператор от
Vladislava
Владислава
Viktorovich call me chicken call me everything
Викторовича зовите меня курино меня все
that's what they call it, that is, professional
так зовут о то есть профессиональная
nickname I know that many cool people have
кличка Я знаю что у многих крутых
operators it is
операторов она есть
Yes, sorry, but your last name is not on
Да Простите просто Ваша фамилия не на
I guess I'm not familiar with S's work
слуху наверное не знаком с работами С
what kind of work
какими работами
Well, what were you filming? I didn't really do anything special.
Ну что Вы снимали Да я так особо ничего
Well, I brought a flash drive if
Ну я принёс флешку если
need Yes yes Come on Sit down
надо Да да Давайте Присаживайтесь
Oh come on, you were filming Gorko.
О да ладно Это же Горько Вы снимали
Gorko Igor is not Gorko
Горько Игорь это не Горько
this is a shitty film
это хреново снятая
wedding in the sense
свадьба в смысле
wedding you shoot weddings Well
свадьба вы снимаете свадьбы Ну
yes, and you make movies Well
да а кино вы снимаете Ну
this is not a movie this is a wedding Wait
вот это не кино это свадьба Подожди
wait look at
подожди смотри на
your fiance
жениха твою
mother Vladislav
мать Владислав
then you understand he brought the operator here
то понимаешь он прил сюда оператора
who filmed his wedding super
который снимал его свадьбу супер
by Listen
по Послушай
give up this crap
сда вот этой хуйнёй
Mihu was told that it was fashionable and people around
миху сказали что это модно а люди вокруг
All this goes into
во ходят Всё это
Nu internet for the whole look what's there
ню интернет за весь посмотри что там
smart people write about this you you
умные люди про это пишут вас же вас же
This [ __ ] is used to zombify people
этой хуйнёй зомбируют
there is no manda in cigarettes there is a leaf
манда в сигаретах нету этого там лист
tobacco like this zavr And here we need and
табачный вот так вот завр А здесь нада и
in this water, [ __ ], they dilute the mountain leg, [ __ ], A
в эту воду [__] бодяжат гор ноге бляд А
you've been smoking this for years and there in
ты ты это годами куришь а там в
There's some [ __ ] scumbag sitting in Washington
Вашингтоне сидит Чёрт бляд какой-нибудь
Just press the button and off you go
кнопочку вот так хуяк нажал и ты побежал
for these pinheads
за этих пиндосов
ri didn't guess mzhe poizhen VS need to be on
ри не догадывался мже поим ВС надо на
fingers explain you wait you Anya you
пальцах объяснять ты подожди ты Аня ты
I told my father about this
батюшке ходил с эти насчёт этого
I'll say this is Satan's dick you suck dick with
скажу это хуй сатаны ты сосёшь хуй с
Satan [ __ ] Vladi what the [ __ ] are you talking about
сатаны [__] Влади Ты что [__] несёшь
this is your brother Yura and I am your brother Yura sucks
это вый брат Юра А я твой брат Юра сосёт
Satan's dick and you too By the way, not everything
хуй сатаны и с тобой Между прочим не всё
[music]
[музыка]
ok come on come on
ладно давай давай
to
ко
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
ko clearly removed will give
ко чётко снял даст
[music]
[музыка]
ABOUT
О
started button
началось кнопку
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Look what's there in the next episode
нали смотрите в следующей серии что там
according to the situation I want the series already
по ситуации Я хочу сериал есть уже
actress but there are three of us main but me
актриса но там нас главных трое но я
I eat two
двоих ем
fly ariu today sent printed
реять ариу сегодня прислали отпечатанный
I saw this script for the first episodes there
сценарии первых серий увидел там эту
line with parallel universes
линию с параллельными вселенными
incinerating fleet and all this is not
испепеляющий флот и вот это всё не
there's enough bloody action from non-sop to
хватает кровавого экшена от не соп до
fantasy you need Star footnote
фантастика вам нужна Звезда сноской
Let's
Давай
let's try there there is one from Hollywood
попробуем там чки есть один из Голливуда
This is Brilliant T You got us a star
это Гениально Т Ты достал нам звезду
Games
Игры
thrones best job on earth
престолов лучшая работа на Земле
earlier in the series you want us to
ранее в сериале ты хочешь чтобы мы
they started showing things that no one would watch
начали показывать то что никто смотреть
if there is no stock, it will become cheaper and we will buy them up
не будет акции подешевеют и мы их скупим
We need a new CEO in full
полностью Нам нужен новый генеральный
[music]
[музыка]
director who will i become general director
директор к кем я стану генеральным
Director of the TV channel TSV Create any
директором телеканала тсв Твори любую
crap This is just awful I don't know at all
херню Это просто ужас Я вообще не
I understand what I'm doing here, don't call here
понимаю что я тут делаю не звони сюда
I'm more of an [ __ ], Masha, your secretary. A
больше [__] я Маша секретарша ваша А
what cartoon is Kotka Kos and his friends
какой мультфильм Котка кос и его друзья
choose a director who will shoot
выбрать режиссёра который будет снимать
our series Igor Zhmykh And I will bring you
наш сериал Игорь жмых А я приведу вам
this is the kind of operator you shoot weddings with Well
такого оператора вы снимаете свадьбы Ну
yes It's time to start casting and actress And what
да Пора начинать кастинг и актриса А что
they took that sample
взяли что проба была
good As soon as it starts rolling in
хорошая Как только начнёт накатывать
stress immediately go and write your book
стресс сразу идёте и пишете свою книгу
the script for the first episode is already ready there
сценарий первой серии уже готов там
fantastic notes appeared
появились фантастические нотки
[music]
[музыка]
Hello
Алло
What
что
who called there and Bondarchuk said that
там звонил кто да Бондарчук сказал что
already naked really wants you as a woman
уже голый очень хочет вас женским
voice
голосом
and Oksanka is a lively girl, 23 years old
а Оксанка заводная девчонка 23 года
the sportswoman is fire what could I answer her
спортсменка огонь че мог ей ответить
say that I'll come today and [ __ ] her
сказать что я приеду сегодня трахну её
like a [ __ ] Why did she call from the number
как сучку А почему она звонила с номера
Bondarchuk Bondarchuk just from his wife
Бондарчука Бондарчук просто от жены так
I wrote down okay what's the situation Yes
записал ладно что там по ситуации Да
Listen I want the series Vlad I want it like
Слушай я хочу сериал Влад я хочу его как
Oksana now even more I understand
вот Оксан сейчас даже больше Я понимаю
So almost everything is already there, there is an operator
Значит уже почти всё есть есть оператор
Dream Team As far as you remember
команда Dream Team Насколько Вы помните
There is already an actress but we don't have any main ones there
есть уже актриса но там у нас главных
Three here But I'll find two more myself
трое Вот Но я двоих Ещё сам найду
I won't trust the director like this
режиссёру доверять не буду вот как
I wish I didn't have to trust anyone with everything
бы да всё никому доверять не надо
correct Valery Fedorovich general
правильно Валери Федорович генеральный
three And I look at the fortune teller correctly
тремя А я гадалку смотрю правильно По
you can see it
тебе видно
Valerie Hello dear we can
Валери Здравствуй дорогой мо можем
talk watched your film Gogol
переговорить смотрел ваш фильм Гоголь
The investigator is simply a revelation
следак это просто Откровение
[music]
[музыка]
Thank you, I'll [ __ ] you like crazy today
Спасибо я тебя сегодня трахну как
[ __ ] And what do you know about Pushkin?
сучку А что про Пушкина знае
guns are bad
пушки плохо
shoots shoots who knows because
стреляет стреляет хуй знает Потому что
[ __ ] hand-to-hand fighter [ __ ] Pushkin hand-to-hand fighter
[__] рукопашник бля Пушкин рукопашник
awesome idea, even has a name
охренительная идея даже название есть
for the first part Pushkin Petersburg
для первой части Пушкин Петербургская
Mesilovo Fu
месилово фу
fire openly
огонь открыто
Hello
Здравствуй
sit down today they sent a printed copy
садись сегодня прислали отпечатанный
scenarios of the first
сценарии первых
I reread the series and saw this there
серий я перечитал их увидел там эту
line with parallel universes war
линию с параллельными вселенными войной
korgov and the fleet ipem lot and this is it
коргов и флоту ипем лотом и вот это вот
Mashenka, please, just don't.
Машенька пожалуйста только не надо
tell or don't tell
рассказывать не рассказывай
I have not been to anyone for many years
никому я уже много лет в
tie Since then, since the time of the Cat
завязке С тех самых пор со времён Кота
But when I'm sober, it turns out I
Но когда я в завязке оказывается я
I had to come up with boring things a bit
придумываю скучные вещи пришлось немного
drink for
выпивать для
creativity
творчества
but I don't remember how I did it
но я не помню как я это
wrote that Well, that's all
написал что Ну вот это вот всё
I wrote this somehow, but how could I not?
Я ведь как-то это написал а как я не
I remember that is, you think that it is you
помню то есть вы думаете что это вы
wrote Well, who else are you, these
написали Ну а кто же ещё ты же сама эти
pages
страницы
received
получила
I deciphered it and what should everyone do now?
расшифровала а что теперь делать всем
I liked it so much
так понравилось
Vlad called and said management praise A
звонил Влад говорит руководство хвали А
what to do how to write further I don't know I
что делать как дальше писать Я не знаю я
I don't understand anything about this, but where
же в этом ничего не понимаю а Где
guarantee that if I drink again then
гарантия что если я ещё выпью то и
Mashenka will go on like this, but I
дальше так же пойдёт Машенька А я ведь
I live only on the interest from the coconut cat
Живу только на проценты с кота кокоса со
all these T-shirts from all these
всех этих маечек футболок со всех этих
repeated showing of this Loboda all sorts already
повторных показав этой Лободы всякой уже
I don't have enough for anything if I'm out of here
ни на что не хватает если меня отсюда
I'll get fired, I don't know what to do, I just don't
уволят я не знаю что делать я просто не
I know what to do, everything, everything, Valera, everything is fine
знаю что делать всё всё Валер всё хорошо
Calm down Look at
Успокойтесь Посмотрите на
write to me calmly as you did not then
меня пишите спокойно как тогда не
Be nervous and history will be sure
нервничайте и история сложится уверенна
the line about the parallel universe will be
линия про параллельную вселенную будет
it's written perfectly. Why are you so sure?
прописана идеально Да почему ты уверена
Well, you can't fail, can you?
ну у вас же не может не получиться Вы же
Great Valery Kiselyov screenwriter
Великий Валерий Киселёв сценарист номер
one of his time, that's the one who created
один своего времени вот тот кто создал
cult
культовое
the work revealed to the world the cat coconut
произведение явил миру кота кокоса
and this is who else is this this is a toy from
и А это ещ Кто такой Это игрушка из
the first batch was never put on sale and
первой партии она так и нела в продажу и
They made me redo it a little
Меня заставили немного переделать
cartoon and remove this character
мультфильм и убрать этого героя
there were originally
изначально их было
two, that is, this rat should have been there too
двое то есть эта крыса тоже должна была
being in a cartoon is
быть в мультике это
mouse At first he was called the cat Coconut and
мышь Сначала он назывался кот Кокос и
mouse
мыш
hashish again cat coconut and mouse
гашиш ещё раз кот Кокос и мыш
hashish a
гашиш а
that is, Coconut is still not
то есть Кокос - это всё-таки не
nut It turns out that no, well, understand, I was
орех Получается что нет ну пойми я был
young
молод
Valera, your fantasy is a whole
Валер под вашей фантазией целое
the generation has grown up you know now
поколение выросло Вы в курсе теперь вон
TV channels are run by, for example, of course
телеканалами руководят например Конечно
I will improve, really, I will improve, I will improve
я исправлюсь правда я я я исправлюсь
our new project I'm all
нашим новым проектом Я всё
I won't give up, just take a breath
Да уж не сдам Вот только вдохнуть
viewers hope for the series Bloody [ __ ]
зрителей надежду сериалом кровавые [__]
it's unlikely to work in a pit
в яме вряд ли удастся
Although there are worse names, for example, cat
Хотя бывает название похуже например кот
Coconut and mouse
Кокос и мыш
hashish understand Herman not everything is allowed
гашиш пойми Герман не всё можно
justify with love the pain that is caused
оправдать любовью боль которую причиняет
I love our vicious
мне наша порочная
passion cannot be justified by anything
страсть оправдать ничем невозможно погр
The Supreme Court can be justified
ВС можно оправдать
the love that ours gives me
любовю которую причиняет мне наша
vicious passion to justify by nothing
порочная страсть оправдать ничем
impossible to understand Herman not everything is possible
невозможно пойми Герман не всё можно
justify with love the pain that is caused
оправдать любовью боль которую причиняет
I need to justify our vicious passion
мне наша порочная страсть оправдать
nothing
ничем
impossible to understand
невозможно пойми
Herman, not everything can be justified.
Герман не всё можно оправдать
love the pain that ours causes us
любовью боль которую причиняет нам наша
vicious
порочная
passion to justify with nothing
страсть оправдать ничем
[music]
[музыка]
I didn't find it I
не я нашл Я
found what is Glasha Glasha I found
нашл чего такое Глаша Глаша я нашёл
I am the second actress
вторую актрису я
Masha How long did it take to turn off what?
Маша Сколько время вырубила что
li number
ли номер
Why las
Почему лас
I got up, so his viewer will get up too
У меня встал значит встанет его зритель
I am the Voice of the People. Who gives you such crap?
Я же Глас народа Кто вам такую херню
said our shareholder
сказал наш акционер
And then Yes, everything is correct 23
А тогда Да всё правильно 23
number
номер
[music]
[музыка]
23 Vladik Vladik Listen to me there
23 Владик Владик Слушай у меня там
I have one girlfriend, well, she's been an actress for a long time now
подружка одна есть Ну актриса уже давно
out of work well I'll think about it Maybe we should get a series
без работы ну я подумаю Может нам сериал
let's invite Isolde for the role why are we Isolde
позовём на роль Изольда зачем мы Изольда
Found today already how found Well so who
Нашли уже сегодня как нашли Ну так кто
Well, what's the difference?
Ну какая разница
m Vladik, well, show me please
м Владик ну покажи мне пожалуйста
Please
Пожалуйста
[music]
[музыка]
show understand
покажи пойми
Herman, not everything can be justified.
Герман не всё можно оправдать
love the pain that it causes us
любовью боль которую причиняет нам на её
you can't take it, you see how bad it is
нельзя брать поч видишь как она плохо
plays
играет
she will destroy our entire project like me
она уничтожит весь наш проект как я
In general, I can work with her better than possible
вообще смогу с ней работать луше возм
my friend
мою подругу
why because my scary And this
зачем потому что моя страшная А это
beautiful And what if she is more beautiful than me?
красивая А если она будет красивее меня
And if the audience loves her more
А если а если зрители её полюбят больше
than me And how will I even be against her background
чем меня А как я вообще на её фоне буду
look And if her role is called at all
смотреться А если её роль завут вообще
the best as an axis in the ass And if a
самая лучшая как ось в жопе А если а
if e zamiru better than me And if a
если е замиру лучше чем меня А если а
if the best job on earth
если лучшая работа на Земле
Here
Вот
she is golden
она золотая
I got the tax at 22 for the best plot.
Такса я получил её в 22 за лучший сюжет
O
о
animals My first film stub and
животных Мой первый фильм огрызок и
success immediately and recognition immediately and immediately
сразу успех и сразу признание и сразу
gold prize
приз золотой
pineapple When I was in yours
ананас Когда я был в твоём
at the age I already held this in
возрасте Я уже держал вот что в
in the hands of a silver ladle Yes, I wanted everything
руках Серебряный ковш Да я всё хотел
ask why everything is gold and the ladle
спросить а почему все золотые а ковш
Silver because the ladle is golden
Серебряный а потому что золотой ковш
You should have received such prizes
должен был получить ты такие призы кому
it didn't hit
попало не
they are distributing and you
раздают а ты
Well
Ну что
look what you are doing to me
ты посмотри что ты мне
brought bloody [ __ ] in the pit dad well you
принёс кровавые [__] в яме пап ну ты же
he himself said that it was necessary to remove it because
сам сказал что нужно снимать потому что
money is needed Yes, but it is needed more than once
нужны деньги Да но они нужны не один раз
A
а
constantly and having removed this
постоянно а сняв вот это
here you will put a black one on yourself
вот ты поставишь на себе чёрную
mark and cried my credit Kruzak
метку и плакал мой кредитный Крузак
dad
папа
Dad Well tell me do you think it's possible somehow
Папа Ну скажи ты думаешь как-то можно
fix it at all because they
вообще это исправить потому что они
refuse to redo anything and
отказываются что-либо переделывать Да и
I don't care, any [ __ ] can be saved
плевать на это спасти можно любое [__]
the old proven way you need
старым проверенным способом вам нужна
Star star star no money big
Звезда звезда звезда денег нет большая
star The bigger the better there is no money
звезда Чем больше тем лучше денег нет
We definitely need it
Точно нам нужна
big
большая
serious
серьёзная
star
звезда
Smoktunovsky on such artists what
смоктуновского на таких артистов какой
Zhenya Mironov he earns in a day
Женя Миронов он в день зарабатывает
more than you in a year Wait Katya [ __ ] Yes
больше чем вы в год Подожди Катя бляд Да
you're kidding me I'm Masha Okay, there's Sasha
вы издеваетесь Я Маша Ну ладно там Саша
Dasha Glasha at least sounds like Well, what the hell
Даша Глаша хоть созвучно Ну каким хером
I am Katya Vla
Я Катя вла
then find us a big serious star
то Найди нам Большую серьёзную звезду
Marina Yes
Марина Да
brighter great Oh
поярче здорово Ой
[music]
[музыка]
great I didn't get to see you
здорово Я же тебя так и не успел за
work thank for wedding
работу поблагодарить за свадьбу
Lately he hasn't even paid much at all
последнее время вообще мало платит даже
to film a funeral but something didn't work out
похороны снимать но чтото не пошло пере
Nolu is somehow worse In general
нолу как-то е хуже В общем
I'm having a great time here Believe me I'm here
спа здесь ься по полной Поверь мне я вот
what question did i read the script for
какому вопросу я прочитал сценарий
cool tell me
крутой скажи
The dacha lacks bloody action from the sop
даче не хватает кровавого экшена от соп
science fiction about crime does not speak
фантастика про криминал говорит не
show I think the script is necessary
показывают Я думаю сценарий надо
rewrite
переписать
[music]
[музыка]
beradi years of weddings filming and script
беради лет свадьб снима те и сценария
rewrite Well, get the [ __ ] out of here with my
переписать Ну дал нахуй отсюда с моей
kitchen I'm fired
кухни я уволен
no cool Vladimir Lvovich I'm sorry
нет охл Владимир Львович Вы извините что
I'm calling directly, your Agent just said
я звоню напрямую просто ваш Агент сказал
I thought you were busy until 2020
что вы заняты до 2020 года я подумала
what's wrong Oh great
что не так Ой здорово
ok yes thanks That's all
ясно да спасибо Всего
good hello you are agent alexander
доброго Здравствуйте вы агент Александра
Petrova Go to hell, go to hell yourself, [ __ ]
Петрова Иди нахуй сама пошла нахуй [__]
stupid
тупая
Hello, you are Evgeny Stychkin's agent.
Здравствуйте вы агент Евгения стычкина
Yes Vladislav Maybe I'd better spend some time on
Да Владислав Может лучше я проведу про у
I still have a wealth of experience with large
меня вс-таки богатый опыт с большими
I didn't see any artists there Igor, we are on
артистами я там не видел Игор нам на
Titi stopped by the gas station once and
заправку один разн Тити заезжал И на
what gas station Yes to my gas station Well I
какую заправку Да на мою заправку Ну я
I own a gas station, you stopped by once
владею заправкой ти заезжал один раз мне
there the gas station attendants told everything Don't worry
там заправщики рассказали Всё Не парь
wait here now
сечас жди здесь
there stychkin Well of course Masha said that
там стычкин Ну конечно Маша сказала что
The real Stychkin is sitting here like this, holding water
настоящий стычкин сидит тут так водичку
drinks Oh, [ __ ], Vladislav, don't calm down
пьёт [__] Владислав не Успокойтесь с
actors the simpler the better the main thing
актёрами чем проще тем лучше главное
Let's show who's in charge here right away
сразу показать Кто здесь главный давайте
in 5 minutes you will have yours
через 5 минут будет у вас ваш этот
Stychkin Gos No
стычкин гос Не
worry Zhenya
волнуйся Жень
hi hi have we met? Well, for sure
привет Привет а мы знакомы Ну наверняка
we crossed paths somewhere and heard about me
где-то пересекались Ну и слышал обо мне
Igor Zhmykh
Игорь жмых
sit down
садись
so did you manage to read anything? no
так удалось почитать что-нибудь нет
Forgive me, I'm only an Agent today.
Простите я меня сегодня только Агент
I just pulled here in the next
дёрнул Я просто здесь в соседнем
I was in the pavilion so I dropped in
павильоне был поэтому заскочил к
Unfortunately, it's a pity. Well, look, it's okay.
сожалению очень жаль Ну ничего смотри
your hero is like a bandit and at the same time
твой герой он как бы бандос и в то же
time as
время как
would you understand the cop at the same time
бы мент одновременно понимаешь
and does it happen like that of course not only
а так разве бывает конечно же не только
so and
так и
It happens
бывает
Okay, well, and who should I do? Well, I
Окей Ну хорошо и и кого мне делать Ну я
and a policeman or a bandit is very good
и милиционера или бандита очень хороший
question
вопрос
at the same time, a piece of Come on is highlighted there
одновременно там выделен кусочек Давай
his
его
let's try Turn on the camera
попробуем Включай камеру
ready Oh yeah yeah now let's try
готов О да да сейчас Давай попробуем
Yes
Угу
And
и
started
начали
It's not just about serving while protecting with your chest
Да не просто служить защищая грудью
Law and order on these dirty streets and
Закон и порядок на этих грязных улицах и
and at the same time know that your own father
при этом знать что твой собственный отец
once headed the Criminal
когда-то возглавлял Преступный
syndicate I am German Ushakov
синдикат я Герман Ушаков
[music]
[музыка]
I give it to you
даю тебе
Violeta word
Виолета слово
officer that I can protect you from
офицера что я смогу защитить тебя от
all the evil that is in this city
всего зла которое есть в этом городе
and our bodies will merge in unison of passion A
и наши тела сольются в унисон страсти А
so it's like a comedy
так это типа комедия
Yes Zhen
Да Жень
look, you seem like a normal guy A
смотри ты вот вроде нормальный парень А
here's the camera, you're starting something too
вот камера ты тоже начинаешь что-то
There is no need to include this Let's do it
такое включать не надо это Давай сделаем
another take and give me more
ещё дубль и дай мне больше
a simpler person with more irony text
человека попроще с текстом больше Иронии
The oil is burning. Turn on the machine.
масло пригорает Маш включай
Yeah, yeah.
Угу да
Uh-huh Okay so
Угу Окей так
and they started Yes no
и начали Да не
just not just serve defending with your chest
просто не просто служить защищая грудью
law
закон
on these dirty streets and still know
на этих грязных улицах и при этом знать
that your own father once
что твой собственный отец когда-то
headed the Crime
возглавлял Преступный
syndicate I am German
синдикат я Герман
Ushakov and I give you
Ушаков и я даю тебе
Violeta, the officer's word that I can save
Виолета слово офицера что я смогу спасти
you from all the evil that is in this
тебя от всего зла которое есть в этом
in the city of Nu
городе Ну
and our bodies will merge in unison of passion
и наши тела сольются в унисон страсти
So
Так
ok let's do it again but without
ладно Давай сделаем ещё раз только без
these jewish things
этих еврейских штучка
and Daro has it, I'll give it a good rating
а а у Даро у него Хорошо поставлю
I can play shorties without Dubrov
коротышки этого могу без Дубров играть
What to do now? We don't have a star.
Что теперь делать У нас нет звезды что
do you find someone else
делать Ты нашла кого-нибудь ещ ктоу
agreed none of ours
согласился из наших нет
But there is one of
Но есть один из
Hollywood
Голливуда
[music]
[музыка]
oh [ __ ] is this Game of Thrones He
вот [__] Это что Игра престолов Он
played in the game
играл в игре
thrones kit harington you did it
престолов Кит хэрингтон тебе удалось
persuade Keith Herrington to film with us
уговорить у нас сняться кита херингтона
Not
не
the frame will be in full view now
совсем вот сейчас будет кадр в полный
height is here, here he is our actor Well, this is it
рост вот во вот он наш актёр Ну это же
he didn't, he duplicated it when he was ass
он же нет он его дублировал когда жопу
We had to show our Russian guy
нужно было показывать наш русский парень
lives here and there At first there was a scourge
живёт то тут то там Сначала был бич боем
in Miami and now got a job in film
в Майами а теперь устроился в кино
ass double for famous actors a
дублёром жоп известных актёров а
talking
говорящая
ass So you're suggesting that I take it
срака То есть ты предлагаешь мне взять
for the main role of the ass double
на главную роль дублёра жоп
Well
Ну что
I can't make such a decision myself.
сам я не могу принять такое решение Я
I'm afraid when I say that we have a star
боюсь когда я скажу что у нас звезда
there will be a stunt double Boss will tell me this
будет дублёр жоп Босс мне скажет это
Brilliant Vlad, you got us a star of the Game
Гениально Влад ты достал нам звезду Игры
of Thrones Yes, there is an opinion that the episodes with
престолов Да есть мнение что эпизоды с
it won't be very easy for him with text
текстом ему не очень легко будут
give in Are you crazy take it no
даваться Ты что с ума сошёл бери не
think, otherwise they'll tear him apart now
думай а то его сейчас разорвут как
they only find out that he is ready to act in
только узнают что он готов сниматься за
funny money by Hollywood standards
смешные по голливудским меркам деньги
it's not that little I want to tell you but
это не так уж и мало хочу вам сказать но
I'm thinking maybe we can use this money
я вот думаю может быть нам на эти деньги
remove the tire cut as the NOC chicken advises me
снять крое шин как советует мне куре НОК
this is my operator that Vlad honestly
это оператор мой что Влад честное слово
Don't you see any prospects?
ты что не видишь перспектив что ли ты
imagine his face on the picture Yes, that's it
представь его лицо на постр Да в том-то
the whole point is that no one saw his face
всё и дело что его лица никто не видел
he's mostly there in Hollywood movies
он в голливудских фильмах в основном там
this is with his back, so put him with his back
это ж спиной и значит поставь его спиной
this is even bolder oh oh everything man came Yes
это ещё смелее о о всё человек пришёл Да
that's it Get out of here Scat scat home
всё Пошёл отсюда Брысь брысь домой
Get lost!
Брысь ты
who is healthy
кто Здоров
healthy And who is this, not your herd?
здоров А это кто у тебя а не пася
my CEO he will snc you yes
гендиректор мой он тебя снц да
slightly 15 years at Gazprom 15 in the holding
слегка 15 лет в Газпроме 15 в холдинге
almost on
почти на
gas stations In short, okay, [ __ ] it, forget about it
заправки Короче ладно хуй с ним забудь
there is a concept one such new for you
есть концепт один такой для тебя новая
Victory T3 can be beautifully removed Very T
Победа Т3 можно красиво Очень снять Т
all your old feathers are ready
все старые пер твои готов
[music]
[музыка]
ready blind me fortune teller
готов слепая меня гадалка
How come I didn't think of this myself
как я сам не додумался до
this
этого
Vla Anya
Вла Аня
Hello, I'm Sasha, take Vladislav
Здравствуйте я Саша водите Владислава
Viktorovich's driver
Викторовича водитель
Yes, Vladislav Viktorovich, and I am Anna's wife.
Да Владислава Викторовича А я Анна жена
ex
бывшая
his Vladislav Viktorovich what
его Владислава Викторовича что
Where does it all come from? I am the same
происходит Откуда всё ято Я же
I told you Anya called that I now
рассказывал тебе звонил Аня что я теперь
Director of the General Directorate of the TV channel You
директор генеральной телеканала Ты
Are you kidding me? I thought you were drunk. No.
издеваешься Я думала ты нажрался нет
Vlad I'm so glad to see you, really. A
Влад что я так рада тебя видеть правда А
you know, I was just shy
знаешь я я просто стеснялась
Yes, I was just embarrassed about the meeting, I thought
Да я просто стеснялась встречи я думала
why are you offended at me? I am you, me
что ты на меня обиделся Я это же ты меня
at the first opportunity I sent and
при первом удом случае посылала и
called mayor lozer vilya what is this
называла мэром лозер Виля что это же
joke yeah I always knew that you were just
шутка да Я же всегда знала что ты всего
you will achieve it
добьёшься
Yes, I knew that he would achieve everything, yes
Да вот я знала что он всего достигнет да
Well, tell me. Well, how can you do anything?
Ну рассказывай Ну как ты что может
let's go have lunch and dinner Vladislav
поехали пообедаем поужинаем Владислав
Viktorovich, urgently needed in 15 minutes
Викторович через 15 минут срочно надо
be on the channel just wrote And what
быть на канале только что написали А что
You
ты
keep quiet tomorrow I'll call Anya for now ok Well
молчишь завтра наберу Ань пока хорошо Ну
maybe today I won't turn it off
может сегодня я не буду отключать
phone today so call Well when
телефон сегодня так что звони Ну когда
you
тебе
it's convenient you're standing here let's go we'll be late well
удобно са стоишь поехали опоздаем же ну
No, we don't need to go anywhere.
да не надо нам никуда я
lied why did you that Anya has been with me for 2 years
наврал Зачем ты что Анька со мной 2 года
You didn't talk normally, did you? Yes, you
нормально не разговаривала ты что Да вы
Don't you see that she doesn't give a damn about you
не видите что е плевать на вас она
I saw that there was an increase and immediately decided
увидела что прибавка тут же решила
back turmoil And you lead Yes of course
обратно смута А вы и ведёте Да конечно
think about who you are now you can
подумайте о том кто Вы теперь вы можете
get any woman why do you need her
получить любую женщину Зачем она вам
needed
нужна
I know School love at the desk together
знаю Школьная любов за партой вместе
Side has probably been in school for about 10 years now
Сиде школу наверняка уже лет 10 как
they demolished it and built a shopping center and that's it
снесли и построили торговый центр и все
these love stories are on the same desk
эти любовные истории за одной партой
you need to be buried in the same pit
надо похоронить в том же котловане ты
You know all this and I teach courses
всё это знаешь а я преподаю на курсах
pickup do you know what this is am I an idiot
пикап знаете что это такое Я что [__]
in your opinion, of course the machine teaches
по-твоему что ли Конечно машина учишь
drive
водить
pickup only What do women have to do with it
пикап только Причём здесь бабы
[music]
[музыка]
the first day of shooting is always like this
первый съёмочный день всегда так
excites Yes I already x
возбуждает Да я уже х
take a picture
сним
[music]
[музыка]
understood please
понял пожалуйста
How sweetly everyone signed for me
Как мило все расписались мне на
plate Yes, this is not an old movie for you
тарелочке Да это не вам старая киношная
tradition is that the whole group signs
традиция вся группа расписывается на
the plates then break it And after
тарелочки потом её разбивают А после
the filming must be put together piece by piece
съёмки должны собрать по кусочкам
sign back and spit in
обратно распишитесь а плевок в
eternity
вечность
sign Igor
распишитесь Игор
please I want to break but according to tradition
прошу Я хочу разбить но по традиции
the director breaks it Well, here's to tradition
разбивает режиссёр Ну вот по традиции
[ __ ] And they'll film everything we have
[__] И снимают у нас всё будет
in a new way comrade We are filming a hit together
по-новому товарище Мы с вами снимаем хит
That's why
поэтому
must break
разбивать должен
I Well give it Give it Let it
я Ну дайте Дайте Пусть
they'll break it Well, as they say, here we go
разобьют Ну как говорится Понеслась
[ __ ] on bumps
[__] по кочкам
oh yeah, you should have hit the tripod, not the camera
а да об штатив надо было не об камеру же
I I didn't know I thought like a bottle about
я Я не знал я думал как бутылку об
the ship looks like
корабль это похоже на
ship
корабль
awesome
заебись
take it off he lives then the waterfall is not needed
снимайте он живёт то водопада не нужна
to him
ему
fence see next
ограда смотрите в следующей
sweat series
серии пот
wisely all friends want
мудро все друзья хотят
they cry from idleness like goats
веселья они плакать от безделья как коз
A cheerful cat, everyone knows that, he will get rid of
Весёлый кот это знают все он избавит от
the worries of adults and children will come to you
забот взрослых и детей го к тебе придёт
Just call him and you will dance with him.
Только позови ты будешь танцевать с ним
from the night
с ночи
[music]
[музыка]
kings earlier in
цари ранее в
series do you want us to start
сериале ты хочешь чтобы мы начали
show something that no one will watch
показывать то что никто смотреть не
the shares will become cheaper and we will buy them up
будет акции подешевеют и мы их скупим
We need a new CEO in full
полностью Нам нужен новый генеральный
director my column diesel to full
директор моя колонка дизель до полного
A person capable of creating such a product
Человек способный создать такой продукт
which will be hated by all viewers
который будут ненавидеть Все зрители
Do any [ __ ] and don't This is just awful I
Твори любую херню а не Это просто ужас Я
I don't understand at all what I'm doing here
вообще не понимаю что я тут делаю не
call here more
звони сюда больше
[ __ ] I want a series there is an operator no
[__] Я хочу сериал есть оператор не
Enough bloody action Dream Team
хватает кровавого экшена команда Dream
Team I Masha Igor Zhmykh Veliky Valery
Team я Маша Игорь жмых Великий Валерий
Kiselyov It's time to start
Киселёв Пора начинать
casting vicious passion And what did they take
кастинг порочная страсть А что взяли что
the sample was good you need a star
проба была хорошая вам нужна Звезда
there is no money, the star will be a stunt double
денег нет звезда будет дублёр жоп
The [ __ ] went wild
Понеслась [__] по
[music]
[музыка]
bumps behind every great story
кочкам за каждой грандиозной историей
success is worth the personality What a huge
успеха стоит личность Какое огромное
number of people eating Ray Kroc hamburgers
количество людей ело гамбургеры Рей Крок
turned McDonald's Corporation How much
превратил Макдональдс Корпорацию Сколько
inhabitants of our planet are carried in pockets
жителей нашей планеты носят в карманах
Steve Jobs iPhones
Айфоны Стив Джобс
made Apple a brand of success How many did not
сделал Apple брендом успеха Как много не
there would be both for each of them
было бы и тех и других для каждого из
they will find a bullet from the very
них найдётся пуля из самого
the most widespread machine gun in the world Mikhail
распространённого в мире автомата Михаил
Twitch Kalashnikov Thank you for this about
Твич Калашников Спасибо тебе за это об
one of these success stories we and
одной из таких историй успеха мы и
let's talk today when this person
поговорим сегодня когда этот человек
the little man was born in a small Khrushchev-era building
человечище родился в маленькой хрущевке
in the South no one could know what he was
в Южном туши никто не мог знать что ему
destined to turn over
суждено перевернуть
television
телевизионную
industry his Odnoklassniki Pina shi
индустрию его Одноклассники Пина вшие
his on
его на
changes and couldn't imagine that they were kicking
переменах и не могли подумать что пинают
the future of russian television his wife
будущее российского телевидения его жена
who left him because he was all his own
бросившая его потому что он всё своё
I didn't devote my free time to work
свободное время отдавал работе не
understood that she was abandoning the embodied
понимала что бросает воплощён ную
man revolutionized his approach to creation
человеке революцию его подход к созданию
movies and TV series struck me that we
кино и сериалов поразил меня что мы с
colleagues unanimously
коллегами единогласным
the decision was entrusted to him
решением доверили ему
manage a TV channel
управлять телеканалом
tsv and its new flagship product
тсв и его новым флагманским продуктом
series bloody [ __ ] in the pit Meet
сериалом кровавые [__] в яме Встречайте
Vladislav
Владислав
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
Polyakov la Submit a project to his
Поляков ла Представь проект чтобы его
saw in all its glory so that
увидели во всей красе чтобы
and competitors
ж а конкуренты
will be trembling
дрожа будет
Hold on, you don't seem interested.
Держись вроде заинтересована ты не
you know Vlad is a standard [ __ ] Believe me
знаешь Влада это эталонный [__] Поверь
to me
мне
Hello, I'm Vlad.
Здравствуйте В общем я Влад
[music]
[музыка]
bloody women with reduced social status
кровавые женщины с пониженной социальной
responsibility in
ответственностью в
pit
яме
here is the script
вот сценарий
written by Valery Kiselev but He is widely
написал Валерий Киселёв но Он широко
known for
известен благодаря
cartoon cat Coconut and his friends Well
мультфильму кот Кокос и его друзья Ну
I guess you all remember how bikes worked
наверно наверняка все помните какс велы
the cat knows this, he will get rid of the scenario
кот это знают все он избавит от сценарий
good director very good cameraman
хороший режиссёр очень хороший оператор
I have a good wedding
хороший у меня свадьбу
Vlad filmed a funny performance Well,
снимал Влад смешное выступление Ну а
Seriously, who is the cameraman and what did he film?
если серьёзно кто оператор и что Снимал
and who is the director and what was filmed so seriously
и кто режиссёр и что снимал так серьёзно
renok Vasily Kurey here you are very good
ренок Василий курей вот ва очень хороший
The cameraman filmed the wedding perfectly They thought
оператор снял свадьбу отлично Они думали
is he joking or something? Well of course now
что он шутит что ли Ну конечно сейчас до
the director will start to get it very much
них начнёт доходить режиссёр очень
Igor is also a good one, he took off the cake
хороший тоже вот Игор жмых снял
short film title title
короткометражку название название
name I don't remember the name
название Название не помню
Name
название
Yes, we understood it all Comedy No no
Да мы так поняли это всё Комедия Не нет
Why not comedy No it is
Почему нет не комедия Нет это это
the melodrama is very serious there
мелодрама очень серьёзная там такая
love story for three Well, not a threesome
история любви на троих Ну не тройничок в
I mean, where are they all three of them there?
смысле где они там шпиля все втроём с
each other Well, all three are each other
друг другом Ну как бы все трое друг
they love each other but they spit in pairs Here But But
друга любят но шпиля по двое Вот Но но
without gayness there are two girls and without
без гейства там есть две девочки и без
lesbianism And as the new director of the channel
лесбиянства А как новый директор канала
what else are you preparing for the viewers on
что ещё Вы готовите для зрителей на
new
новый
season honestly yes honestly honestly
сезон честно Да честно честно
Come on, we spent all the money on
Давай Ничего мы все деньги пустили на
[ __ ] well I mean not on [ __ ] which
шлюх ну в смысле не на шлюх который
he's [ __ ] TV [ __ ] and not those
долбится а телевизионных шлюх и не тех
which are on the screen there Hello there in
которые на экране там Здравствуйте там в
on air news and on ours
эфире новости а на на наших
TV [ __ ] Series Well you get it and
телевизионных шлюх сериал Ну вы поняли и
what's on the channel? There won't be anything new
что же на канале Ничего нового не будет
besides this, how are you going to
кроме этого А как же вы собираетесь
build an etheric grid what to build What
строить эфирную сетку что строить Какую
grid
сетку
and what will you show? And we will. Well.
а показывать Что будете А мы будем Ну
I was told here that they will be possible
мне сказали тут что их можно будет
so we will repeat them
повторять поэтому их будем
show Let's let the [ __ ] go
показывать Пустим шлюх по
[laughter]
[смех]
circle Andrey Andryush Andryush look look
кругу Андрей Андрюш Андрюш смотри смотри
on the stock price Yes Yes I told you the market
на курс акции Да Да Я же говорил рынок
hears us and
слышит нас и
reacts awesome
реагирует обалденная
presentation What is what
презентация Что такое что
so the [ __ ] took off
сак взлетели ёпты
[music]
[музыка]
Don Oleg
Дон Олег
Hello, thank God, we have already arrived.
Здравствуйте слава Богу прилетели мы уже
thought the plane was delayed I Masha I
думали самолёт задержался я Маша я
communicated with you your
общалась с вами вашим
agent, and you speak Russian as best you can
агентом а вы по-русски как умеете
a slight accent has appeared over the years in the USA
появился небольшой акцент за года в USA
like us
как у нас
they say but I will try to remove it class
говорят но я постараюсь его убрать класс
We sat you down right after your shift, we took you off
Мы вас сразу после смены засели мы сняли
you a wonderful apartment and now
вам прекрасную квартиру а сейчас
let's go please call you with s I would
пойдёмте пожалуйста нари вас с с Я бы
I wanted to discuss the role now I'm busy they're there
хотел обсудить роль сейчас занят они там
rehearsing maybe I can somehow
репетируют может я как-то могу
help
помочь
Oh my character who
Ой мой персонаж кто
he he
он Он
man What is his
человек В чём его
conflict what does he want there are two girls he
конфликт что он хочет Там две девушки он
he loves them both, what's so difficult about it?
их обеих любит че особо сложного
please go Okay What's his name?
пожалуйста пойдёте Окей А как его
name is Haven't you read the script?
зовут Вы что не читали сценарий
Yes
Да
Class
класс
And
и
started Isolde I'm sure that you tell me
начали Изольда я уверена что ты мне
you're lying my friend saw you with herman
лжёшь моя подруга видела вас с германом
in the cafe and your communication did not look
в кафе и ваше общение не выглядело
friendly Violetta since when is yours
дружеским Виолетта с каких пор твоя
a friend can identify people by
подруга может определять людей по
communication and in general who is she she is a psychologist with
общению и вообще кто она она психолог с
with three diplomas and she can somehow
тремя дипломами и она уж как-то может
understand what is happening between people even
понять что происходит между людьми даже
from a distance of 70
с расстояния 70
mtro and it is from this distance that she
мтро а именно с такого расстояния она
I saw you in
видела вас в
cafe are you accusing me of something
кафе ты в чём-то обвиняешь меня
[ __ ] calm down I just want
мерзавка успокойся Я просто хочу
dot all the i's
расставить все точки над
and it's not enough that all the dots are needed
и ещё не хватало чтобы все точки надо
I arrange it with me
мной расставляю
some kind of profursetka
какая-то профурсетка
stop I'm sorry
стоп Простите
Sorry
простите
sorry sorry so so so so so
простите простите так так так так так
so so so
так так так
so Arina why did you get lost again
так Арина Почему ты опять сбилась в
end of the scene Yes with the rhythm Well to be honest
конце сцены Да с ритма Ну если честно
I'm just a little confused by the word
меня просто немножко смущает слово
profursetka Yes why Well I'm not a little
профурсетка Да почему Ну я я немножко не
I understand what it means secondly
понимаю что оно значит во-вторых
I'm a little ashamed because I'm afraid that
немножко Стыдно потому что я боюсь что
you will watch My Grandma is Old
ты будет смотреть Моя бабушка старенькая
your grandma will watch Baby You
бабушка у тебя будет смотреть Беби Ты
I saw what this series is called, I mean
видела как этот сериал называется мне же
they said that this is a working title yes
сказали что это рабочее название да
then the word [ __ ] will be replaced by More
потом слово [__] заменит на Более
decent Yeah, [ __ ], so stop the light
прилично Угу [__] так свет перестань
please girls understand me in this
пожалуйста девочки поймите мне в этой
the scene simply needs it
сцене необходим просто необходим
conflict you understand so that everything sparks
конфликт понимаете чтобы всё искри
Tell me, do you have any theatrical experience?
скажите у вас есть театральный опыт Я
in general I am a theater actress you are a [ __ ]
вообще я Театральная актриса [__] ты с
with your ears
ушами Ты
what No I don't understand what's going on
чего Нет я не понимаю что происходит
Sveta, I ask you to go for 10 minutes.
Света я тебя прошу на 10 минут Пойди
take a rest MRKO I ask you that I
отдохни МРКО я тебя прошу что я
did a second second come on come on
сделала секунду секунду Давай давай
let's talk Arinochka quieter quieter quieter quieter
поговорим Ариночка тише тише тише тише
quiet, well she's just jealous, it's simple
тише ну она же просто ревнует это Просто
actor's jealousy You understand, right?
актёрская ревность Ты же понимаешь да
everything everything everything everything tell me what you are in
всё всё всё всё расскажи В каком ты
worked in the theater that played penzinsky
театре работала что играла пензин ский
tyus snowy
тюс Снежная
queen all all all ti ti Well maybe
королева всё всё всё ти ти Ну а может
Anything classic was that classic
что-нибудь из классики было это классика
I almost have a dramatic dialogue with Kai and
почти у меня там драма диалог с каем и
song I sing well you see clever clever
песенка Я пою ну видишь умница умница
She's a smart girl if she played the Snow Queen
умница если Снежную королеву сыграла
then everything you can do thanks and I have
значит всё Сможешь спасибо А у меня к
please Yes Irina
вам просьба Да Ириночка
What Don't hold me by the ass
Какая Не держите меня за жопу
Please
пожалуйста
I'm sorry somehow
прости как-то само
eh, we're getting ready
э готовимся
getting ready Vladislav and Masha the secretary
готовимся Владислав та Маша секретарша
who sits by the door and now works
который сидит у двери а теперь работат
on the site for three Masha well I know what
на площадке за троих Маш ну я знаю что
You tell me about this every time
ты мне каждый раз об этом говоришь на
You look like an idiot
идиота похож что
li Hello I think
ли Алло Я думаю
AKM doesn't matter Come to us quickly without
АКМ неважно Приезжайте скорее к нам без
you are hard And why should I go to you and me
вас тяжело А зачем я к вам поеду мне и
It's nice here It's finally quiet
здесь хорошо Тихо стало наконец-то
now Valery will come, we will have a story
сейчас н Валерка придёт будем сюжет
I discuss new episodes myself in the evening
новых серий обсуждать он вечером я сама
start
нача
Ute ut microbe at
Уте ут микроб при
He needs a little pathos to be with him
Он слегка пафосе нужно чтобы с ним
Boss said They like it like that
поговорил Босс Они это любят так а
the second actress who is Violeta in life
вторая актриса которая Виолета в жизни
Sveta pounced on the one that Isolde was in
света набросилась на ту что Изольда в
Arina's life needs to be calmed down Svetka A
жизни Арина её надо успокоить Светку А
What does this have to do with me?
я-то тут причём
Well, well, you understand. No, I dont understand you there.
Ну ну вы понимаете Нет не понимаю вы там
you film it yourself
сами снимаете сами
calm down it says light and sucks
успокаивайтесь написано света и сосёт
Now
сейчас
I'll come What the hell oh Vladik hi This is
приеду Какого хрена ой Владик привет Это
you are the light what is going on with us and what
ты свет что у нас происходит А что
Why did you quarrel with another?
происходит Зачем ты поссорилась с другой
actress Explain to me she annoys me
актрисой Объясни мне она меня бесить
let's start firing I won't fire anyone
начала давай уволим Да не буду я никого
I haven't even fired Svet yet
увольнять Свет я даже с ней ещё не
I met you please I really like you
познакомился пожалуйста Я тебя очень
please behave normally what can i do
прошу Веди себя нормально че я могу
get angry in the end you are like that
разозлиться в конце концов ты такой
nervous Well of course I'm nervous Well because
нервный Ну конечно я нервный Ну потому
that everyone calls me all the time this A
что мне все звонят меня постоянно это А
what do you have and I am for everything
что у вас и я же за всё
I answer
отвечаю
and you were standing here waiting the whole time Yeah, you
а ты всё время здесь стояла ждала Угу Вы
for a long time because I couldn't for a long time
долго потому что я долго не мог
end the conversation well done finished
закончить разговор ну закончили закончил
Excellent, you have a white one on your right trouser leg
Отлично у вас на право штанине белая
Oh you
Ах ты
Playpen, [ __ ], no need to use your hands
манеж бля Да не надо руками
thank you I ate Olivier and got infected or
спасибо С ел Оливье и попала зараза или
ryazhenka ryazhenka
ряженка ряженкой
Mash was drinking somehow, well, what's all there is
запивал как-то Маш ну что там все
the questions have been resolved
вопросы решили надо
shoot more No let's do it now
снимать ещё Нет давайте скорее сечас
now now
сечас сейчас
Oleg Sorry, I'll distract you, Vladislav has arrived
Олег Извините отвлеку Владислав приехал
with you
с вами
boss Sorry figure it out What
начальство Извините разберись Какое
boss why are you our star i am so
начальство зачем вы у нас звезда я так
formally Well, what are you to me big
формально Ну что вы для меня большая
It's an honor to work with such a pro
честь работать таким про как
howled prino what is this
выла прино что это
ice cream Ice cream was eaten apparently under the tile
мороженое Мороженое ел видимо под тайла
Masha Platov quickly and drop it Vladislav
Маша Платов быстро да бросьте Владислав
Viktorovich, what do you think I am?
Викторович вы что думаете я какая-то там
Hollywood
голливудская
Everything is a [ __ ]
Неженка все
yours And what is this with
свои А что это с
Mary probably got pregnant, toxicosis
Мэри залетела наверное токсикоз
Yeah, interesting ice cream.
Угу интересное мороженое
creamy
сливочная
uga creamy
уга сливочная
[laughter]
[смех]
I'm listening Oh, sorry, I must have made a mistake
слушаю А ой извините я наверное ошиблась
you need Vladislav Viktorovich now
вам Владислав Викторович нужен он сейчас
on the set and the phone while I have me
на съёмке а телефон Пока у меня я
Secretary Maria
секретарь Мария
and I'm Anya, we just agreed today
а я Аня просто мы договаривались сегодня
I can meet him at his place for dinner.
встретиться у него свободен ужин могу
you Record a meeting in a restaurant what
вам Записать встречу в ресторане какую
kitchen
кухню
prefer No guys understand I
предпочитаете Нет ребята понимаете Я
I feel it's not true You must first
чувствую неправду Ты сначала должен
see lips evaluate and then touch
увидеть губы оценить а потом уже трогать
rud you understand then it will be
руд понимаешь тогда это будет
stand there I didn't know you were married what
стои я и не знала что вы жената чего
I made an appointment for dinner with my wife today
назначила м сегодня с женой ужин в
Japanese restaurant with my wife with Anya you them
японском ресторане с женой с Аней вас их
several momun No we got divorced Sasha
несколько момун Нет мы развелись Сашка
the driver said she was a sly [ __ ]
водитель сказал что она коварная [__]
She kept sending me away and insulting me.
она всё время меня посылала оскорбляла А
now he only wants my money what do I need
сейчас хочет только мои бабки что мне
do
делать
now Well, I understand that you are now the king
теперь Ну я так понимаю Вы теперь король
situations Tell VS as it is Oh exactly I
ситуации Скажите ВС как есть О точно Я
I'll go and tell her straight away right now
сейчас пойду и пря в ли ей скажу так ра
Thea see
тея виде
I
Я
I also miss you very much
тоже я очень соскучилась
Well, how are you? Well, tell me more. How?
Ну как ты Ну рассказывай побольше Как
got on TV Well I took part
попал на телевидение Ну я принимал
bold decision and you
смелые решение А ты
yes oh yes yes you you can you are with me
да А ну да да ты ты можешь ты у меня
You are so brave. Big people noticed.
такой Ты смелый Большие люди заметили
me and now you are also a big person
меня и теперь тоже большой человек а ты
Which
как Ой
Vlad, I keep thinking, How stupid.
Влад я вот всё думаю Как же глупо
it turned out that we broke up Well, because of
получилось что мы расстались Ну из-за
some kind of nonsense the neighbor planted
какой-то там ерунды тея засадил сосед
Anya, yes, but also the Pizzeria Courier No, well
Ань ну да но и Курьер из пиццерии Нет ну
Daniyar just works as a courier. This is not
Данияр просто работает курьером Это не
the fact that I called pizza we didn't know each other
то что я вызвала пиццу мы не знали друг
friend it happened we met
друга это случилось Познакомились мы
through a mutual friend yes through a neighbor Well
через общего друга да Через соседа Ну
Vlad
Влад
Why are you remembering this now?
Зачем ты сейчас это вспоминаешь это же
mistakes of youth mistakes of youth to you
ошибки молодости ошибки молодости тебе
forty soon it was 2 years ago
сорокет скоро это было 2 года назад
how young is Anya
какой молодости Ань
Vlad is dear, but now it doesnt matter
Влад дорогой но ведь сейчас это не имеет
none
никакого
meanings now that we understand everything and
значения сейчас когда мы всё поняли и
we want to be together again that I don't have anything
снова хотим быть вместе что я ничего не
I understand, I don't want anything
понял я я ничего не хочу
[ __ ] how is this
[__] как это
happened Who is there Valera this is a chicken NOC
произошло Кто там Валера это куре НОК
What other NOC operator is this from yours?
Какой ещё курье НОК оператор с Вашего
series Open a serious conversation
сериала Откройте серьёзный разговор
[music]
[музыка]
u
ю
owls
свы
listen to us prophesy
вни нам пророчат
[music]
[музыка]
We bear the burden of trouble
беду мы на плечи
they put it on and now it's Valery's turn
взвалили и Ну а теперь дело Валер
trouble where
беда Где
for all the greatest work of all your life
на все величайший труд все твоей жизни
the dog's tail flies Kai T bloody [ __ ]
летит псу подхвост Кай Т кровавые [__]
in the pit series this is the manifesto of generations
в яме сериа это же манифест поколений
Valera, this is your manifesto, this is our manifesto.
Валер это твой манифест это наш манифест
and some geek is filming it
а его снимает какой-то гиковский
Dilettante Yes and Vlad with all my love
Дилетант Да и Влад при всей моей любви
grannies are zhmt Apparently he wants to saw them up nothing
бабки жмт Видимо хочет их распилить ниче
I don't understand, I see what the series lacks
не понимаю я вижу что сериалу не хватает
bloody action brutality so good
кровавого экшена жести такого хорошего
mat there is no money sometimes there is no money for this
мат денег нет иногда для этого деньги не
need need desire with noah
нужны нужно желание со ной
[music]
[музыка]
No, you are with me.
Нет ты со мной
yes you are gone time 330 we will all go
да вы поехавшие время 330 мы все пойдём
I don't give a damn about you baby
по пизде детка я нет насчёт вас не знаю
if we don't make this series a masterpiece
если мы не сделаем этот сериал шедевром
We won't be given a second chance Our daughter
нам не дадут второго шанса Наша дочка
listen, he's telling the truth. What are you talking about?
слушай нка он правду говорит Вы что
Are you drunk or something? No, Valeria is not at all.
пьяная что ли Нет Валерия вообще не
I knew you knew each other What difference does it make
знала что вы знакомы Какая разница что
you knew you wanted it for the rest of your life
ты знала ты хочешь до конца жизни
weddings to shoot What weddings don't scream
свадьбы снимать Какие свадьбы не ори
you mean so if i understood correctly you
ты значит так если я поняла правильно ты
are you offering us some kind of pirate
предлагаешь нам каким-то пиратским
a way to add parts to the series about
способом доснять в сериал куски про
which besides Nani
которые кроме Нани
Yes
Да
look, there is a scriptwriter, you organize it
смотри сценарист есть ты организует
actors I
актёров я
will drag away I will mount
утащит монтирую
I will find them only in the air to remove
я обнаружит их только в эфире убирать
will
будет
it's late how can I organize actors for you Well
поздно как я тебе актёров организую Ну
how much money will we chip in for something like this?
на какие шиши сами скинемся за такие
Only Masons will withdraw money Yes
деньги только масоны сниматься будут Да
We will be freemasons for Masha without prejudices. Well
мы Маше без предрассудков масоны буд Ну
it doesn't matter, masons I mean extras
это без разницы масоны В смысле массовка
this is a complete mess, they don't talk at all
это же конченая вообще не разговаривают
with difficulty
с трудом
Damn, I still have to spend money on movie blood
блин ещё на кровь киношную тратиться
we need to, but where can we get actors and money?
надо а где вот взять актёров и денег
simultaneously
одновременно
Oh, I have
О у меня
One of my rich friends has an idea
идея у одного моего богатого друга есть
the stupid daughter who wanted to be an actress
тупая дочь которая хотела стать актрисой
He once asked to introduce him to someone.
Он как-то попросил свести его с кем-то
from the world of cinema so here it is
из мира кино так вот
he paid half a million to have his daughter
он заплатил полмиллиона чтобы его дочь
starred in some TV series
снялась в каком-то сериале В
episode
эпизоде
Brilliant We need such idiots here
Гениально Нам нужны такие [__] Тут
straight up serious roles in the flagship
прямо серьёзные роли во флагманском
You can make a lot of money in the series
сериале кучу бабла можно заработать
Make a ton of money But the plan isn't really that
Заработать кучу бабла А план не то чтобы
unreal I mean characters like this
нереальный Я про таких персонажей
I heard, come on
слышала давай
You need money, well look at yours
Тебе нужны деньги ну посмотри на свою
I have a great [ __ ] apartment
сраную квартиру у меня отличная
the apartment is normal
квартира нормальная
apartment Sorry I'm in [ __ ] and I can't see Well
квартира Прости я в [__] и не вижу Ну
look at what the [ __ ] you have and
посмотри на то что у тебя есть сраное и
understand that it can become normal you
пойми что оно может стать нормальным ты
with us, okay, okay
с нами да ладно уж с
you Union of four We are three yes
вами Союз четырёх Нас трое да
the side of the thing is rigid
борт вешо жёстко
removed the Union
убрал Союз
three What happened to you?
трёх Что у вас случилось
yes horror slept with ex-wife what
да Ужас с бывшей женой переспал что
Why did I warn you? Well
зачем Я же вас предупреждал Ну
please well I don't know how this is
пожалуйста ну я я не знаю как это
Well, I don't know, at school with her
получилось Ну не знаю же в школе с ней
we sat at the same desk together here she is
вместе за одной партой сидели тут она
she said something and put her hand on me like this
что-то сказала руку мне вот так положил
I have a bump and that's it and that's it
у меня шишка чпок и всё и всё уже в
In the process in the morning she asked for money for the salon
процессе с утра денег на салон попросила
She said that her phone was broken and that Mom needed it.
сказала что телефон сломался И Маме надо
help with teeth No, well, if it's mom Listen
помочь с зубами Не ну если маме Слушай
This old [ __ ] is not worth the money
Это старая прошмандовка за эти деньги не
that the tooth vampire fangs itself can
то что зуб вампирские клыки себе может
put the sphere of [ __ ]
ставить сфера бляд
What should I do now?
что ж теперь делать-то
what is it on these courses of yours?
что там на твоих этих курсах это
they said hatchback
говорили хэтчбека
pickup is not allowed so that she can take you away
пикапа нельзя чтобы она вас себе
fixed it switch to another one
починила переключитесь на другую
I can give Svetkina's fang to a woman
женщину я могу светкина клыка дать для
let me pull you into the beginning
начала сойдёт Давайте Я потяну вас в
on this issue Let me make you
этом вопросе Давай сделаю из вас
Alf do you know who this is?
Альф знаете кто это
Sasha, what do you think, I'm completely [ __ ]?
Саш ты что я по твоему совсем отсталый
what? Of course I know this is Alf
что ли Конечно знаю это Альф
alien only What does it have to do with it
инопланетянин только Причём здесь
I'm Masha, hello. What do we have there? Who is this Masha?
я Маш привет Что у нас там кто сего Маша
today on the set And I'm under her Sometimes I
сегодня на съёмках А я её под Иногда я
Marina Marina No I will forget you all
Марина Марина Нет я так забу вас всех
you will remember today Masha Okay, that's all
запоминать сегодня будешь Маша Ладно все
who is on this chair
кто на этом стуле
Masha how
Маша как
say a man comes into the office without
скаже мужчина прил жтс в кабинете без
records but he was very persistent it's the same
записи но он был очень настойчив это же
I missed it and I'll fire you now, Masha
упустила я а я же тебя сейчас уволю Маш
me or
меня или
Masha women you will destroy this
Машу бабы вы уничтожите этот
world so forgive me who are you and why are you without
мир так простите вы кто и почему вы без
records to me Maria Sit down fool what does it mean
записи мне Мария Сядь дурачок что значит
Sit down, you fool, how am I the director of yourself?
Сядь дурачок как я директор те себе
finally allow money to be drunk
позволяете в конце концов дено пй до
full
полного
what diesel per 1000
чего дизель на 1000
[music]
[музыка]
And listen to me carefully, Uncle Me.
А слушай меня внимательно дядя Меня
My name is Egor. I was sent by the owners of everything.
зовут Егор Меня послали владельцы всего
of this holiday
этого праздника
Why did you say at the presentation that there were shares?
Зачем на презентации сказал что акции
grow can grow after what is there
растут могут расти после того что там
NS I'm not from Simonov I'm from those people
НС я не от Симонова я от тех людей
which he tries
которых он пытаются
[ __ ] from whom from the Financial group
наебать От кого От Финансовой группы
which owns the majority of shares
которая владеет большей частью акций
these shares and Simonov uses you
этих акций а Симонов использует тебя
wants to bring them down so he can buy them up later
хочет их обрушить чтобы потом скупить по
cheap but we won't do that to him
дешёвке но мы ему этого сделать не
let me
позволим меня
Unfortunately we can't fire this
уволить к сожалению не можем это
the last year when Simonov has the right
последний год когда Симонов Имеет право
hire a general manager yourself
самостоятельно нанимать генеральным
director than you
директором чем вы
uses Well then I'll tell him everything
пользуется Ну я ему тогда всё расскажу
let him
он пусть
he'll figure it out, you still don't understand anything No
разберётся ты так ничего не понял Нет
Simonov is not your friend. He hired you to
Симонов тебе не друг Он нанял тебя чтобы
You are an idiot who is filming
подставить Ты идиот который снимает
what a piece of [ __ ] you're investing your money in
лютое дерьмище вы вкладываете бабки в
a series that no one will ever have
сериал который никто никогда не будет
look at all these freaks you hired
смотреть все эти уродцы которых ты нанял
will remain without work for the rest of their lives and
останутся на всю жизнь без работы а на
you will be hung with fines and debts
тебя повесят штрафы и долговые
obligations You will not pay off until
обязательства Ты не расплатишься до
at the end of your life you will sell your apartment and
конца своей жизни ты квартиру продашь и
both kidneys And when this [ __ ] comes out
обе почки А когда эта [__] выйдет в
ether is your life
эфир твоя жизнь
what will happen to me when it ends
кончится что ж мне
do You only have one
делать У тебя есть только один
chance we need to make a normal series the most
шанс нужно снять нормальный сериал самый
ordinary The main thing is that it doesn't fail
обыкновенный Главное чтобы не провалился
then Simonov won't be able to fire you. And in
тогда Симонов не сможет Тебя уволить А в
next year when we come to last we
следующем году Когда мы придём ласти мы
We'll fire you, that's it
тебя уволим так вед это же
humanely
по-человечески
with good
с хорошими
golden recommendations
рекомендациями золотым
parash Why the [ __ ] are you melting gold Parat for me?
параш Нахуя мне золотой Парат плавишь
sale
прода
that they wanted to make a good movie I don't now
что хотели снять хорошее кино Я тепер не
I know what to do
знаю что делать
In short, fire everyone you hired immediately
короче всех кого ты нанял срочно уволить
I'll give you a normal director.
Я дам тебе нормального режиссёра
screenwriter they made the hotel it
сценариста они делали отель это
I can fire them. How is that possible?
лю могу их уволить Как же это
wife Valery Mashka and wx somehow
жено Валерка Машка и жх как-то
made friends in Svetka artist get rid of
подружились ин Светка артист избавь от
details
подробностей
You have a choice, a good life or
У тебя есть выбор хорошая жизнь или
halfwit
полудурок
[music]
[музыка]
and was killed the other day Try to get it out
и убита на днях Попробуй вывести
put our director from the game
режиссёра из игры поставить нашего
cut the little man somehow you are here more
человечка к режи как то ты больше здесь
There's no one here, just hurry up and do all this.
никого нету толь Давай побыстрее всё это
we need to take it off before 5am because at 6am we
нужно снять до 5 утра потому что в 6 нам
I need to get up and go to the main road
нужно вставать и ехать на основную
I offer a job, it's cool, and the script
работу Я предлагаю это ништяк а сценарий
Valera promised something
Валера обещала что-то
I would never throw such code
накидать такого кода е никогда не
I heard we're going to tear this world of cinema apart
слышал мы порвём этот мир кино
earlier in the series you want us to
ранее в сериале ты хочешь чтобы мы
they started showing things that no one would watch
начали показывать то что никто смотреть
if there is no stock, it will become cheaper and we will buy them up
не будет акции подешевеют и мы их скупим
We need a new CEO in full
полностью Нам нужен новый генеральный
Director Seventh Column Diesel Do
директор Седьмая колоно дизель до
a complete person capable of creating such
полного Человек способный создать такой
a product that everyone will hate
продукт который будет ненавидеть все Зри
I want a series
Я хочу сериа
the team is in a best-case scenario to film a TV series
команда раким способом до снять в сериал
pieces that no one but us knows about
куски про которые кроме нас никто не
knows The [ __ ] went wild
знает Понеслась [__] по
It is a great honor for me to work with bumps
кочкам для меня большая честь работать с
I ate like you, how did it happen?
таким проел как вы как это произошло она
All the time she sent me away and insulted me.
всё время меня посылала оскорбляла А
Now he only wants my money
сейчас хочет только мои бабки
switch to another
переключитесь на другую
woman vicious passion My name is Egor
женщину порочная страсть Меня зовут Егор
I was sent by the owners of all this
Меня послали владельцы всего этого
holiday me fire everyone you
праздника меня уволить всех кого ты
hired urgently fire
нанял срочно уволить
[music]
[музыка]
strangely it doesn't dull the pain like
странно не заглушает боли как
earlier when I crashed my plane over
раньше когда я разбилась на самолёте над
taiga I also have a lot
тайгой Я тоже много
the saw tried to dull the pain and how do you
пила пыталась заглушить боль и как тебе
managed to drown out the pain
удалось заглушить боль
No, I couldn't mute it.
Нет мне не удалось заглушить
there is pain
боль есть
handkerchief vera yes yes
платок провера да Да
Holy [ __ ] I've never been like this before
[__] я такого ковда ещ никогда не
I heard so-so It's a pity I said that
слышал так себе Жалко я говорила что
too much about pain what
слишком много про боль что же
do as
делать как
Excuse me, please tell me the text
же Извините подскажите текст
please how can I dull the pain Yeah
пожалуйста как же заглушить боль Ага
thank you so much
спасибо как
or muffle
же заглушить
pain Herman pain cannot be drowned out
боль Герман боль не заглушить
no way stop
никак стоп
removed Tell them they have a real one there no lo s
снято Скажи у них там настоящий нет ло с
with boiled water so that it doesn't foam
водой прокипячённой чтобы не пенилось
find the real one
найди настоящий
roch Guys this is incredible guys this is
роч Ребята это невероятно ребят Это
just amazing rub me
просто потрясающе потрите ме
tears
слёзы
Vladislav here
Владислав вде
why did you go to this Isolde Arina
чего заехал к этой к изольде Арине к
Arina Arina Arina without Yes I know that
Арине Арине Арина без Да я знаю что
Arina without But why are you always me
Арина без Но что ты меня всё время
you make everything look like Sorry, you don't know
выставляешь каким всё Извините не знаеш
does she have someone I mean who Well I mean
есть у неё кто В смысле кто Ну в смысле
Well, some kind of a dumbass, a husband, a guy
Ну долбилка какая-нибудь там муж парень
M And why do you need it and what is your salary?
М А вам зачем а зарплата тебе
why is there no husband Judging by the questionnaire a
зачем мужа нет Судя по анкете а
otherwise no
остальном не
I know. Do you think she really has it?
знаю А как думаешь реально ей ширша
hit me now you are serious with me about
врезать вы сейчас серьёзно со мной об
What do you recommend about this?
этом советуете
Yes, well then, come here.
да Так ну-ка иди-ка сюда
extras come on this [ __ ] for free here
массовка ну-ка это Нехер на халяву тут
eat this for real actors everything
жрать это для настоящих актёров всё
ul Listen here How serious I am
ул Слушай сюда Какая у меня серьёзная
trouble happened to me suddenly
беда приключилась за моими внезапно
with the resulting money and high
образовавшимися бабками и высоким
My ex is chasing after my social status
социальным статусом гоняется моя бывшая
same
же
In short, it can have an impact on
Короче говоря она может оказывать на
I have influence, you know, she twists you
меня влияние понимаешь она крутит вами
like a sucker yes no yes and the situation
как лохом да нет да и ситуация
got worse after our recent sex
усугубилась после нашего недавнего секса
and she constantly asks me to lend her money and
и она постоянно просит занять ей денег и
hints in every possible way to come together
намекает всячески на слова сходиться
you have to understand so well what it is
надо понимаешь так отлично какое это
Sashka Well has something to do with all of us
отношение имеет ко всем нам Сашка Ну
My driver teaches at some
водитель мой преподаёт на каких-то
driving course and they told him there that in
автокурс и ему там рассказали что в
in such cases you need to switch to
таких случаях надо переключаться на
a new woman for a driving course, well, something's wrong
новую бабу на автокурс да ну что-то с
I don't remember the pickup and you decided
пикапа связано я не помню и вы решили
that Arina is a suitable option Here you go
что Арина подходящий вариант Во вот
only you understand me and I don't understand you
только ты меня понимаешь А я вас не
I understand, but Sveta is not enough for you or something
понимаю а Светы Вам мало или там по
instructions two are needed no there is a new one needed
инструкции двух надо Нет там новую надо
I already had light for that
света у меня уже брала была на тот
moment so great now where in this
момент так отлично теперь где в этом
in the mysterious equation I am this one
загадочном уравнении я вот вот этот
ridiculous pick-up line I'm rich sexy
нелепый подкат я богатый сексуальный
man this is complete nonsense chu sexy and
мужик это Полная ерунда чу сексуальный и
rich only by his own standards Oh listen
богат только по своим меркам Ой слушай
richer than some, in short, there are women there
побогаче некоторых короче там бабы
more seriously Svetka There is just a sluggish one
посерьёзнее Светки Там вялого просто так
don't steam the entry
не попарить заход
This is how I hang out here. You know, this is how I hang out here.
такой я здесь тусуюсь Вот и такой знаешь
like I came to check on yours
типа приехал проконтролировать вашу
work by the way yes And you are like that
работу между прочим да А ты ты такая
all day long she's been like that in her ears
целый день ей так в уши туда по
they throw in a few facts there Well, oh
чуть-чуть забрасывают туда факты Ну о
that I'm like that there
том что я там типа такой
fum
фум
such as Well, you understand Well, such as I am not
такой какой Ну ты поняла Ну какой я не
I understood Well, I'm the most enviable man that
поняла Ну что я самый завидный мужик что
behind me there are people standing in line on all fours
за мной ба там в очередь стоят раком до
The Kremlin can't rearrange them, what will I do?
Кремля их не переставить что я буду
rule the world Well, come up with something
управлять миром Ну придумай что-нибудь
on the whip, do I need to teach you or something?
на плети что мне тебя учить нужно что ли
How I got drunk here at Davi and stole it there
Как я набухался вот Дави и там угнал
cop
ментовскую
so go like this
таку Так иди
work I have the power to raise you
работай У меня есть власть повысить тебе
salary I raise your salary
зарплату Я повышаю твою заработную плату
by 20%
на 20%
and tell her that you [ __ ] me
а и скажи ей что ты со мной [__] что
I'm so sick of the picket fence
меня хер как штакет от забора очень
long Oh, and you're not with
длинный Ой а вы не с
aliexpress I am much better
алиэкспрес Я гораздо лучше
Olya My name is Egor I am a person who
Олей Меня зовут Егор я человек который
effectively solves
эффективно решает
problems I won't buy a vacuum cleaner on the spot
проблемы Я не куплю пылесос на самом
in fact if I say
деле если я скажу
buy Sit down
купишь Присядь
do you want to buy a collectible figurine
вы хотите купить коллекционную фигурку
coconut cat number
кота кокоса под номером
one Sorry I won't sell she's dear to me
один Извините я не продам она дорога мне
leave it as a memory
как память оставь
I want you to take these
себе Я хочу чтобы ты взял эти
money And in return he allowed m to write
деньги А взамен позволил м Написать
good script Who are we for
хороший сценарий Кому нам
It doesn't matter the script is already in production
неважно на сценарий уже в производстве
we just write more episodes and nothing happens to me
мы просто пишем серии дальше И ничего я
I will find authors who will save anyone
найду таких авторов которые спасут любую
troubles all that is required of you is necessary
бед всё что от тебя требуется нужно
send us what you haven't removed yet
прислать нам то что вы ещё не сняли заме
you will give what is needed to the film crew
выш то что нужно ты отдашь съёмочной
group and you will earn
группе и заработаешь
money script with me deciphers
денег сценарий со мной расшифровывает
girl with
девочка с
channel these are your problems solve it yourself
канала это уже твои пробле решай сам
I suggest
Я предлагаю
[music]
[музыка]
this is by listening
это по слуша
Father We checked yours
отец Мы проверили твои
bills You have a house under
счета У тебя дом под
collateral loans for all
залогом кредиты на всех
maps your real earnings from this
картах твой реальный заработок с этого
the series won't cover anything
сериала не покроет ничего
this is your last chance to meet
это твой последний шанс встретить
old age is not cheap
старость не в дешёвый
bagatelle no
багатель не
pick up or
забрать или
leave
оставить
great This is my email
отлично Это моя электронная почта
you only keep in touch with me by email
держишь со мной связь только по
you don't tell her or anyone about it
ней и никому об этом не говоришь
Yes, this is Egor. In general, grandpa, I paid.
Да это Егор В общем дедуль я заплатил
I'll try to correct the script in a few days
сценарий выправить на днях попробую
take the director out of the game and put
вывести режиссёра из игры и поставить
our little man Vladislav himself
нашего человечка сам Владислав
Ladislav himself didn't answer anything. I left.
сам ладислав ничего не ответил Я оставил
gave him his number and told him to
ему свой номер и сказал чтобы он
I thought not
думал не
called back Good
перезвонил Хорошо
I'm waiting Phew, I've run so much that I have no strength. And I
жду Фух на бегала сил нет А у меня
Vitamins are great if you are tired
витаминки есть отлич Если ты устала
do you want Don't bother thanks Just boss
хочешь Не нери спасибо Просто бос
I arrived and when he was nearby I was just somehow
приехал а он когда рядом Мне прям как-то
I don't feel comfortable with such male charisma
не по себе такая Харизма мужская
you know, well, we're not really with him
понимаешь ну мы на самом деле с ним не
familiar
знакомы
But they say that he personally
Но поговаривают что он меня лично
approved Oh that's for sure It means you liked it
утвердил О это точно Значит понравилось
so I envy you cool man
так Завидую тебе крутой мужик
of course he is of age Well of age what
конечно Он в возрасте Ну в возрасте что
right away age age is experience now
сразу возраст возраст - это опыт сейчас
they don't make them like that anymore, he's educated
таких уже не делают он и образованный
studied at sorbo da
учился в сорбо да
yes master of horse food and chess
да мастер верховой еды и шахмати
Yaki knows
яки знает
what Well, you're Japanese
какие Ну вот ты японский
you know, does he like live music?
знаешь а он да музыку живую любишь
of course Well what instrument is there fano
конечно Ну какой инструмент там фано
chape, he plays fano like a god
шапе так он же на фано шпарит как Бог
chape especially last year
шапе особенно в прошлом году
international piano competition won
международный конкурс пианиста выиграл
Are you serious? And what is your position?
Ты что серьёзно Да а должность Какая
perspective and not married Just
перспектива и не женат Просто
dream Wait if he's so cool
мечта Подожди если он такой классный
Why don't you go with him yourself? Oh, yes, we would.
Почему ты сама с ним не Ой да бы у нас
Novel
Роман
but u
но у
his dick is 30 cm damn yeah [ __ ] yeah and
него член 30 см блин Да ну нахуй Да а у
me well as for the Japanese you know
меня ну как как для японцев Понимаешь
I was in real pain, it was painful
мне реально больно было больно
Arin Damned nature Why did this happen to me
Арин Проклятая природа За что мне так
Okay, sorry.
Ладно извините
distracted
отвлекла
Work for you roulette
Работайте у тебя рулетка
yes Vlad I understand that you are big
есть Влад я понимаю что вы большой
Coconut cat fan if possible
поклонник кота кокоса если можно не
Sing and accordingly admirer of Valera
Пойте и соответственно поклонник Валеры
I like him too but the script is He
он мне тоже нравится но сценарий Он
a bit like
немного как бы
Is it too weak to say that? No, it can't.
сказать слабоват что ли это Да не может
to be yes 100% I had to read and
быть да 100% мне приходилось читать и
more interesting Although I haven't worked with a genius
поинтереснее Хотя я не работал с гением
I want to tell you that maybe
хочу вам сказать Я к тому что может
somehow help him with ideas
как-то ему помочь идеями
advice
советами
Vlad, I'm sorry, I missed something again.
Влад извини Я прослушал чего ещё раз я
I say Maybe he can get help about this
говорю Может ему помо по поводу
next scene Oh hello Sorry
следующей сцены Ой здравствуйте Извините
we don't know each other Arina this is our Vladislav
мы не знакомы Арина это Владислав наш
Producer and CEO
продюсер и генеральный директор
TV channel
телеканала
seriously so young oh so interesting
серьёзно такой молодой Ой так интересно
listen to how you achieved all this
послушать как вы всего этого добились мы
let's agree if possible, good Yes yes yes
договорим если можно хорошо Да да да
of course of course sorry I'll be in
конечно конечно извините я буду в
the actor's nut right yes
актёрской орех прямо да
gu I hope he breaks up soon
гу Я надеюсь его скоро расстал
what Well Arina she was free thought
чего Ну Арина она свободна думал
invite where I know where Yes where to the cat
пригласить куда я знаю куда Да куда коту
under the muda And you haven't mixed anything up, my dear
под муда А ты ничего не попутала родной
I approved it and I will crack the nut
я её утвердил я и орех раскалывать буду
But as far as I know you already have one
Но насколько я знаю у вас уже есть одна
that now I only have one pair of shoes
что теперь у меня вон и ботинки одни
yes, should I not go to the shoe store now?
есть м теперь в обувной не ходить что ли
And it seems to me that it is a little unfair when
А мне кажется что немного нечестно когда
Some people have two pairs of shoes and others
у кого-то две пары ботинок а кто-то
sideways What are you starting? Well, please get out
боком Что начинаешь Ну пожалуйста вон
sits here please you are lost take it and
сидит вот пожалуйста ты теряешься бери и
everything with not even sure can speak And you
всё со даже не уверен умет разго А ты
Are you going to the cities with her?
что с ней в города что ли собираешься
play Good afternoon, I'm Igor
играть Добрый день я Игорь
director
режиссёр
Yes, you can. Oh, I'm sorry, please. I'll do that then.
Да можно Ой извини пожалуйста я тогда
everything is fine, I'm not naked
всё в порядке я ж не голая а
It's a pity. I mean, it's not like I like to stare.
жаль В смысле не то что Я люблю пялиться
on the naked Well, no of course I love
на голох Ну вот Нет конечно Я люблю
when necessary and so that it shines on all sorts of things
когда надо а так чтобы на всяких сверкай
there it's just like that, in short, it's normal, I mean, yeah
там просто так короче нормально я а да
yes yes come in and make yourself at home You can do that
да да проходи располагайся Можно же на
you Yes you can yes of course yeah yeah yeah oh right
ты Да можно да конечно угу угу ой сечас
I'll fix what's in the way
поправлю что мешается
ABOUT
О
well well maybe you can tell me how you do it well
ну ну может расскажешь как ты это ну
rose to the very top such stories se
поднялся На самый верх такие истории се
so inspiring i worked as a gas station attendant
так вдохновляют я я работал заправщиком
burned my car
жёг тачку меня
I bought myself off and I'm happy
откупились я весёлый
Wow, you're funny, right?
Ух А ты Весёлый да
Yes, and I came to conquer, so to speak.
да А я приехала Так сказать покорять
Moscow from Penza Yes, and
Москву вот из Пензы Да а
This is my first leading role. And before that
Это моя первая главная роль А до этого
there were a couple
было пару
advertisements
реклам
Well, maybe you can come to my house today.
вот Может приедешь ко мне сегодня домой
In the evening the script
Вечером сценарий
we will read to you at home yes
почитаем к вам домой да
Oh, and the script is New Well, that's how I understood it
О а сценарий Новый он же Ну я так поняла
that he is not ready that he is being written in
что он не готов что он пишется в
I understood it in the process
процессе я так поняла
Well, let's read something
Ну почитаем какой-нибудь
another old one
другой старый
Let's read Let's read
почитаем Давай
address quiet quiet quiet don't be afraid darling
адрес тихо тихо тихо не бойся родной
what are you drinking for your health drink my dear drink
чего ты пей на здоровье пей родной пей
what is your name
как звать
Vityusha Let's go cut and burn, he allowed him
Витюша Давай к режи и сжи разрешил ему
give you a line of text Thank you Thank you
дать тебе строчку текста Спасибо Спасибо
big Come on darling come on come on
большое Давай родной давай давай
Come on Are you crazy or something? Quiet, you
давай Да вы поехавший что ли что Тихо ты
quiet, what are you yelling about? Mash, you're putting sausage in
тихо что ты орёшь-то Маш вы колбасу в
wore panties and then back to the buffet
трусах носили а потом обратно буфет
put Yes and what's the problem Well with her
положили Да и какая проблема Ну с ней
nothing at all She didn't even mention red mullet
вообще ничего Она даже о барабульки не
I rubbed it with strips and everything is all fu
тёрла с о полосок и всё всё фу
Take her away from here immediately Mash, come on
немедленно Уберите её отсюда Маш ну на
the crowd will demolish everything often Oh, what are you saying
массовка всё снесёт по частую Ну что ты
you start
ты начинаешь
Vladislav thinks I have a ticklish personality
Владислав думае что у меня щекотун
such a good thing mom is not
такой Хорошо мама не
sees Well, what's going on with our secret operation?
видит Ну что там с наши тайной операции
everything is ready You mean night shooting I found
всё готово Ты про ночную съёмку Я нашла
a couple of checks from the crowd, one acquaintance
пару чек из массовки одну знакомую
unemployed make-up artist she namus film 5
безработ ную гримёр она намус фильме 5
Did I steal blood? But the most important thing I found
ли крови украла Но самое главное я нашла
one type of actress who is not going anywhere
одну типа актрису которая никуда не
But her husband gives us money, which she does for us
берут Зато у её мужа денег шо она нам за
roles half a million pays a ton in one day
роли пол-ляма платит ништяк одним днём
it paid off as I said and I have heaps
окупилось как я и говорил а у меня кучи
I'll take a camera and a couple from the warehouse
от склада я возьму камеру и пару
devices and Valera promised a scenario
приборов а сценарий Валера обещала
throw something We will tear this world of cinema apart
что-то накидать Мы порвём этот мир кино
Yeah, Sanya, you're a real handsome guy.
Угу Саня ты красавчик вообще вот прям
everything you advised worked
вот всё что ты советовал всё сработало
everything Masha and also ears are on fire and Arina
всё Машка ещё и уши накала и Арина
today he's coming to read to me
сегодня едет ко мне читать
scenarios Where to your home I mean here
сценарии Куда к вам домой В смысле сюда
home Where do you live Well, what are you talking about
домой Где вы живёте Ну да вы что
Vladislav is a chovnik Oh, do you hear?
Владислав это же човник Ой слышишь ты
in general, from Kapotnya you have fish there
вообще из Капотне у вас там рыбы с
four Burka Chupacabras through the streets
четырьмя Бурка чупакабры по улицам
I run yes but it's not about me you're in her
бегают я да но речь не обо мне вы в её
in the eyes of a show-off
глазах понтовый
Dude, a show-off dude, can't live like this
чувак понтовый чувак так жить не может
This is a deceived expectation, it's as if she
Это обманутое ожидание это как если она
undresses and she has a hose and
разденется А у неё шланг и
cuckoos
кокушки
[ __ ] you didn't expect this
ледибой именно вы этого не ожидали вам
it will be unpleasant to give myself to her like that
будет неприятно так и ей отдаться
dream man in a house with vietnamese
мужчине мечты в доме с вьетнамским
I don't really want to have a hostel in the entrance
хостелом в подъезде не очень охот это
miscalculation so centuries me some
просчёт так века меня какую-нибудь
write hotel quickly
гостиницу быстро написать
what A what e
что А что е
write butlers started a rearrangement
написать дворецки затеял перестановку
furniture for sure
мебе точно
maybe you really think that she has
може что ты реально думаешь что у неё
there is Red Hulk
там Красный Халк
It seems to be hanging out
болтается дака Вроде
no hi hi come in
нет привет привет Заходи
To be honest, I feel a little awkward
Я если честно себя немножко неловко
I feel Come on, what are you saying, just give it up
чувствую Да ладно что ты брось ты
come on in while I'm there, settle in
проходи пока там располагайся я
I'll change my clothes
переоденусь
Well, sit down, Arin, why are you standing there?
Ну ты садись Арин что ты стоишь-то
What
Что
happened What is Nothing nothing
случилось Что такое Ничего ничего
Sorry, let's just read it already.
Простите давайте давайте уже читать
oh well, I don't really have any
а ну у меня как бы нет
scenario I understand everything from Penza you don't know
сценария Я всё понимаю из Пензы не знаеш
what a fool
что дура
let's do it without a script
давайте уже без сценария
Come on, why are you crying?
давайте что ты плачешь-то
I
я
virgin who are you
девственница кто ты
virgin is this
девственница это
surname vocation Well what
фамилия призвание Ну какая
surname virgin meaning sex me
фамилия девственица смысле сексо меня
never been and how many years are you 25 Well
никогда не было а лет те сколько 25 Ну
it doesn't matter I just wanted the first one
это неважно Я просто хотела чтобы первый
once I had a beautiful one so that's it
раз у меня красивый был чтобы вот вот
This was the first time I've ever done this
такой первый раз был я не
wanted Are you sure you're a virgin
хотела Ты уверена что ты девственница
because you don't look like
потому что выглядишь ты не как
virgin is this
девственница это
How can I not be beautiful anymore?
какже мне уже нельзя быть красивой
the parents didn't have anything
ничего у родителе не было тка в
I worked at a music school and they stuck me in there
музыкальной школе работала туда засунули
then one theater didn't take me to finish
потом в один театраль не взяли закончи
I'm taking acting classes here and I'm renting a room
Като актёрские курсы тут комнату снимаю
No, I actually had a role.
Нет у меня была роль на самом деле была
Rema Where I play whom I play
рема Где я балу играю кого балу балу
the virus will excite and kill Kong and me
вирус возбудит е прикончит Конг и меня
there they water I die with the words to me
там поливают Я умираю со словами мне
death came from the roots, defeated and killed
смер пришла от корени побеждена и убита
remember Yes no well maybe not
помните Да нет ну может быть не
I know Nobody remembers It's my first time in
знаю Никто не помнит У меня первый раз в
life some serious role project And I
жизни какая-то серьёзная роль проект А я
this is what they said about you in the hallway today
про вас сегодня такое в коридоре
I heard it doesn't matter, everyone says that
услышала неважно нуже все говорят что
that's how you should live, you see a man who
так и надо жить видишь мужика который
the rich man is interested in you and it doesn't matter
богатый тобой заинтересовался и неважно
that he is bald, old, fat, it's not
что он лысый старый толстый это безо
now if he liked you, that's sha
сечас вот если ты ему понравилась это ша
and is this necessary?
и надо это ль
do whatever you want, just do it for him
как хочешь делай что хочешь лишь бы ему
to be liked and that's why I
понравиться и вот поэтому я
I came, don't kick me out, please
пришла не не выгоняйте меня пожалуйста
from
из
series
сериала
I wanted this with you
Я хотел с тобой это
here well
тут ну
to get my ex-wife to leave me alone
чтобы от меня моя бывшая жена отстала
she she wants to come back to me but I don't
она она хочет ко мне вернуться А я не
I want it to be like you and me
хочу тут получается что мы с тобой
I came up with the idea of two peas in a pod
два сапога пара я придумала
what
чего
Now I have jewelry here from different places
сейчас вот у меня тут бижутерия с разных
filming is left than watch hop
съёмок осталась чем смотрите хоп
ring Here, let's do it
колечко Вот ну-ка давайте че
oops oops look
оп оп смотрите
send this photo to your ex-wife and
отправите это фото своей бывшей жене и
say that you met the love of your life
скажете что встретили любовь всей своей
life If she doesn't believe me, I'll confirm and she will
жизни Если не поверит я подтвержу и она
will leave you alone
от вас отстанет
And we don't need that either then
А это и нам не обязательно тогда
[ __ ] you yes no at all but we can
трахаться с тобой да Вовсе нет А можем
by the way just to go for dinner I'm like that
кстати просто по ужину сходить Я такая
hungry Yes, let's do it just me and a couple
голодная Да так и сделаем только я пару
Viagra screwed in I need kefir to drain not
Виагры вкрутил Мне нужен кефир слить не
will you help no
поможешь нет
[music]
[музыка]
Guaranteed everything GM
гарену всё ГМ
and your name
and your name
[music]
[музыка]
Hello, night owls, Lera, hello, let's go
Здорово полуночники Лера привет давайте
I will introduce everyone to everyone. This is Valery.
я всех со всеми познакомлю Это Валерий
our author Vasily he is the cameraman Vera Dima
наш автор Василий он оператор Вера Дима
the actors and Lika accordingly too
актёры и Лика соответственно тоже
actress Lika you brought
актриса Лика вы привезли
moneyne And this is the only place
деньгине А это единственное место
which we managed to get hold of for
которое удалось раздобыть для
just by acquaintance but Valera something
по знакомству просто на но Валера что-то
managed to
удалось со
I was guided by two scenarios
сценарием я руководствовался двумя
things our first story about
вещами первая наша история про
parallel worlds because that's the only way
параллельные миры потому что только так
can we justify the absence of our actors
можно оправдать отсутствие наших актёров
Kurinka's second wish about cruelty
второе пожелание куринка о жестоких
there's something about the bloody scenes that I'm already scared of
кровавых сценах что-то Мне уже страшно
ok, here are our heroes
ладно Вот наши герои это как
Isolde and Violetta but in
быте Изольда и Виолетта но в
parallel reality and therefore
параллельной реальности поэтому и
They look different
выглядят Они по-другому
in general, Valery's gun is now such a thing
вообще пушка Валер сейчас такое см
Cameron will suck And what about the blood on the spot
Кэмерон отсосёт А что с кровище на месте
And we will show that in this reality and
А мы покажем что в этой реальность и
hatred replaced love for them and they killed
ненависть заменила им любовь и они убили
Friend
друг
friend's last
друга Последний
survivor
выживший
he cut off his own head
сам отрезал себе голову
and how can you cut off your own head? Well
а как можно само себе резать голову Ну
this is a parallel reality, huh, yeah, well
это же Параллельная реальность а Угу Ну
what director take script command who
что режиссёр бери сценарий командуй Кто
director somehow you are no one else here
режиссёр как то ты больше здесь никого
no, just hurry up and do it all
нету только давай побыстрее всё это
need to take off before 5:00 am because at 6
нужно снять до 5:00 утра потому что в 6
we need to get up and go to the main road
нам нужно вставать и ехать на основную
work So guys, here's the script
работу Так ребята держите сценарий
Rewrite Tom, put us in the dressing room
Переписывай Том поставь нам гримёрный
Need a renok table
столик ренок нужен
Svet Valery
свет Валерий
I made a thermos of coffee in the trunk
там термос кофе в багажнике я сделала
we are all
нас всё
[music]
[музыка]
bring this how to understand it? And what what
принесёте это как понимать-то А чего что
you sent me a photo of some
ты мне прислал фотку с какой-то
I met a clever young girl and I kind of met her
малолетней ловкой и типа я встретила
love walk akamy in general you are divorced
любовь гуляй акамы вобще тобо разводе в
Kuse A and when it comes to [ __ ] everything is fine
Кусе А как чпокаться так всё нормально а
how to talk about life like that in divorce Yes you
как о жизни говорить так в разводе Да ты
you start yelling Well, you come to me yourself
начинаешь ты орёшь Ну ты сама ко мне на
dick jumped Well
хер прыгнула Ну
I'll show you how good I am
дас покажу как я хороше
your fiancee called and said
пово звонила ваша невеста говорит
your future father-in-law is really looking forward to seeing you for breakfast
будущий тесть очень ждёт вас на завтрак
You promised to be there, but they have their own rules.
Вы обещали быть а у них по понятиям
he said it should be done, he was in the second zone
сказал надо делать он на зоне на второй
who was rude in the store they him
хово кто нагрубил в магазине они его
now they'll quickly hand it over to the cops I know
сейчас знакомым мусорам быстро сдадут
so that they would close it and also bring her to
чтобы закрыли и тоже привезут её к
breakfast well Tanya you I can give you
завтраку ну Таня ты Я могу тебе дать
phone you can talk to her yourself
телефон ты можешь поговорить с ней сама
personally Sasha Sasha you You are just a genius How
лично Саша Саша ты Ты просто гений Как
Why are you a simple driver and a former
ты Почему ты простой водитель а бывший
drug addict but normal
наркоман а нормуль
let's go Listen Violet, you're so easy about
поехали Слушай Виолет ты так легко об
you say this It's still mine
этом говоришь Это всё-таки моя
Mom, I think it's different for everyone.
мама мне кажется у каждого по-разному
I have been experiencing grief at school for a month
горе переживается я в школе месяц
I cried because of the fish And recently mine died
плакала из-за рыбки А недавно умер мой
grandfather
дедушка
and I didn't want tears but nothing Yeah
и не слезинки я хотела но ничего Да уж
losses make us realize who we are
потери заставляют нас понять кто мы есть
or who we are not
или кем не являемся
Listen to the [ __ ] new text, I don't even
Слушай охрененно новый текст даже не
It's not that I'm not ashamed
стыдно Да не то что не стыдно даже
just cool and really good Where from
просто круто да и правда хорошо А откуда
he took over Valera sent at night he says
он взялся Валера ночью прислал говорит
improved the dialogues he can do great
доработал диалоги он озы может классно
write Well, it would be impossible where
писать Ну это невозможно бы где
Well, where was he supposed to sleep at night?
он ну где спать должен был ночью-то
so you didn't sleep
значит не спал
stop guys guys my dears here
стоп ребята ребята дорогие мои вот
now I can with full responsibility
теперь я могу с полной ответственностью
say that we will have the coolest series
сказать что у нас будет крутейший сериал
guys for the viewer it will be complete
ребята для зритель это будет полный
knockout
нокаут
wow i have nothing to do with it
вау я не при чём
guys Accident
ребят Несчастный случай
Well
Ну что
[music]
[музыка]
[ __ ], the director is a slob who went to intensive care
[__] режиссёр жмых уехал в реанимацию
I don't know for long, but I'll hit him on the head with a device
надолго не знаю но прибором по башке я
I didn't want to receive
получить не хотел
would hold it like
бы держи как
[music]
[музыка]
agreed who you are and why you need it
договаривались вы кто такой И зачем вам
All
всё
this is a minibus
это маршрутка
yours Well the director is also ready Try
твоя Ну режиссёр тоже готов Попробуй
plant a normal teapot there
подсадить нем нормального чаечка
No, Vladislav himself hasn't responded yet
нет сам Владислав пока не отвечает
maybe
наверно
chooses a [ __ ] vine on
выбирает сраный витесь на
crossroads Svetik How about in This
распутье Светик Как насчёт в Это
beautiful morning delay [ __ ]
прекрасное утро отстрочить миньетик
m Let your seamstress be a motorist
м Пусть тебе Твоя швея мотористка
scribbles
строчит
what is this
чего вот
Manda she posted it
манда она её выложила
[music]
[музыка]
watch the next episode What happened
смотрите в следующей серии Что случилось
where it's quieter, quieter, don't shout Terminator
где тише тише не кричи Терминатор
they will hear you were in a coma for 12 years I suspect
услышат ты 12 лет был в коме подозреваю
that you and I are involved in a plot to turn away intrigues
что мы с вами вовлечены в отворот интриг
and the horseshoe fight collected the best TV
и подковный борьбы собрал лучшую ТВ
press Vlad for the presentation of this
прессу Влад для презентации этого
masterpiece and here is the first assembly of one of
шедевра а здесь первая сборка одной из
series buddy connect to the projector
серий дружище подключай к проектору
People, we are filming [ __ ], yes, yes
народ мы хуйню же Снимаем да да
pudov series bloody [ __ ] in the pit must
пудов сериал кровавые [__] в яме должен
become the most spectacular failure
стать самым грандиозным провалом
modern television now
современного телевидения сейчас
let's work
поработаем
[ __ ] earlier in
[__] ранее в
series do you want us to start
сериале ты хочешь чтобы мы начали
show something that no one will watch
показывать то что никто смотреть не
the shares will become cheaper and we will buy them up
будет акции подешевеют и мы их скупим
We need a new CEO in full
полностью Нам нужен новый генеральный
Director Seventh column diesel do
директор Седьмая колоночки дизель до
a complete person capable of creating such
полного Человек способный создать такой
a product that everyone will hate
продукт который будут ненавидеть Все
viewers Do any [ __ ] I want a series
зрители Твори любую херню Я хочу сериал
Team dm Team you offer us
Команда дм Team ты предлагаешь нам
finish filming it in some pirate way
каким-то пиратским способом доснять
series pieces about which no one but us
сериал куски про которые кроме нас никто
doesn't know The [ __ ] went wild
не знает Понеслась [__] по
Here's a ticket to the Maldives for the bumps
кочкам вот путёвка на Мальдивы Пусть
Your seamstress, the motorist, stitches for you. I stitch for you.
тебе Твоя швея мотористка строчит я те
ssia
сся
She posted it My name is Egor and I
она её выложила Меня зовут Егор и меня
send the owners of this whole holiday
посли владельцы всего этого праздника
I will fire everyone you hired immediately
всех кого ты нанял срочно уволить Я дам
you need a normal director and screenwriter
тебе нормального режиссёра и сценариста
for the viewers it will be complete
для зрителей это будет полный
knockout
нокаут
Oh yeah, are you [ __ ] nuts?
О да ты охуел что ли
cake What happened
жмых Что случилось
quieter quieter don't shout Terminator hear you
тише тише не кричи Терминатора услыши ты
I was in a coma for 12 years now it's the year 2031 of the machine
12 лет был в коме сейчас 2031 год машины
captured almost everything we are in
захватили практически всё мы находимся в
the last stronghold of man are you a fool
последнем оплоте человече Ты дурак что
Are you scaring him Igor don't worry
ли что ты его пугаешь Игорь не переживай
It's all not true
Это неправда всё в
I haven't been in a coma for 12 years, no
порядки я не пробыл в коме 12 лет нет
only P And you are now a woman
только П И ты теперь женщина
Vladislavka
владиславка
I applied the device myself
самом прибор приложила
Great
Здорово
let's drink you're kidding And what about the Soviet
накатим вы издеваетесь А что в Советском
In the Union, this is the only way they treated you, you are the only one here
Союзе только так и лечились ты одна тут
a child of the nineties and older men
детя девяностых а мужики постарше всё
Do you understand that you will actually drink? Yes
понимают вы что реально будете пить Да
yes of course we will Well then I will
да конечно будем Ну ну тогда я буду
How long should I stay here? The doctors say no.
сколько мне здесь быть Врачи говорят не
less than a week oh my god we have filming
меньше недели Господи у нас же съёмки
please don't be nervous about filming
пожалуйста те не надо нервничать съёмки
filming Especially since we have it there now
съёмками Тем более что у нас там сейчас
there are a couple of candidates later when
есть пару кандидатур потом когда
you will come back no this can't be
вернёшься нет этого не может быть
the surname Zhmykhov cannot be next to
фамилия жмыхов не может стоять рядом в
in the credits with some other surname each
титрах с какой-то другой фамилии каждый
the cake was always removed by one, this can't happen
жмых всегда снимал один такого не может
I beg you to be
быть вас прошу
Give
Дай
Guys, well, you feel like you owe me too.
ребята ну и ты чувствую что должен вам
something
кое-что
say I suspect that you and I
сказать подозреваю что мы с вами
involved in the lapel of intrigues and horseshoe
вовлечены в отворот интриг и подковный
struggle I think you Reread Valerin
борьбы Мне кажется вы Перечитай валерин
script No this is not Valerian script to
сценарий Нет это не валерин сценарий к
Unfortunately, this is life like this
сожалению это жизнь так вот некой
unknown to me semi-poker by name
неизвестный мне полупокер по имени
Egor offered me a sum of money to
Егор предложил мне сумму денег чтобы
it's obvious that someone is going to ruin our series
развалить наш сериал очевидно что кто-то
really doesn't want us to achieve this
очень не хочет чтобы мы с вами добились
grand success and is eager to destroy
грандиозного успеха и жаждет развалить
our series I didn't agree and I'm afraid that
наш сериал Я не согласился и боюсь что
the incident with Igor It is because of this
происшествие с Игорем Именно из-за этого
Tell me, has anything happened to anyone?
Скажите с кем-нибудь происходило что-то
unusual
необычное
and definitely to ruin In the sense of well, maybe
а точно развалить В смысле нуну Может
on the contrary, someone is waiting for us to fail
наоборот кто-то ждёт что мы провали а
another someone to harm the first
другой кто-то чтобы навредить первому
someone wants to do the opposite Well then
кому-то хочет сделать наоборот Ну то
there is Maybe what we
есть Может то что мы
we're not doing anything that grandiose
делаем не так уж и тянет на грандиозный
[music]
[музыка]
success Judas
успех Иуда
sparkles
искрит
nib that we make great movies
ниб что мы делаем великое кино
m well that's great Star team
м ну вот прекрасно Звёздная команда
we work
работаем мы
we'll win People, well, it's [ __ ] We'll shoot yes yes
победим Народ ну хуйню же Снимаем да да
No
нет
and what was the question, are we filming [ __ ]?
а какой был вопрос снимаем ли мы хуйню О
Yes
да
pudov Well, how is your new director Well
пудов Ну что Как ваш новый режиссёр Ну
maybe he will die but not a fact
возможно сдохнет но не факт но
the management sent a worthy one
руководство прислал достойную
candidate for replacement studied in America
кандидатуру на замену учился в Америке
In general, we have two people from Hollywood on
вообще у нас двое людей из Голливуда на
good project
проекте добрый
I know what to do with these women
зна голова кру с этими бабами что делать
It's not clear at all that show business is his mother
Непонятно вообще шоу-бизнес это его мать
so women are my thing, whatever
так бабы - это по моей части в чём там
problem Yes I wanted to register this boa constrictor
проблема Да я хотел удавы прописать этой
She started crying to Arina and said that
Арине она плакать начала сказала что
virgin and that's what never with
девственница и это что не никогда ни с
who is nothing girl there but doesn't look like yeah
кем ничего девочка там а не похожа да
That's what I'm talking about, that I didn't do it the same way
Вот и я о том же что не похожа сделала
in short, a photo with a ring like I gave it to her
короче фотографию с кольцом типа я ей
did
сделал
offer why How why well so that oty
предложение зачем Как зачем ну чтобы оты
from Well, why did I end up posting this photo in
от Ну зачем В итоге выложил эту фотку в
network and got me off not only from my ex
сеть и отмазал меня не только от бывшей
but now I can't get Yana Anka from Svetka either
но и от Светки теперь Яни Аньку не могу
saw off Svetka does not suck and arena shirsha
отпилить Светка не сосёт и арене ширша
Not
не
cut in the pitchforks yes yes and replace them I already
врезать вилы да да и заменить Я их уже
What can I do?
могу что же делать-то
And you know there is a solution
А Знаете есть решение
What the [ __ ] extras
Какое ебите массовку
[music]
[музыка]
spank
пороть
Manyu friends this is Victor the director who
Маню друзья это Виктор режиссёр который
will replace Igor
будет заменять Игоря
show
показват
SBO VM
СБО ВМ
I'm in charge of work ladies and gentlemen, let's get started
усь в прос рабо дамы и господа приступим
list yourself
список сам
[music]
[музыка]
please I can't believe it's me
пожалуйста Не могу поверить что это я
I've been here for about five years, probably not at all
мне здесь лет пять наверное совсем не
I remember this photo understand Violeta pain not
помню этого фото пойми Виолета боль не
allows us to live in peace and
даёт нам спокойно жить и
we we erase it from
мы мы стираем её из
memory stop stop was
памяти стоп стоп был
stop Oleg very interesting acting
стоп Олег очень интересное актёрское
solution Well, let's think about it together
решение Ну давайте мы с вами подумаем
about some other option and let's move on
ещё о каком-то варианте а отойдём
meditate
помедитируйте
look Victor we have a concept Shut up
смотрите Виктор у нас концепт Заткнись
idiot yes you can I don't know what you are
[__] да можеш я не знаешь что ты
I'm a [ __ ] understudy, but I'm unlike you
сраный дублер жо я в отличие от тебя
I worked in Hollywood normally but
по-нормальному в Голливуде отработал но
without but they gave me a mountain of money so that I
без но мне отвалили гору бабла чтобы я
I made something decent out of this [ __ ]
из этого дерьма сделал кое-что прилично
And I won't let you come between me and
И не позволю тебе стать между мной и
I got it from this mountain Yeah, so far the ass is the best
этой горой усёк Угу пока [__] лучшая
part of you is talentless but not hopeless
часть тебя ты бездари но не безнадёжно
let's start with what you
давай мы с тобой начнём с того что ты
you'll just pronounce the text That's how I will
будешь просто произносить текст Так я и
I pronounce you don't pronounce you
произношу ты не произносишь ты
he's making faces, no need to play anything, this is it
кривляется не надо ничего играть это
looks monstrous just say And when
выглядит чудовищно просто говори А когда
you will be
будешь
keep quiet Come on
молчать Давай
shut up the [ __ ] your gun is stupid
помолчи [__] у тебя ружи тупая
[ __ ], come on. Repeat the table to yourself.
бля ну-ка Повтори про себя таблицу
multiplications
умножения
what what did you hear come on 55 25 56 30 Come on
что что слышал давай 55 25 56 30 Давай
let's go ahead Well 57 35 yourself
давай вперёд Ну 57 35 себя
oh well you can
а ну вот можешь
went incredibly Oleg how lucky I am with
пошли невероятно Олег как мне повезло с
such a professional How do you work And
таким профессионалом Как вы работаете И
Your offer is excellent
предложение у вас отлично
let's implement them my dear
давайте мы их реализуем дорогой мой
good awesome
хорошо потрясающий
artist believe me Masha
артист верьте мне Маша
believe Hi Arin Why did you do this
верьте Привет Арин Зачем ты это сделала
Well, this is Alibi, as we agreed, like
Ну это Алиби Как мы договаривались типа
we have a relationship Well, that's for the wife, but
у нас отношения Ну так то для жены а
now everyone on the internet can see you can
теперь все в интернете видят Ты можешь
delete This I'm afraid that no why Well this
удалить Это боюсь что нет почему Ну это
my insurance so you don't kick me out A
моя страховка чтобы вы меня не выгнали А
so there is a reason for a scandal
так есть повод для скандала
I thought you were good Yes I am good nono
Я думал ты хорошая Да я хорошая нуно
I just really need at least one
просто мне очень нужна хотя бы одна
the main role A with my appearance
главная роль А с моей внешностью
for some reason it's hard to work without
почему-то тяжело работать так чтобы ни с
who not to [ __ ] I thought you
кем не трахаться Я думал ты
virgin do you know what it is
девственница Вы знаете что такое
the little train pulls the carriages in context
паровозик вагончики тянет в контексте
there is no sex and I know
секса нет А я знаю а
Babylonian
Вавилонская
this harlot
блудница вот эту
the scene needs to be divided into two, that's how we do it
сцену нужно разделить на две мы так
planned and inserted one between them
планировали и вставить между ними одну
from those bloody ones that we filmed recently
из тех кровавых что мы сняли недавно
Yeah
Ага
we share
разделяем
insert watch I don't know what awaits us
вставляем смотрим Я не знаю что ждёт нас
ahead but I know I want to meet it
впереди но знаю что хочу встретить это
together RN what happened to us Where
вместе РН что с нами случилось Где
we don't know just a minute ago we were in
мы не знаю ещё минуту назад мы были в
our apartment and looked
нашей квартире и выглядели
Otherwise I
Иначе я
I know what we should do now
знаю что же нам теперь
do not
делать Не
I know I think we're in
знаю мне кажется мы попали в
parallel universe
параллельную вселенную
I
Я
I know
знаю
no big deal we have a problem and we all have a problem or
нештяк у нас проблема а у нас всех или
only you two have jokes over 30 you
только у вас двоих шутки за 30 вам
you get a pig in a poke and you're an [ __ ] Well, what?
достаётся Кот в мешке и вы [__] Ну что
it starts normally, you were communicating
начинается нормально же общались вы
noticed that we have a new director and
заметили что у нас новый режиссёр Да и
he wants to edit it himself and demands everything
он хочет монтировать сам и требует весь
material No, I'm editing, well, you go to him
материал Нет я же монтирую ну ты иди ему
tell him about this and he will notice all our
об этом скажи а он же заметит все наши
inserted episodes and will understand what we are up to
вставные эпизоды и поймёт что мы до
we're filming something of ours there, you're the one with the ingenuity
снимаем туда что-то своё смекалка за ты
and you get the Crystal [ __ ] owl
и вам достаётся Хрустальная [__] сова
What to do?
Что делать-то
if we are not ready to show him
если мы не готовы показывать ему
We don't have the concept of parallel heroes
концепцию параллельных героев мы не
ready, need to cut everything out urgently before morning
готовы нужно срочно всё вырезать до утра
you'll manage everything
управишься Всю
tonight i need 27 whiskey box
ночь мне нужно 27 вискаря коробку
chocolate for the gentleman And why me what
шоколад кавалеру А меня-то зачем я что
dressed that I should howl all this Valera
одел что должен всё это выть Валеру
Take the rest, buy it in advance
Забирай остальное купишь вперёд
it's just a brain explosion, some kind of fire
это просто взрыв мозга какой-то огонь
that the bomb is just here it is here it is Vladislav
что бомба просто вот он вот он Владислав
Polyakov rising Media star Anton
Поляков восходящая Медиа звезда Антон
Grace portal series amani Anton Nice
Грас портал сериал амани Антон Приятно
nicely collected the best TV press Vlad for
приятно собрал лучшую ТВ прессу Влад для
the presentation of this masterpiece brought brought
презентации этого шедевра принёс принёс
here is the first assembly of one of the series
вот а здесь первая сборка одной из серий
after that he had no questions at all
после у него вопросов вообще никаких не
there will be some left believe me buddy connect to
останется поверьте дружище подключай к
projector Let's watch
проектору Давайте смотреть
are you worried
волнуешься
no friends within this presentation you
нет друзья в рамках этой презентации вы
you will see the first assembly of one of the series
увидите первую сборку одной из серий
our flagship project I ask you
нашего флагманского проекта Прошу вас
paint it in all colors for
распишите его во всех красках для
future viewers and our shareholders
будущих зрителей и наших акционеров
turn on
включай
what's so strong about that?
что так сил-то се
it's okay that it was a [ __ ] And I'm in the Star
нормально что это было [__] А я в Звезде
what was that on the screen I'm asking you
на экране что это было Я тебя спрашиваю
[ __ ] Bloody Pit people clapped creature
[__] Кровавой Яме люди хлопали [__]
I don't quite understand it badly It worked out Yes
я не совсем понимаю плохо Получилось Да
when it's bad people clap I don't know
плохо когда плохо люди хлопают не знаю
you don't like it I don't like it like well
вам не нравится Мне не нравится как ну
how did this happen this disk is for me
как это получилось вот это диск мне
today they gave it and I was there
сегодня дали и там было я
I don't understand, I read the dialogues there but
как я не понимаю я читал диалоги там но
they are completely different somehow
они совсем другие какие-то более
some peculiar some to me
какие-то своеобразные какие-то мне
They said Valera is rewriting a little
сказали Валера немножко переписывает
script and therefore it turns out better so that
сценарий и поэтому выходит получше чтобы
he rewrites it for him and the director does it
ему переписывает он а режиссёр это
will you give it to Nikovsky Well, how is it with us?
выдашь в никовский Ну как так у нас же
it was another director who did Victor from
это другой режиссёр делал Виктор из
America what and what other Victor from
Америки что да какой ещё Виктор из
America Well, how can you tell me about it yourself?
Америки Ну как же вы же мне его сами по
they sent it by mail when will I fly there
почте прислали когда ж маху там
a light fixture fell on my head
осветительный прибор на голову упал я
sent the device fell Yes you have a director
прислал прибор упал Да у вас режиссёр
new And I don't know anything about this How not
новый А я про это ничего не знаю Как не
you know, you sent it to me yourself
знаете Вы же мне сами его прислали по
mail Show me
почте Покажи бе смо
[ __ ] sorry can i leave no [ __ ]
[__] Извините А можно мне уйти нет сри
further
дальше
now and now now now like this Well
сейчас а сейчас сечас сейчас вот так Ну
well profile photo my go [ __ ] yourself
ну профиль Фотография моя иди твою мать
here is the address Simonov 75 And my address
здесь адрес Симонов 75 А мой адрес
Simonov
Симонов
1975 Do you understand what this is?
1975 Ты понимаешь что это
it means that you are 44 years old I will throw you in the toilet
значит что вам 44 года я тебя в унитаз у
I'm drowning Vlad, this means that someone has revealed it
топлю Влад это значит что кто-то раскрыл
my plan and he wants to interfere with me
мой план и хохочет мне помешать какой
plan Who will interfere I don't understand wait
план Кто кто помешает я не понимаю жди
[music]
[музыка]
instructions to [ __ ] what
инструкции посрать что
Did Andryusha find out everything while you were driving?
ли Андрюш всё узнал пока ты ехал
The shareholders sagged our layout and hired
акционеры просели наш расклад и наняли
his What the hell Yegor Enoch is the best
его Что за Чёрт Егор енох лучший
specialist in non-standard situations
специалист по нестандартным ситуациям
black anti-crisis manager so to speak
чёрный антикризисный менеджер так скажем
what the hell faked my mail It looks like
что э [__] подделала мою почту Похоже
Well, I'll ask about him at the market
что да я поспрашиваю про него на рынке
They say he will stop at nothing and
Говорят он ни перед чем не остановится и
he hasn't had any failures yet
неудач у него пока не было неудач не
it was a [ __ ]
было [__]
Hold on, listen, I flew to the Maldives there.
Держись Слушай я слетала на Мальдивы там
it's so cool there
так классно там такой
by Yes I am
по Да я
I don't need it now, I remember that you are there
сечас не надо я помню что тебя там
the shift is ending now
сейчас смена заканчивается
schedule let's go sit and have a drink
расписание пойдём посидим ку попьём
let's chat
поболтаем
please let's go I'm already doing something
пожалуйста пойдём я что-то вообще уже
I don't understand anything
ничего не понимаю
nothing, they are some kind of intrigue around me
ничего они вокруг меня какие-то интриги
SP yato time was happy
СП ято пора обрадовался
now I don't know who and what from
сейчас я я уже не знаю кто И чего от
I want the guys with whom I make films
меня хочет ребят с которыми я кино делаю
I feel like I let them all down and
Мне кажется я их я их подвёл всех и
talk to someone honestly like this
поговорить вот так вот с кем-то честно
I'm afraid I thought there Well, everything is up there
боюсь думал туда Ну всё наверху же там
everything should be
всё должно быть
ok, it's so brutal there Katya
хорошо там такая жесть Катя
You know, I am like this
такая знаешь я
I was happier when I was at our gas station
счастливей был когда на нашей заправке
worked oh come on Vla what are you talking about
работал да ну Вла ты что такое говоришь
what is this Impossible
чего это же Невозможное
I did it but none of us went there
сделал да никому из нас туда не
get there
попасть
I would never visit the Maldives in my life
я на Мальдивах бы в жизни не побывала
If it weren't for you, this would be nothing.
Если бы не ты это ерунда в ниче себе
nonsense No, well, what did you want? What did you think?
ерунда Не ну а ты как хотел Ты что думал
What
что
something really cool without
чтото вот по-настоящему такое крутое без
there are no difficulties
трудностей что ли бывает не
sometimes my brother is a fan of one
бывает меня брат фанат одного
the porn actor wanted a dick too 25
порноактёра захотел себе член тоже 25
smash the whole one class with a tied girko
сме весь один класс с привязанной гирко
from scales
от весов
passed by to
проходил чтобы от
just like you, I didn't tie it up, I didn't mean
вот как и ты не я не привязывал я не про
I mean that you are not afraid of difficulties
это я про то что ты трудности не боишься
for the sake of achieving great things
ради достижения больших
heights yes
высот да
yeah right And what kind of weight did he tie there?
да так А какую гирьку он там привязывал
well, just for fun
ну чисто ради интереса
Bye bye
Счастливо до
tomorrow Melnikova
завтра Мельникова
Maria, yes, pay off your [ __ ] car loan.
Мария да выплатил ваш сраный автокредит
I am very happy for you, you are being called
очень рад за вас Вас вызывают
Vladislav's leadership is with him today
руководство Владислав у него сегодня
day off other
выходной другое
manual come on in sit down
руководство проходи Садись
[music]
[музыка]
[ __ ] fidelis
фак фиделис
fidelis I didn't really understand the word but
фиделис я так особо не поняла но словоа
this does not bode well, this is Latin
хорошего не предвещает это латынь будь
faithful to the one who is faithful to you yes Mashenka Yes
верен тому кто верен тебе да Машенька Да
no maybe I don't know which one
нет может быть я не знаю какой
correct
правильный
option I read your personal file here
вариант Я почитал тут твоё личное дело
you work with us for 5 years already started with
ты работаешь У нас уже 5 лет начала с
from the very bottom on the set of programs now
самого низа на съёмках передач теперь
personal assistant boss good
личный ассистент босса хорошая
career You know who
карьера Ты знаешь кто
I am you a man in a [ __ ] expensive
я Вы мужик в охрененно дорогом
in the office it's a joke eh I just went to
кабинете это шутка э Просто я ходила на
They say I have a stand-up course
курс стендапа говорят у меня
unconventional feeling
нестандартное чувство
humor you Andrey Simonov one of three
юмора вы Андрей Симонов один из трёх
creators of tsv Media manager of the year I
создателей тсв Медиа менеджер года И
Chairman of the Board of Directors of the channel in
председатель совета директоров канала в
the next year and then the shareholders will be able to
ближайший год да потом акционеры смогут
change the composition of the council, including
менять состав совета в том числе и
I'm glad that unlike the others
меня Я рад что в отличие от остальных
participants of the process you are a girl
участников процесса ты девушка
smart How old are you
умная Сколько тебе лет
Mashenka, it's written there
Машенька так там же написано
27 written
27 написано
27 do you know Mashenka how much
27 знаешь Машенька сколько на
television commercial directors
телевидении коммерческих директоров
TV channels at the age of 27
телеканалов в возрасте 27
years
лет
no matter how much
сколько ни
one but this year the first one may appear
одного но в этом году может появи первый
Maria is the commercial director of the TV channel
Мария коммерческий директор телеканала
tsv yes yes you are driving me away no I am not you
тсв да да вы меня гоните не я тебя не
I'm driving, listen to me, girl, what do you want?
гоню слушай меня девочка что тебе надо
make a series bloody [ __ ] in the pit
делать сериал кровавые [__] в яме
must become the most gigantic failure
должен стать самым грандиозным провалом
modern television under the carpet by us
современного телевидения под ковёр нами
some people are trying to correct things through intrigue
интригами кое-кто пытается выправить
situation They all came You are the only one
ситуацию Все они пришли Ты единственный
our man
наш человек
there you have to make sure that no one
там ты должна проследить чтобы никто не
prevented that idiot Vlad from ruining
мешал этому идиоту Владу разваливать
channel and devalue the shares, that is, everything
канал и обесценивать акции то есть всё
it's true you hired him to fail
это правда вы наняли его для провала
naturally, he must implement it
естественно и он должен реализовать его
in full
в полном
[music]
[музыка]
volume remove any Noah new director
объёме убери любой Ной нового режиссёра
Bring back the idiot
Верни придурка
zmykha figure out why old fool
жмыха разберись почему старый дурак
Kiselev started writing normal scripts
Киселёв стал писать нормальные сценарии
and give Vlad a chance
и дай Владу возможность
wear as much chaos as possible [ __ ]
носить как можно больше хаоса трахать
actresses do Well everything he does
актрис делать Ну всё что он делает
ok and the main thing is to beware of this
хорошо и Главное остерегайся вот этого
person who is this enemy upon detection
человека кто это Враг при обнаружении
Report
Сообщай
what do I need
мне что
you say you have a [ __ ] awesome but
скажешь у вас охуенная а по
I feel sorry for Vlad, he may not be
делу мне жалко Влада он может быть не
very smart but a good person
очень умный но человек хороший
good-natured
беззлобный
Melnikova Maria Commercial Director
Мельникова Мария комерческий директор
TV channel
телеканала
[music]
[музыка]
tsv fak focus mon
тсв фак фокус Мон
ficus you said make sure they
фикус ты сказала Убедитесь что они
focused on the fig
сосредоточены на Фигово
tree again awl in the ass
дереве ещё раз Шила в жопе
this is a diagnosis this is an effect I need that
это диагноз это эффект Мне нужно чтобы
you gave such a drug for which
вы дали такой препарат от которого
a person will have an awl in his ass Thirst
человека будет шило В жопе Жажда
activities so that he would just run and
деятельности чтобы он просто бегал и
did and did and did and meldonium
делал и делал и делал и мельдония
sprinkle m well Maria what are you here
посыпьте м ну Мария то что вы тут
described it as a serious recipe for me
описали тянет на серьёзный рецепт Мне
just discharged
как раз выписали
if the friend doesn't laugh you turn on the sun you
если руг не смеётся ты включаю Солнце ты
I want him to have stars
Хочи ему звёзды это
just you fix the mistake by replacing
просто ты Исправь ошибку заменяя
smile all the sadness and tears it's just
улыбку все грустинки и слёзы это просто
and if suddenly you don't laugh or the sun doesn't laugh for him
и Если вдруг не смеётся ты чи ему солнце
you turn on the stars for him it's just you
ты включи ему звёзды это просто ты
Fix the fish by turning everything into a smile
Исправь рыбку превращая в улыбку все
dinky and tears it is
динки и слёзы это
I just feel like today will be the day
просто чувствую день сегодня будет
Just
просто
wonderful fortune teller no
прекрасный гадалки не
go come on come on faster faster faster
ходи Давай давай быстрей быстрей быстрее
go faster my dear faster top up pedal
езжай быстрей родной быстрей топи педа
then yes, if possible, give it 60, maybe 80
то Да придать если можно 60 можно 80
If possible, give me 80 hundred, it's not too much of a hassle
если можно 80 соточку не западло давай
Come on, Raz, drive straight through the parking lot.
давай Раз езжай прямо вон через парковку
through the parking lot now drive through
через парковку сейчас езжай через
parking Look at this six that's banging and
парковку Смотри какая шестёрка херачит и
g steam what parks look parks
джи пар какой паркуется смотри паркуется
what kind of G-steam parking I'm sick of these others
какой Джи пар парковки Заебали эти ещ
condoms walk from the room taking pictures of the area
гондоны ходят с номера фотографируют пло
take a picture of everyone woodpecker I am a woodpecker by the way
всех сфотографируй дятел Я кстати дятла
I saw it in the forest when I was a child
видел в детстве детстве в лесу очень
Beautiful
красивый
dyat is very handsome dyat is very handsome in
дят очень красивый дяд очень красивый в
forest in the village in the village village villages
лесу в деревне в деревне деревня деревни
now mocs are dying in Russia they are already dying
сейчас умирают в России моки умирают уже
30 years old die I already think no no
30 лет умирают Я уже думаю уже не не
there are none left at all
осталось их вовсе
I went to my uncle went went to
я дядя своему поехал поехал поехал к
uncle To uncle To all godfather godfather A
дяде К дяде К всем крёстному крёстному А
the drunks there are already all on Lacoste on lokos
там алкаши уже все на Лакост на локос
Uncle Kolya na na Fred peri ebosh ebosh
дяде Коля на на Фред пери ебоши ебоши
sorry, sorry, are you okay?
простите простите с вами всё в порядке
Remind me who
Напомни кто
You
ты
Hi, what's normal and great?
Привет что как нормально а здорово
cool glasses
классные очки
Hello
Привет
great Oh, great sneakers, well done, keep it up
здорово О шко кроссовки Молодец держи
Oops, let's get to work now.
Опа Сейчас поработаем
[ __ ]
[__]
and Svetik came with his own explanations
а пришёл скими объяснениями Светик
darling Or do we continue to love each other
дорогая Или мы продолжаем любить друг
friend or your heroine gets into an accident
друга или твоя героиня попадает в аварию
gets plastic surgery and gets
делает пластическую операцию и получает
brand new face so cute
совершенно Новое лицо такое милое
agreeable to the whole person
согласное на всё лицо
Arinochka Please delete this photo
Ариночка Удали пожалуйста эту фоточку
write that you have typed everything, otherwise I
напиши что ты всё набрала Иначе я
photoshop
прифотошопить
everything on the internet under the guise of home
всё в интернет под видом домашней
everyone will believe semochkin Masha
сёмочкин поверят все Маша
check
проконтролируйте
I've been waiting for this day and hour friends
я ждал этого дня и час друзья Мне
It seems our series has lost its former spark
кажется наш сериал утратил былую искру
the management was very unhappy with the first
руководство было очень недовольно первой
assembly that yes they said that the hall
сборкой что да сказали что зал
I personally applauded out of pity now
аплодировал из жалости сейчас я лично
I will control the process Masha
буду контролировать процесс Маша
text Oleg read
текст Олег читай
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Yeah, all my life I was afraid that the payback For
Угу всю жизнь Я боялся что расплаты За
made impossible to avoid I waited for this day and
сделанные не миновать я ждал этого дня и
hours but never thought I would have to
часа но никогда не думал что придётся
I ask you to give the most precious thing before the nonsense Where
отдать самое дорогое прошу пред чуш Где
drama where are the guys this movie actor
драматизм где ребята это кино актёр
should be like Don Leon in slave and
должен быть как Дон Леон в рабыне и
zauri burn well [ __ ] play like you
заури гореть ну [__] играй так как ты
played with ass in game of thrones just like that
играл с жопой в игре престолов прямо так
just like that
прямо вот так
[ __ ] all my life I was afraid that the retribution for
[__] всю жизнь Я боялся что расплаты За
not made
сделанные не
I waited for this day and hour to pass Yes I did
миновать я ждал этого дня и часа Да я
I never thought I'd have to give it back
никогда не думал что придётся отдавать
the most expensive
самое дорогое
this is real
это же настоящее
art
искусство
[music]
[музыка]
got me going, watch the next episode here
пробрало смотрите в следующей серии тут
I watched what another director filmed
посмотрел то что снял другой режиссёр ме
it won't work like that
так не получится Он
lost that there lost confidence in
утратил что там утратил уверенность в
he lost confidence in himself
себе уверенность себе он утратил надо
somehow restore his faith in himself there
как-то вернуть ему Веру в себя там
talk to say that without him we
поговорить сказать что без него мы
we won't take anything away that he's awesome
ничего не снимем что он потрясный
director and Well, I can't make this movie
режиссёр и Ну вот это кино мне не снять
a team of us Niku Dyshne Let's just
команда из нас Нику дышне Давайте просто
let's get drunk and
напьёмся и
everything is possible
всё може
Guys, I worked on the series before.
ребята ранее в сериале я работал
the gas station attendant burned the car they bought me from
заправщиком сжёг тачку меня купили от
cops and appointed head of the TV channel
ментов и назначили главой телеканала
because I'm funny Do any [ __ ] I
потому что я весёлые Твори любую херню Я
I want a series you hired him to fail
хочу сериал вы наняли его для провала
The [ __ ] went wild
Понеслась [__] по
bumps first assembly of one of the series that
кочкам первая сборка одной из серий что
it was a [ __ ] and people clapped the creature
это было [__] а люди хлопали [__]
Valera rewrites the script a little bit. I
Валера немножко переписывает сценарий Я
I want you to take this money and the director
хочу чтобы ты взял эти деньги а режиссёр
someone has discovered my plan and wants to tell me
это кто-то раскрыл мой план и хочет мне
The owners of everything sent me to interfere
помешать меня послали владельцы всего
you must follow this holiday
этого праздника ты должна проследить
so that no one interferes with this idiot Vlad
чтобы никто не мешал этому идиоту Владу
to destroy the channel and devalue the shares
разваливать канал и обесценивать акции
now we'll work [ __ ] remove any with
сейчас поработаем [__] убери любой с
me new director Bring back the idiot click
мной нового режиссёра Верни придурка жм
I need you to give me this drug.
Мне нужно чтобы вы дали такой препарат
from which a person will be an awl B
от которого человека будет шило В
standing on the ass
жопе стоящее
[music]
[музыка]
art what happened to me overdose
искусство что со мной было передозировка
meldonium mixed with caffeine and others
мельдония смешанная с кофеином и другими
drugs How from where Well Vladislav little
препаратами Как откуда Ну Владислав мало
Where do you eat all kinds of apples from?
ли Откуда вы едите всякое яблоки едите
on the channel at apples there is no meldonium well
на канале у яблоках Нет мельдония ну
How would you know, doctor, what this is?
вам-то откуда знать доктор что это за
apples in short Vladislav on happy
яблоки короче Владислав по счастливому
by coincidence we find ourselves in
стечению обстоятельств мы находимся в
the same hospital as our director
той же самой больнице что и наш режиссёр
cake
жмых
so without him we can't film a normal one
так без него нам не снять нормальный
series You must return it as soon as possible
сериал Вы должны его вернуть как можно
faster i why i because you are the center
быстрее я почему я потому что вы центр
our Universe you gathered us he you
нашей Вселенной вы нас собрали он вас
believes Well, we have another one and according to
верит Ну у нас же есть другой и согласно
the contract that I signed without looking at us
договору который Я подписал не глядя мы
we can't just fire you, I'll take care of it
не можем просто так уволить этим займусь
I and you do the cake Okay okay I
я а вы займитесь жмыхом Хорошо хорошо я
Oops, I have a dick colon. Side effect.
Опа у меня хер колон Побочный эффект
overdose Side effect Ah well
передозировки Побочный эффект А ну
It sticks out like a pin, but I can't do that
торчит как штырь мне же нельзя так
it's cool to walk Although doctor A you can
ходить прикольно Хотя доктор А вы можете
inject something to calm down
вколоть что-то для успокоения
Yes, it is dangerous. It contains many substances.
Да опасно В нём намешано много веществ
it will go away on its own in a few hours
само пройдёт через несколько часов
so in a few hours I'll be there
значит через несколько часов как я буду
go doctor i'm sure something
ходить доктор я уверена что-нибудь
we'll figure it out
придумаем
cover up
прикрыть
[music]
[музыка]
breadwinner sounds to a minimum so as not to
кормильца звуки на минимум чтобы не
interfere with these
мешать эти
clouds
облака
purple ma flowers with ice ours
фиолетовая ма цветов со льдом наших
glass
стакана
Hello How
привет Как
feeling so-so
самочувствие Так себе
this is yours
это у вас
that he worked part-time as a hospital clown
что подрабатывал больничным клоуном
entertained patients with a glass on his penis
развлекал пациентов стаканчиком на члене
Well, what kind of patients are these? Entertainment You
Ну какие пациенты такие Развлечения Ты
what sad Head hurts yes yes no I
что грустный Голова болит да да нет я
here I looked at what someone else filmed
тут посмотрел то что снял другой
director Me
режиссёр Мне
they brought it, I can't do it with him somehow
принесли я так не смогу у него как-то
it worked out I don't know
получилось Я не знаю
stop it, listen to one motivational one
перестань вот послушай одну мотивирующую
story from my life If I could pass
историю из моей жизни Если я смог пройти
such and you will be able to overcome yours
такое то и ты сможешь преодолеть свои
doubts at 5 years old i became an orphan i grew up
сомнения в 5 лет я остался сиротой Я рос
in the family of a grandfather who was lost
в семье деда который был пропащим
I often had to be a human being
человеком мне приходилось частенько быть
Bim sleep on the streets and eat on
Бим спать На улицах и питаться на
I couldn't bring it to my grandfather in the garbage dumps
помойках ня би я не мог принести деду
enough money reigned around me
достаточно денег вокруг меня царил
crime everywhere there were murders drugs
криминал повсюду были убийства наркотики
Oh my God, what a horror. I didn't know.
Господи какой ужас Я не знал
Yes, my first love was completely out of
Да моя первая любовь была совсем из
other
другого
Kruga girl from a rich family
Круга девушка из богатой
her parents couldn't afford her
семьи её родители не могли позволить ей
dating someone like me and at 18 years old I
встречаться с таким как я и в 18 лет мне
had to make the first tough choice in
пришлось сделать первый Суровый выбор в
I had to kill my life for her sake
жизни я вынужден был убить ради неё
What
что
Yes, it was promised.
Да она была обещана
another son of very influential people
другому сыну очень влиятельных людей
which she does not
которого она не
loved was very cruel and dangerous
любила был очень жестоким и опасным
I had to sneak in as a human at night
человеком мне пришлось ночью прокрасться
to his house and throw it in his bed
в его дом и подбросить ему в постель
cobra cobra Where did you get the cobra? [ __ ] it.
кобру кобру А где вы взяли кобру хуй его
knows where Well Igor Well somewhere got there on
знает где Ну Игорь Ну где-то взял там на
I went and bought some small corn for the bird
Птичке пошл купил корн маленького
grew up and then took
вымахал потом взял
after his death, my beloved and I
после его смерти мы с возлюбленной
fled the city
бежали из города
ran That is, it was in another city
бежали То есть это было в другом городе
and then you came back Of course we did
а потом вы вернулись Конечно мы
Igor returned
вернулись Игорь
Of course I came back with the right money
Конечно я вернулся с деньгами верными
the allies bribed the police and took away
союзниками подкупил полицию и отобрал
business already at the insidious father Wow And here
бизнес у е коварного отца Обалдеть И вот
now I am here before you as the king
теперь я здесь перед тобой король
new delhi sun varma
нью-дели Сан варма
what was missing
чего это недо было
Well, Yamal is the source of all this. Well, what kind of
Ну Ямал это исто из ше Да ну какая
story from my life are you stupid
история из моей жизни Ты что дурак
Is this really from an Indian movie?
совсем что ли Это из индийского фильма
Revenge through the years I wonder how it should be
Месть сквозь года Интересно как должно
this motivates me, listen, that's enough
это меня мотивировать жмых слушай хватит
brain sakme what is it in Tatar to [ __ ]
мозга сакме чего это по-татарски [__]
My grandmother from Kazan was my brains
Мозги у меня бабушка из Казани была
Get up We need to make a movie We don't have one
Вставай Нам надо снимать кино у нас нет
I don't have time after everything
времени нет я после того как всё
I looked at this, here I am, I lost it
посмотрел вот это вот я я потерял
I won't have self-confidence anymore
уверенность в себе я больше не буду
take it off we'll give it back to you
снимать ём её тебе вернём
no need not now Yes not right away
не надо не сейчас Да так сразу не
tell us we all need to get together
скажешь нам надо собраться всем
arrange an evening with the cast
актёрским составом устроить вечер
honoring the cake of Something That is necessary somehow
чествования жмых Чего Того надо как-то
give him back his faith in himself to talk about there
вернуть ему Веру в себя там поговорить
say that without him we won't be able to film anything
сказать что без него мы ничего не снимем
that he is an amazing director
что он потрясный режиссёр
Ire
Ире
I saw covid You said it yourself
ковиде видел Ты сам сказал что ты
put cat food on the directors and
выложил кошачий корм на режиссёров и
I chose moss because the cat ate it Yes
выбрал мха потому что кот с него поел Да
said puncture Well, in short, then it is necessary
говорил прокол Ну короче Тогда нужно
I don't know if I should lie, but you're a good person
что-то соврать не знаю ну ты же хорошая
actress, you know how to lie
актриса ты же умеешь врать
Oh well, I'm after the others.
Да ладно я за остальными
get ready Victor how are you today
собирайся Виктор Как вы сегодня
cool shirt
классная рубашка
Thank you. It really highlights yours.
Спасибо Она так подчёркивает вашу
masculinity you know in our world of cinema
мужественность знаете в нашем мире кино
real men
настоящие мужчины
rarity What do you want I'm tired of
редкость Что ты хочешь Я устала от
I want to work here When will you finish?
работы здесь хочу Когда вы закончите
continue to work with you on the present
дальше работать с вами на настоящем
cinema and you are probably tired
кино и Вы наверно устали
Let's say this evening
Допустим сегодня вечером у
me here
меня вот
address Arinochka I deleted everything you are great
адрес Ариночка Я всё удалила вы молодец
But that's not what we're talking about now. You still have a long time left.
Но речь сейчас не об этом Тебе долго ещё
one SN Yes, well then after that
одна СН Да хорошо после этого тогда
Get ready and let's go to the bar to drink and
Собирайся и пойдём в бар пить и
tell a fly how we all can't do without him
рассказывать муху как мы все без него не
we can do this why then so that there is work
можем это зачем Затем чтобы была работа
and salary that's why it's reasonable so And where
и зарплата вот зачем резонно так А где
this is our ass star at Oleg's
этот наша жопная звезда у у Олега
today is a day off, damn, okay, I'll do it later
сегодня выходной блин ладно я его Потом
I'll find you be low
найду будьте на низком
at the start maybe
старте может
Let's kiss
Поцелуемся
no al Oleg hi this is Vladislav I am
нет ал Олег привет Это Владислав я Я
I know you have a day off today but I have to
знаю что у тебя сегодня выходной но надо
urgently
срочно
see each other Well tell me where What Where am I
увидеться Ну ты скажи где Чего Куда я
I'll come by, I need to explain something to you
подъеду мне надо объяснить тебе кое-что
yes I'm in the parking lot yes A De
да я я на паркинге да А Де
198 Yes, you are on, and I see here is a car, you are on
198 Да ты на а вижу вот машину ты на
taxi yes And listen there is no one in the taxi yes
такси да А слушай в такси никого нету да
No, I'm here.
Нет я здесь а
and I just said that I was taking a taxi, I thought, eh
а просто сказал что на такси я подумал э
Yes I know what you thought please
Да я знаю что вы подумали пожалуйста
don't tell anyone No Why
никому не говорите Нет А почему
a cup is yes it is not a cap it is
стаканчик это да это не не колпачок это
you know when they put it on the handle
знаешь на ручку когда надевают чтобы
the ink didn't leak from you're a taxi driver Well yeah
чернила не вытекали от ты таксуешь Ну да
money is needed as you get it per day
деньги нужны как ту ты получаешь в день
you starred in game of thrones for many thousands
много тысяч ты в игре престолов снимался
How much do you know in Hollywood?
как знаете сколько в Голливуде стоит
How long should I show my ass on the screen?
жопой на экране посветить сколько на
I don't even have enough money to rent a room, so I
аренду комнаты даже не хватает вот я и
I came back here and they wouldn't hire me to act in a movie
вернулся сюда кино сниматься не брали
because I speak poorly and the text is not
потому что я плохо говорю и текст не
I remember I got a job as a taxi driver. And when I came to you
помню устроился такси А когда к вам
I was called from this job and did not quit
позвали с это работы увольняться не стал
Who knows, there are probably more of me
Мало ли что скорее всего меня больше
You won't get a movie
кино ты не возьмут
to be filmed
сниматься
[ __ ] So it turns out you're just as ordinary
бля Так ты оказывается такой же обычный
man How are we in the sense Well in the sense of that
человек Как мы в смысле Ну в смысле того
that you also don't just like some people well
что тебе также не просто какы людям ну
how well how are we how Well yes and what's in this
как ну как мы как Ну да а что в этом
strange actor is the same profession as
странного актёр такая же профессия как
a taxi driver for example or a gas station attendant Well, yes A
таксист например или заправщик Ну да А
What did you want there? And I wanted Well, listen.
Вы что хотели там А я хотел Ну слушай
there I need to drink it with some cake and
там надо со жмыхом подбухну как-то и
convince him
убедить его
come back yes no problem seriously yes
вернуться да не проблема серьёзно Да
far away Thank you right here and do you remember
далек Спасибо прямо вот а ты помнишь
the day we shook hands
день когда мы пожали друг другу руге у
I was also there Ice cream Yeah, funny
меня ещё там Мороженое было Ага смешно
It wasn't ice cream, what was it?
Это было не мороженое а что
I just decided that now is the time
Я просто решил что сейчас такой ну
the right moment to be honest
подходящий момент чтобы честно всё
tell Why the hell was it necessary at all
рассказать А нахрена надо было вообще
[music]
[музыка]
tell openly
рассказывать открыто
oh romance Mash and where are you I'm waiting in the bedroom
о романтика Маш а ты где Я в спальне жду
I love you straight to the point
тебя что прям сразу к делу люблю
practical It's good to be
практичных Хорошо быть
director guys watch some
режиссёром ребята вот смотрите каких-то
some months
нехто месяцев
we would
ми бы
stop it
ча перестань
please and smile at all of us
пожалуйста и нам всем с вами улыбнулась
luck
удача
smile this is how to look how
улыбнись это как посмотреть как
look Yes You have the main role in
посмотреть Да У тебя главная роль во
flagship series I don't suck like
флагманском сериале Я за не сосу как
German police buddy so then and
немецкий полис дружок так потом и
looks good This is your model of success
выглядит уда Это же твоя модель успеха
you know he is
ся знаеш он быть
sympathy left our team he
симпати выбыл из нашего коллектива он
lost that there lost confidence in
утратил что там утратил уверенность в
He lost his self-confidence. He lost Rina.
себе уверенность в себе Он утратил Рина
tell me what you value in working with
скажи что ты ценишь в работе с
Igor
Игорем
Oh well, I don't really have anything to compare it to.
Ой ну мне вообще особо не с чем сравнить
but but when I was filming a commercial for con
но но когда я снималась в рекламе кон
Greni the director didn't know me at all
грени режиссёр вообще не знал как меня
name is A Igor, I know, but you haven't seen anything else
зовут А Игорь зна а ты больше нигде не
played Hello I'm in the theater I'm Snow
играла Здраствуйте Я же в театре я Снеж
ah yes yes yes penzin we remember we remember Sveta
а да дада да пензин вспомним помним Свет
Why do you always offend her like that?
ну зачем ты всё время её обижаешь как
as if I myself had played in so many places. I though
будто сама так много где играла Я хотя
I wish the idea would not shine instead of others and
бы задум не светила вместо других и у
By the way, I had an episode with Moshko Well
меня между прочим был эпизод с мошко Ну
no well now well really well where are we
нет ну сейчас ну правда ну гдето мы
gathered here today to talk
собрались здесь сегодня чтобы поговорить
about Igor No need about me
об Игоре Да не надо обо мне
it's clear that it's a movie to me
разговаривать и так понятно что кино мне
we can't take off the team, we're a lousy team
не снять команда из нас никудышная
Let's just get drunk and that's it
Давайте просто напьёмся и всё
Wow, that was of course, yes, you Masha
Ого ну это было конечно да ты Маша
Certainly
конечно
super and I'm glad you liked it
супер и я рада что вам понравилось
what's going on here? What are you doing, swinging?
что тут происходит А вы что свиинг что
are there any
ли какие-то
And thanks to Lera, everything was fine
А спасибо Лера всё было на
Are you stupid or what do you want records? You're a boy
записи ты что дура что ли хочешь ты бойд
Do you want to blackmail me? Show Zhenya
меня шантажировать хочешь Жене показать
no questions asked, I can do it myself
без вопросов я и сам
I can We have an open relationship and
могу У нас ней свободные отношения а
Better on the internet
лучше в интернет
post it will be
размести это будет
bomb no no don't care Yeah, what
бомба нене по барабан Да ну какой
Internet cops will be enough
интернет ментовки будет достаточно
Are you 15 or something? Yes, 15, and you are 10.
тебе что 15 лет что ли Да 15 А вам 10
they will give it to you, but when you leave you will be able to take it off
дадут при этом по выходу сможете снять
great gay drama So I pushed
отличную гей драму Так что я продвинул
you to
вас к
Oscar, how much money do you want me to give you?
Оскару сколько ты хочешь мне деньги не
voluntary termination of the contract is required
нужны добровольно расторжение договора
We won't fire you ourselves.
Сами мы вас уволить не
we can do that what are you
можем так ты что
offered me
предложила мне
fifteen year old
пятнадцатилетняя
Are you sick or something, uncle? Well, sign it.
Ты что больная что ли дядь Ну подпиши
papers You don't want 10 years
бумажки Ты же не хочешь 10 лет
crow
кукарекать
crowing Valeria hints that you
кукарекать Валерия намекает что вы
you will become
станете
[ __ ] [ __ ] you're all crazy in this
петухом Бля вы все ненормальные в этой
There are sick people in the country
стране люди больные
you see, I will definitely go to America
понимаете обязательно уеду в Америку я
Just
просто
wanted to help you do something
хотел помочь вам сделать что-то
decent from your [ __ ] series
приличное из вашего [__] сериала
teach you how to work somehow and you even
научить как-то работать вас а вы даже
everything is here
здесь всё
[ __ ] on me Cool, I'm telling you already
обосрали Прикольно да говорю уже
ok so that's what you need it for
нормально так вот для чего Вам нужна
was my photo real Yes no
была моя фотка настоящий Да нет
props made How old are you
реквизитор сделали Сколько тебе лет
really
реально
Damn, why the hell are you a prostitute, come to us
блин нафиг ты [__] чаш иди к нам в
actresses You have talent x I won't think about it
актрисы У тебя же талант х Я подумаю не
I can understand how you married her. She
могу понять н как ты на ней женился Она
as terrible as my life he says
же страшная как жизнь моя он говорит
the second one says it's all nonsense. But here's
второй говорит это всё ерунда Зато вот
these are the worms
такие глисты вот такие
But you're not a Fisherman.
А ты же не Рыбак
so okay, I understand that now it's mine
так ну ладно я так понимаю теперь моя
turn to tell Well in
очередь рассказывать Ну в
in general, my father is the same
общем отец у меня тоже
the director filmed all sorts of things there
режиссёр снимал там всякое там
Chairman
председатель
2 there is no one for sausages
2 нет никого на сосиски не
watched The Return of the Tushino Rose
смотрели а Возвращение Тушинской розочки
Oh, I saw that. Yes, seriously.
О это я видел А да серьёзно
in Hollywood film school they show us
в голливудской киношколе нам показывают
this movie is about how to play
этот фильм на предмет того как играть
no, yeah, that's not the point
нельзя Ага ну не суть в
In general, my dad has been filming since the Soviet Union
общем батя у меня с самого Совка снимал
he actually got me settled in
он меня собственно пристроил а
I had a classmate Petya boo who is this
однокурсник у меня был Петя бу кто это
the director Boomer filmed Boomer He filmed He
режиссёр же Бумер снял Бумер Он снял Он
I killed three women in my course
у меня на курсе трёх баб убил трёх
you see, no one looks at me at all
понимаете никто вообще на меня не
I looked only at him and then at him again
смотрел только на него вот а потом ещ на
gave me a drink at an institute event
институтском мероприятии дал мне выпить
loosen up so that I am in front of the master
слабите так что я на глазах у мастера
the dean [ __ ] himself in the courses, and not in
курсах декан обосрался причём Ну не в
creative In direct
творческом В прямом
I mean wait Buslov got you drunk
смысле погоди буслов напоил тебя
laxative Why how how well like this
слабительном Зачем как как ну вот так
that's how it happened, I mixed it up for him and came up to him
вот так вышло я ему подмешал подошёл
like with toast and then got it mixed up myself
типа с тостом а потом сам перепутал
glass and
стакан и
I drank, well, in short, that's how it is guys
выпил ну короче ну вот так вот ребята со
this is always how it happens to me
мной всегда вот так вот происходит
you understand and then I quote thermo
понимаете и вот тогда я цитировать термо
I confessed from my pants that I would [ __ ] him that
со штанов я покаялся что я въебу его что
The whole world of cinema will hear the name Zhmykh
фамилию жмых услышит весь Киномир весь
you understand and in general it's simple
понимаете и вообще просто
world and for now I'm only 15 years old
мир а пока что я 15 лет только
I'm [ __ ] on you Ilyusha, forgive me And why do we need this?
обсираю Илюша прости А ты зачем нам это
I told you everything Well, how? Well, we did.
всё рассказал Ну как Ну мы же
we tell our true stories
рассказываем свои правдивой истории
life is out of order about his ex-wife
жизни вон лад про свою бывшую жену
told This is actually
рассказал Это вообще-то
Here's a joke again
анекдот вот опять ну
varli quiet quiet quiet oh no need to cry
варли тихо тихо тихо о не надо плакать
don't offend this
не обижайте это
Big deal, it's a problem. You're all just [ __ ] on it.
подумаешь проблемка Да все вы обсирать
anyway, well you know what mine was like
так или иначе ну знаете какой у меня был
text In the episode with Mashkov
текст В эпизоде с машковым
Hello Hello one shitty
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте одно сраное
one word I was just his neighbor
слово одно я просто была его соседка по
I just couldn't get through the entrance and it took me a whole
подъезду просто не прошла а мне за целый
bare ass day in game of thrones
день с голой жопой в игре престолов
paid only 200
заплатили всего 200
They pay you a lot more dollars here
долларов тебе здесь платят гораздо
more and I 2 months ago
больше а я 2 месяца назад
at the gas station Sorry hose fight for
на заправке Извините шланг боем за
little things like that
мелочи вот так
here is the third column before
вот п третья колоночки до
[music]
[музыка]
[laughter]
[смех]
full Thank you very much for your support But
полного Спасибо большое за поддержку Но
it's of course funny that you're on
это конечно смешно что вы на
gas station awesome i remembered where i was
заправке [__] я вспомнила где я вас
I saw a gas station on Svoboda Street
видела заправка на улице Свободы с
exit roll yes
выездом накат да
no What yes
нет Что да
OK
ладно
Holy [ __ ], that's awesome
[__] ой зачёт
[music]
[музыка]
no need, oh oh
на ой ой не надо
what to say Slav I beg you no need
что сказать Слав Я вас прошу не надо у
I only have a skull
меня только череп
stros let's start with the fact that you are a [ __ ] eyes
строс начнём с того что ты пиздо глазы
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[ __ ] What can we help with?
мудила Что поможем
[music]
[музыка]
Hi, I know that you are now on your own.
Привет А я знаю что вы теперь сами
send the script to the channel Just me
отправляете сценарий на канал Просто я
I was nearby and decided to stop by
была здесь рядом решила Заехать по
friendship can have tea of course of course
дружбе можно чаю конечно конечно
Mashenka, come in
Машенька заходи
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
of course it's a cool figurine
конечно классная фигурка
under number one it says there
под номером один там написано
collectible made of stone there were such
коллекционный сделан из камня таких было
Only 100 of these were produced
выпущено всего 100 этот
first
первый
cool Valera, what's the deal with the World Cup scenario?
кайф Валер а в чём дело в ЧМ сценарии
changed Plus you said that never
изменились Плюс вы говорили что никогда
didn't work on the computer and then suddenly
не работали на компьютере а т резко
learned Well, yes, so what?
научились Ну да а что
Show me this
такое Покажите
me Well, print at least a page and I
мне Ну напечатайте хотя бы страничку а я
I'll time it, I want to understand how you are
время засеку хочу понять как вы
You still have time to write half an episode a day
успеваете По пол серии в день писать ещё
and rewrite the old one
и старый переписывать
she had to pay for the car
ей надо было за машину выплачивать за
apartment
квартиру
you have to pay to live on something for now
платить жить на что-то надо пока с
I can't get a job and I have nothing
работы не устроиться А у меня уж ничего
there is nothing left I'm still her stop I don't have anything
не осталось я же всё ей стоп Я ничего не
I understand To whom
понимаю Кому
to her
ей
Natasha
Наташа
my daughters, I had no choice, they
дочки ше у меня выбора не было они
lots of logos
много лого
Sali myself I thought Lord anyway
Сали сами я подумал Господи всё равно в
my life will all fall apart as usual and
жизни моей всё развалится как обычно и
our project won't live long and
проекту нашему долго не жить так и
got something out of it well we always do
что-то получил с этого ну мы всегда же
something incomprehensible was filmed there before
что-то там до снимали туда непонятного
Well, I thought, God, what difference does it make?
Ну я подумал Господи ну какая разница
thought quietly quietly Valery Calm down then
подумал тихо тихо Валер Успокойтесь то
there are these new scenarios here are the new ones
есть вот эти новые сценарии вот новые
they didn't write
писали не
someone paid you not to
вы кто-то вам заплатил за то чтобы вы не
wrote and all the money you earn
писали и все деньги что вы зарабатываете
you give away
вы отдаёте
daughters and not this person by chance to you
дочери а не этот человек случайно вам
paid Yes who
платил Да кто
he doesn't care car please yes go
он неважно машинка пожалуйста Да ехать
I'll work till the end please I have
до конца до работаю пожалуйста Я у меня
there is simply no way out, that's the situation
просто выхода нету ну такая ситуация
life please I will fight to the end and
жизненная пожалуйста Я добою до конца и
All
всё
please old gang yes yes and you know
пожалуйста старой бандой да да И знаете
T such a father as you mine That's about me
Т такого отца как вы мой Вот про меня
remembers only when he borrows money
вспоминает только когда денег в долг
ask
попросить
Oh my God, what is this? This is Vladislav
надо Господи что это это Владислав
for some reason I recorded my burp and sent it
зачем-то записал свою отрыжку и отправил
I have audio messages, I set this sound
мне аудиосообщения я поставил этот звук
I'm sorry I need to
на него Извините мне надо
read what
прочитать что
happened to us
случилось нас
closed closed Yes, not all of Vlad
закрыли закрыли Да не всех Влада
they tied everyone up for the fight along with him
повязали за драку вместе с ним всех
actors, let's go, we need to rescue them tomorrow
актёров поехали надо выручать завтра
change in
смена в
de Sveta well how are you anyway
де Света ну ты вообще как ты Как
kick in the balls
тыт по яйцам
Oleg is like Hollywood in a jump
прям Олег вообще Голливуд в прыжке
acoustics
акустика
I thought you were a white collar worker now
Я думал вы Белый воротничок сечас те
collar
воротничок
When you were young, you know how it is with rappers
По молодости знаешь как вон с реперами
At Strelka there was just rap crap and
на Стрелке ходили вообще ну реп кал и
all that stuff was just a way and that's all we have
всё такое месили только путь и жх у нас
Young people, what am I? It's good that I didn't get hit on the head
Молоде что я Это хорошо что по башке не
they knocked again Sveta I just
настучали опять Света я просто в
shocked Orekhova Borisova South
шоке Орехова Борисова Южная
By the time you get home by metro there are these
пока в метро до дома дойдёшь там такие
Adventures happen So Igor
Приключения случаются Так что Игорь
can you have me in strut scenes
можешь меня в струковых сценах
use
использовать
easy guys guys thank you very much
легко ребята ребята Спасибо вам большое
you stood up for me no one stood up for me
вы заступились за меня за меня никто
he never stood up for me or my friends
никогда не заступался у меня и друзей-то
no Arina what are you what do you think I
нет Арина ты что ты что думаешь я
I'll let some [ __ ] [ __ ] you
позволю какому-то хрену тебя за жопу
Only I can paw this place no no
лапать только я могу это де то нет не
you can do it well I can't you see you see
можете хорошо не могу вот видишь видишь
gang we are all a gang
банда мы все банда
Guys, what are you talking about? Well, will you watch a movie?
ребята ну что ты Ну будешь киношку ты
You'll be filming for us, otherwise Svetka will do it for you
нам снимать будеш а то Светка тебе
your red mullets then I will be I will be
барабульки твои Всё тогда буду буду
[music]
[музыка]
Are you all blocked? Girl, are you
вы все что ли перекрыты Девушка Вы по
what question do you know these hooligans
какому вопросу знаете этих хулиганов
Comrade policeman it happened
товарищ полицейский произошло
the misunderstanding is that the cinema workers have them
недоразумение это работники кино у них
tomorrow is the shift, they need to be released
завтра смена нужно чтобы их отпустили
No, what are you talking about, they can't do that
нет что вы реч быть не может они такого
they made three men and kneaded them into dough
натворили трёх мужиков замесили в тесто
just spelt
просто полба
I smashed it
разнесли я
we can somehow come to an agreement in person
компе е сможем как-то договориться лично
and I'll take all the damage you what What is it
и я возу весь ущерб вы что Что такое
tell me you MTI Why are you offering a bribe
говорить вы МТИ Поче взятку предлагаете
Yes, calm the girls down, they are sitting here
Да девуш успокойте сидеть они здесь
will be at best until tomorrow
будут в лучшем случае до завтрашнего
morning and at worst Mashenka Are you sure that
утра а в худшем Машенька Ты уверена что
you could just park there
там можно было парковаться просто там
sign guys oh my god it's the same
знак ребята Господи это же
va and
ва и
his cat coconut I grew up on it I
его кота кокоса я ж я же вырос на нём я
I show this to my children too, this is Coconut
я и детям своим показываю это ж Кокос
A cheerful cat, everyone knows that, he will get rid of
Весёлый кот это знают все он избавит от
illness of adults and children
забол взрослых и детей
[music]
[музыка]
[laughter]
[смех]
y So that's it
й Значит так
uh a joint photo and you can take it
ээ совместное фото и можете забирать
everyone right now
всех прямо сейчас
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
watch the next episode if we
смотрите в следующей серии если мы
we are filming lo
снимаем ло
we are filming well, they are firing us, I have no way out
снимаем хоро нас увольняют я-то выхода
I don't see that we have to take off Magnificent for now
не вижу нам остатся снять Великолеп пока
Vlad is at the helm, the series can't be saved in any way
у руля Влад сериал не спасти никак начи
I don't need to make a movie, I ask you not to
меня кино делать не надо я вас прошу не
We don't need to fix anything, we'll just do it
надо ничего исправлять мы сделаем только
hu with the dismissal of Victor the editing returned
ху с увольнением Виктора монтаж вернулся
the conveyor belt can be in your hands again
в твои руки конвейер может снова
earn money on an industrial scale
заработать уже в промышленных масштабах
Valera, if we start filming like this
Валера если мы начнём до снимать так
Nobody knows much new about the World Cup
много нового о ЧМ не знает никто и
Pasting this into the series could be it
вклеивать это в сериал это же может его
spoil
испортить
earlier in the series And I 2 months ago on
ранее в сериале А я 2 месяца назад на
refueling
заправке
I was going to be Who I am as the CEO
шла Кем Кем я генеральным директором
tsv channel Do any crap you want
телеканала тсв Твори любую херню вы
hired him to fail I want a series
наняли его для провала Я хочу сериал
Team
Команда
The [ __ ] went wild
Понеслась [__] по
My name is Egor and I was sent
кочкам Меня зовут Егор и меня послали
the owners of this whole holiday for
владельцы всего этого праздника для
there will be a full audience
зрителей это будет полный
knockout
нокаут
oooh I want you to take this money who
уу Я хочу чтобы ты взял эти деньги кто
you were paid not to write and
вам заплатил за то чтобы вы не писали и
You give away all the money
все деньги Вы отдаёте
daughter, you must make sure that no one
дочери ты должна проследить чтобы никто
didn't stop that idiot Vlad from ruining it
не мешал этому идиоту Владу разваливать
channel and devalue shares series
канал и обесценивать акции сериал
bloody [ __ ] in the pit should be the most
кровавые [__] в яме должен стать самым
a grand failure of modern
грандиозным провалом современного
television what unites us
телевидения что нас объединяет
friends we are all Russians no at all he is a pomace
друзья мы все русские Вовсе нет жмых он
Jew Yes with What is this suddenly I am Russian yes Ir
еврей Да с Что это вдруг я русский да Ир
listen please look at yourself
слушай пожалуйста вон посмотри на себя в
mirror you only have side curls, you're [ __ ] nuts
зеркало тебе только пейсы прихуел
I think I know Yes, we will all go today
Кажется знаю Да мы все Сегодня поедем
hang out No, we all ended up on this
тусить Да нет мы все оказались на этой
work by chance and here's nothing I'm doing yet
работе случайно а вот и ни хрена я ещё
I worked here before you and it was great
до вас здесь работала и прекрасно
it worked correctly too but you will fly out
работала тоже верно но вылетишь ты
together with us with all of us if anything well we still
вместе с нами со всеми если что ну мы ещ
let's see then look what
посмотрим значит смотрите что
it turns out this jerk
получается вот этот ушлёпок
pretending to be our friend hired us to
притворяясь нашим другом нанял нас чтобы
we filmed some blatant crap here
мы с вами сняли откровенное гомно вот
if this happens then goodbye goodbye
если это случится значит Прощай Прощай
high earnings Sweet life and us
высокие заработки Сладкая жизнь и нас
let's get it from the other side
поиме с другой стороны
there is a second jerk who represents
есть второй ушлёпок который представляет
the interests of shareholders he wants us to
интересы акционеров он хочет чтобы мы
they made a normal series and then he went nuts
сняли нормальный сериал и тогда он помет
Ivo Usha
Иво ушка
what are you carrying How how are you carrying them
какой ты несёшь Как как ты их
are you going to leave? If anything, I once
собираешься валить Если что я один раз
Killer may have played
Киллера играл может
help if we shoot badly
помочь если мы снимаем плохо нас
they fire us we shoot well we are fired I
увольняют снимаем хорошо нас увольняют я
I don't see a way out, quit yourself Yes
что-то выхода не вижу уволься самим Да
the beauty has already had the system no no no
уж красотка поимела систему нет нет нет
no no no no no you you don't think
нет нет нет нет нет вы вы мыслите не
look wide if we can't take off
широко смотрите если мы не можем снять
good and we can't take it off bad for us
хорошо и не можем снять плохо нам
all that remains is to take off your pants
остаётся снять штаны
we just have to take it off
нам остаётся снять
great then this one won't fire us either
великолепно тогда и этот нас не уволит и
this one won't be able to And even if we can
этот не сможет А даже если сможет мы
we will be so cool with you guys that
будем с вами ребята настолько круты что
any TV channel will snatch us up
нас с руками оторвёт любой телеканал Я
I can even see how RNF is standing below
даже вижу как рнф внизу стоит с
by agreement like this near the TV center
договором вот так возле Телецентра
Ostankina is like this, that is all that we have
останкина вот так то есть всё что нам
We need to make a super hit of this Well, that's all
нужно это снять суперхит Ну да всего-то
Vladislav but I can still help you a million
Владислав но я вам могу ещё помочь ляма
100 dollars to raise Amu Doha te
100 долларов поднять Аму Доха те
heavyweight champion on the market and all the money
чемпиона супертяжи на ринке и всё бабки
yours If you need to, you will need to wash it off
ваши Если нужно будет отмухув
[music]
[музыка]
anything other than this book Well
что-нибудь кроме этой книги Ну
please, why are you starting again? Well
пожалуйста ну что ты начинаешь опять Ну
I'm trying to light you up, it says here that
я пытаюсь вас зажечь здесь написано что
you need to burn you need to do about the most
нужно гореть нужно делать о самом
turn the soul inside out in secret
сокровенном душу наизнанку выворачивать
Well, you all have them.
Ну у вас же у всех есть
soul Well except
душа Ну кроме
[music]
[музыка]
chicken teach me cake of life Yes what
куринка Научи меня жмых жизни Да какой
life toadstool you from the clearing of life I you
жизни поганка ты с полянки жизни я тебя
I'll teach you myself, teach me by wearing it
Сам научу научи меня нося
Well, the teaching of Light is not the teaching of darkness
Ну чение Света не учение тьма
do you know what it means in this context
знаешь что это значит в данном контексте
what you're [ __ ] with is what it means
то что ты [__] вот что это значит в
in this context Well teach me how to make movies
данном контексте Ну учи меня кино делать
Well, you studied there at VGIK, didn't you?
Ну ты же учился там в ВГИК своём так
You've been teaching me for 5 years, so what if I go there?
меня 5 лет учи ну и что я ту пойду можно
I'm sure I can tell you how it is in half an hour
за полчаса рассказать я уверен Как там
to make people watch us
сделать то чтобы люди нас смотрели он
He watches this nonsense on NTV Tavs Yes
смотрит же на НТВ эту пургу тавс Да
he watches because this is the most detective
смотрит потому что это детектив самый
an easy way to keep our attention
простой способ удержать внимание у нас
I'm not a detective anymore, you know, it's too late. Well
уже не детектив понимаете уже поздно Ну
ok okay And these gray-haired students on
хорошо ладно А эти вот седые студенты на
TNT gray students on TNT - This is Vlad
ТНТ седые студенты на ТНТ - Это Влад
comedy is funny Well, or should be
комедия это смешно Ну или должно быть
funny, we don't care about these options
смешно неважно нам эти варианты не
we have a melodrama that suits us Yes with
подходят у нас мелодрамма Да с
elements of fantasy but melodrama in
элементами фантастики но мелодрамма в
melodrama is interested in something completely different
мелодраме важно совершенно другое вот
here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go
вот вот вот пошёл разговор пошёл пошёл
went went what what we should
пошёл пошёл какое какое такое мы должны
to touch the nerve of the common people
задеть нерв простого народа простого
the viewer that is the heroes the hero must be
зрителя то есть герои герой должен быть
exactly the same as them Okay then
точно такой же как и они Хорошо тогда
what are we doing wrong Well, here you are
что мы делаем не так Ну вот вот вы
common man Let's say Well, now
простой человек Допустим Ну а теперь
Look at yourself and at Oleg who
Посмотрите на себя и на Олега который
he plays our main character very much
играет у нас главного героя он очень
looks like a common man You often
похож на простого человека Вы часто
You see nine of these in the entrances
таких Вот видите в подъездах девяти
floors Well, Alec actually starred in the game
этажах Ну Алек вообще-то снимался в игре
Thrones so for a second he duplicated there
престолов так на секу он там дублировал
ass that's one and secondly even if
жопу это раз а во-вторых если бы даже и
no Game of Thrones is not a melodrama it is
нет Игра престолов это не мелодрамма это
we secretly need to fix this No need
же мых тайно это надо исправить Не надо
I ask you not to fix anything
я вас прошу не надо ничего исправлять мы
we'll only make it worse for you
сделаем только хуже я вас
please Free cheese only happens in
прошу Бесплатный сыр бывает только в
mousetrap yes
мышеловке да
Renault at Valera's
Рено у Валеры
trouble he took other people's money a lot
неприятность он взял чужие деньги много
money for the fact that he himself will not write
денег за то что он сам не будет писать
scenarios if he starts this again now
сценарии если сейчас он снова начнёт это
there may be problems but it
делать могут возникнуть проблемы Но его
they won't take you to the forest like in
же не будут возить в лес как в
nineties first of all many others
девяностых во-первых много других
methods and secondly it is not a fact Thank you
способов а во-вторых не факт Спасибо
Masha
Маше
Save not Here are the names for this
Спаси не Воте имен для этом
How much was there?
Сколько было
five bucks
бабла пять
Wow, five pieces of greenery didn't come that fast.
Ого ну пять штук зелени так быстро не
collect how much is it in rubles is it in
насобирать сколько это в рублях это в
rubles
рублях
millions are you serious
миллионов вы вы серьёзно
Valera, you asked for plyamov where and what
Валера ты проса п лямов куда ш каких
I need to order women and that's it
надо заказывать баб и что с ни дела
Okay, he's good, it's none of our business where he goes
Ладно хорош не наше дело куда он
spent it but how is it not ours anymore
потратил да как это не наше мне уже
I myself am interested in where he asked them though
самому интересно куда он их проса хотя
well cat Coconut I see, enough Vasya, well, well
ну кот Кокос Понятно хватит Вася ну ну
I have enough of this
хватит мне и так
I felt awkward when I gave them to my daughter, that's how I am
неловко я их дочери отдал вот такой я
old fool Well, I'm happy
старый дурачок Ну доволен
ok Well, sorry about that
нормально Ну это извини
what am I
что я
let's just rob a bank I'd just like to
просто ограбим банк хотелось бы только
this will turn out even worse for us than
это выйдет у нас ещ хуже чем
Cinema While the proven method is only
кино Пока проверенный способ забо только
one shoots idiots for money in
один снимать идиотов за деньги в
additional line namely A because
дополнительной линии именно А поскольку
With Victor's dismissal, editing returned to
с увольнением Виктора монтаж вернулся в
your hands conveyor can again
твои руки конвейер может снова
earn money on an industrial scale
заработать уже в промышленных масштабах
Valera I'm terribly sorry I'm very touched
Валера Я дико извиняюсь Я очень тронут
that you want to help me and are ready
что вы хотите мне помочь и готовы
do all this but if we start before
сделать всё это но если мы начнём до
shoot so many new things that he doesn't know about
снимать так много нового о чём не знает
nobody and pasting it into the series is the same
никто и вклеивать это в сериал это же
can ruin it
может его испортить
at snim suhi
ат снима сухи
Valera will succeed honestly you are true
получится Валера честно Вы правда
do you think that if we don't do this
думаете что если мы этого делать не
the series will suddenly become super
будем сериал вдруг станет супер
[music]
[музыка]
I'm cool, I'm naive while Vlad is at the helm, series
крутым я наивный пока у руля Влад сериал
there is no way to save it Let's try to save it
не спасти никак Давайте попробуем спасти
at least
хотя бы
you A is there anything to roll pipes are burning
вас А есть что накатить трубы горят
where did you bring us you said it will be
го куда нас привёл ты сказал будет
it was fun and important the last time was
весело при этом важно последний раз было
fun and important when i graduate with mushrooms
весело и важно когда я диплом грибочками
received no here it's different important important
получала нет тут по-другому важно важно
for our series we must learn
для нашего сериала Мы должны научиться
turn one's soul inside out
выворачивать душу
inside out Hello Hello
наизнанку Здравствуйте Здраствуйте
kind
добры
Mast goes to all kinds of trainings constantly
Маст ходит на всякие тренинги постоянно
Yeah, to leave the last money there.
Ага чтобы оставить там последние Деньги
earned with your ass in the frame not by that
заработанные своей жопой в кадре не тем
What does Sveta teach at these trainings? Well, you
Чему учит на этих тренингах Света ну ты
Well, everything is fair here, this is the first lesson
что Ну тут всё честно вот первое занятие
free of course everything is fair here
бесплатно конечно Тут всё честно я
I heard amazing reviews about this
слышал потрясающий отзывы об этом
Master Tikhomir Stroganov I am the first time
Мастере тихомир Строганов Я первый раз
I hear as if the merchant of the tsarist times
слышу как будто Купчина царских времён
some kind of sausage maker, who are you anyway?
колбасник какой-то тебе кто вобще
stories about him my friend he is an actor too
рассказы про него мой друг он актёр тоже
beginner says career
начинающий говорит карьера
we took off from Kostya
взлетела мы от Костя
would like to sign up great first
хотели бы записаться прекрасно первое
the introductory lesson will start already
ознакомительное занятие начнётся уже
In half an hour, come into the classroom.
через полчаса Проходите в аудиторию я
I'll take the forms now
сейчас понесу анкеты
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah Kost hello three suckers came to you
Угу Кость привет три лоха Тебе пришли
Yeah Well, in general, if I lasso you
Угу Ну в общем если захомутать тебе по
five demolitions As agreed
пять сноса Как и договаривались
Let's make a movie I mean Well, that's right
Давай снимите кино В смысле Ну вот прямо
here now make me a movie, yours over there
здесь сейчас снимите мне кино вон ваша
heroine for example
героиня например
that receptionist girl yes yes
что ресепшн девка да да
y filmed Yeah, well, you didn't film a movie. You filmed
й снял Ага ну вы сняли не кино Вы сняли
[ __ ] oh go to hell oh listen
[__] ой шёл бы ты в срак ужх слушайте
You yourself asked me to tell you what
вы сами мне попросили рассказать вам что
such a movie I'm trying to describe it to you B
такое кино Я пытаюсь вам это описать В
In general terms, what you filmed is this
общих чертах то что вы сняли - это
a video file with a woman and nothing else
видеофайл с бабой и больше ничего
you understand A cinema is something more than that
понимаете А кино Это нечто большее что
well that's it
ну это
[music]
[музыка]
look
смотрите
Yeah, [ __ ].
Да [__]
[music]
[музыка]
p Well, you see, cinema is a drama cinema -
п Ну понимаете кино - это драма кино -
this is a conflict, you understand, it needs to be recorded
это конфликт понимаете нужно фиксировать
real life moments That's what
настоящие острые моменты жизни Вот что
need to be awesome Igor it's me
нужно Обалдеть Игорь это я
I think I'm starting to understand this, I'm starting to understand
это я кажется начинаю понимать я начинаю
understand
понимать
Oh come on Take it off Hey you man
Ох ты вот ну-ка Снимай его Эй ты человек
stop you big-eared [ __ ] and you're fired no
стой ты лопоухий [__] и ты уволен нет
I'm kidding, you're not fired, but you're definitely an [ __ ].
шучу ты не уволен но [__] однозначно
[laughter]
[смех]
Go and see his face What a range of feelings
иди ты видел лицо его Какая гамма чувств
Oh come on, what a class, this is incredible.
Да ну О какой класс это невероятно это
tormented for p years Well, there is still of course
мучат п лет Ну там ещё есть конечно
some moments but this is the spine
некоторые моменты но это это хребет
systems a Class everything I understood everything about the movie
системы а Класс всё я всё понял про кино
I understand everything. Now I want to see how.
Всё понял Я теперь хочу увидеть как
they make cool movies, cool ones and I'm sure
снимают крутое кино крутое и я уверен
that we can do it too So can you
что у нас тоже получится Так у тебя
I still have some connections
связи остались я кое-что
I'll think of something
придумаю
awesome, I understand this is the Zombie company
заебись я так понимаю это компания Зомби
saved Yes it's us Hello Hello
спас Да это мы Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
And you are at a meeting about investments m
А вы на встрече по поводу инвестиций м
yato me-yes It's very nice to meet you
ято я-то да Очень приятно познакомиться
guys, I told you our business will go well
ребят же говорила наши дела пойдут и
the key to the abandoned business environment will work Yash
ключ брошенной бизнес-среде сработает Яш
Bring us a smoothie, come on in
Принеси нам смузи проходите
Yeah So who are you?
Ага Так а вы кого
Can you imagine what
представляете Какую
I have such a structure
структуру я такого
I present
представляю
here is the TV channel
вот телеканал
tsv assistant general director
тсв ассистент генерального директора
listen
слушайте
made it into the media
пробились в медиа
Cool yeah Well I am of course a TV
Круто да Ну я конечно само собой телик
I don't watch that's why Well, of course you do
не смотрю поэтому Ну само собой вы
Natasha Yes Yes And please tell me how
Наташа Да Да А расскажите пожалуйста чем
you are doing it here with pleasure
вы здесь занимаетесь с удовольствием
Zombie rescue is a mobile application
Зомби спас - это мобильное приложение
which we are developing for the Zombie case
которое мы разрабатываем на случай Зомби
Apocalypse Zombie Apocalypse DaDada Well
Апокалипсис Зомби апокалипсиса дадада Ну
if suddenly some kind of thing breaks out there
если там вдруг вырвется какой-нибудь
virus or comet or just something like that
вирус или Комет ну или там просто
the dead will start howling and eating everyone Yes I
мертвяки начнут выва и есть всех Да я
I know what it is And it turns out that it is
знаю что это И вот получается что это
the app is only needed for this
приложение нужно только вот в этом
in this case yes and this is not a computer game
случае да И это не компьютерная игрушка
about zombies no no no no no that's all
про зомби нет нет нет нет нет это всё
very seriously In case
очень серьёзно В случае
zombie apocalypse app Zombie Rescue
зомби-апокалипсиса приложение Зомби Спас
depending on your location
в зависимости от вашего местонахождения
will immediately generate a map of the nearest ones for you
тут же сгенерирует вам карту ближайших
shelters and the route to them
убежищ и маршрут как к ним можно
get to shelter means you by the way
добраться убежищ значит вы кстати
Try the smoothie, it's very tasty. We like it.
Попробуйте смузи очень вкус Нам его
every day from Dragomir market
каждый день с Драгомир ского рынка
let's go Try Well then
припустить Попробуйте Ну так
here the shelter is assessed by three
вот при этом убежище оценивается по трём
indicators first Zombie resistance
показателям первый Зомби устойчивость
here is the strength of the walls, the amount of glass and
вот крепость стен количество стёкол и
so the second thing is the availability of products
так далее второе - это наличие продуктов
and the duration of the reserve Well, in this case
и длительность запаса Ну в данном случае
Of course supermarkets are in the lead third
конечно лидируют супермаркеты третий
weapons potential Well that is if
оружейный потенциал Ну то есть если
there are weapons nearby in what quantity if
рядом оружие в каком количестве если
for example, this is a store with regular cafeterias
например это магаз с обычными столовыми
with knives then of course it's one star if
ножами то это конечно одна звезда если
farms with chainsaws, then that's already two
хозяйствен с бензопилами то это уже две
we have different variations on 3 iche But if
у нас разные вариации на 3 иче Но если
there is an armory or army depot nearby
рядом оружейный склад или армейский
the store is of course five stars Well
магазин то это конечно Пять звёзд Ну
of course it is of course Five stars and
конечно же это конечно же Пять звёзд и
You rent an office for this? Yes
вы вот под это снимаете офис Да
and irz expect to receive investments
и ирз рассчитываете получить инвестици
were interested Yes no you know just one
интересовались Да нет знаете просто один
moment Have you ever thought that if
момент А вы не задумывались что если
Zombie Apocalypse will happen then cellular
случится Зомби Апокалипсис то сотовая
the network will be disconnected, GPS won't work
сеть отключится Ну не будут работать GPS
and all that jazz Because people on
и всё такое прочее Потому что люди на
cellular stations and power plants Well
сотовых станциях и на электростанциях Ну
they too
они тоже
zombie do you think
зомба думаете
Yes, you know, there is such an idea.
Да Знаете есть такая мысль
do you think that we should work on
считаете что нам лучше работать над
offline
офлайн
cards on olan
картами на олан
Are you completely out of your mind with cards or something?
картами Ты совсем ёбу Далась что ли что
Now I understand where you put 5 Milne
я теперь понимаю куда ты дела 5 Милн
which your father
которые тебе отец
shipped what Well, you're Natasha Kiseleva
отгрузил что Ну ты же Наташа Киселёва
Valery Kiselev's daughter
дочь Валерия Киселёва
screenwriter and his fool from Nest
сценариста и дура своего от Нест
only the remains of the cat coconut live
только остатками кота кокоса и живёт
to rent this [ __ ] office to sit with
чтобы снимать этот сраный офис сидеть с
these [ __ ] flipcharts and startups
этими ебу флипчарта и стартапи
Zombie Apocalypse App
приложение на случай Зомби Апокалипсиса
Nata You said this money is from Elon
Ната Ты же сказал это деньги от Илона
mask from hu Ilona huya are you stupid or something
маска от ху Илона хуя дурак ты что ли
a beard in socks on such a body even in
бородка в носочках на такую боду даже в
Skolkovo wouldn't give money for a smoothie from them
Сколково денег бы не дали смузи у них с
Dragomilov market so girl
драгомилов ского рынка так девушка
leave our Open immediately
немедленно покиньте наш Open
[music]
[музыка]
speed and agility are what will save you
скорость и ловкость вот что спасёт во
it's Zombie Apocalypse time and not yours
время Зомби апокалипсиса а не твоё
[ __ ]
сраное
app get ready go with
приложение собирайся едешь со
by the way, I don't work in fast food
мной если что я в фастфуде работать не
I can And this is Nothing here Beautiful
умею А это Ничего здесь Прекрасная
training program you go go
программа обучения ты давай давай
write the date of issue
пиши дата выдачи
0 division A you forgive her sister
0 подразделение А вы простите её сестра
no I'm her Agent you know how it is with actors
нет я я её Агент знаете как у актёров
Agent at the fast food cashier Yes times
Агент у кассирши фастфуда Да времена
I'll give you some crispy ones
такие я тебе дам немного хрустящих
money And in return you inform me about
денежек А ты меня взамен информирую об
her
её
success especially if she tries
успеха особенно если она попытается
quit And now you have a task, girl
уволиться А у тебя девочка теперь задача
work off and return to your father everything that you have
отработать и вернуть отцу всё что ты у
I took him with such a salary in 10
него взяла Я с такой зарплатой через 10
I'll give you back years so don't worry We have
лет верну вы так Не волнуйтесь У нас
overtime can be done at night
сверхурочные есть можно по ночам
clean up Well, and the career prospects
убираться Ну и перспектива карьерного
growth Of course you see the prospect
роста Разумеется видишь перспектива
growth again if the Zombies come here and
роста опять-таки если Зомби придут тут и
there's a lot of food and all sorts of knives and walls
еды дофига и ножи всякие и стены
strong And the most
крепкие А самое
the main thing is that you apologize to me today
главное ты сегодня же извинишься перед
who got into such trouble for you
который за тебя попал в такие
troubles that hell dissipate and promise
неприятности что хрен рассе и пообещаешь
that you will not take anything more from him
что ты больше не возьмёшь у него ни
kopecks
копейки
Okay, but what if something suddenly goes wrong?
Окей Ну а если что-то вдруг пойдёт не
so well do you remember what happened with those two
так Ну ты помнишь что было с теми двум
Yes okay Okay I got it fill it out
Да окей Окей я поняла заполняй
Next I'll go for a burger
дальше пойду бургер
But
Зато
So what is acting?
Итак что такое актёрская игра
please yes and this is a driving school Yes so
пожалуйста да а это автошкола Да так вот
what is acting do you know it
что такое актёрская игра вы знаете Это
not just an imitation of another's life
не просто имитация жизни другого
it's like a person
человека это как бы
accommodation Here you are for example Before
проживание Вот вы например До
today we knew about the actor
сегодняшнего дня знали об актёр све
only by hearsay no we are all actually
только понаслышке нет мы вообще-то все
three professional actors And also
втроём профессиональные актёры Да ещё
It's better then you knew about the actor
лучше значит вы знали об актёр све не
by hearsay but in fact you know nothing about
понаслышке но на самом деле вы ничего о
I don't know about him
нём не знае
So I didn't understand, they knew and they didn't know, but they knew
Так я не понял знали и не знали знали но
but the deputies didnt know
но не знали мго депутаты
Yes, there is probably another reason why
Да Наверняка есть ещё причина по которой
you have no roles here at all No we all
вы здесь совсем нет ролей Нет мы все
we are filming in the same series. Yes, there are roles.
снимаемся в одном сериале А да роли есть
but there are always few of them and there are never enough of them
но их всегда мало и их всегда же не
enough you dream of something more No
хватает ты мечтаешь о чём-то большем Нет
I dreamed of this. Oh well, ...
я такой мечтал А хорошо ну ну ну в общем
All three of us want to raise our level
мы все втроём хотим повысить наш уровень
to play better Well in her case I
чтобы играть лучше Ну в её случае я
I play normally Everything is clear Everything is clear
нормально играю Всё понятно всё понятно
There is nothing easier, so listen to me
нет ничего проще значит слушайте меня
carefully secret of school tech world
внимательно секрет школы Техо мира
Stroganova actor svo -
строганова актёр сво -
This
это
pain I thought life is your pain for sure
боль Я думал жизнь - это боль твоя точно
yes true true life is pain and an actor
да верно верно жизнь это боль а актёр
svo is life, therefore the actor svo is
сво - это жизнь поэтому актёр сво это
pain something I didn't understand anything Well
боль что-то Я ничего не поняла Ну
you didn't understand anything correctly because
правильно вы ничего не поняли потому что
I haven't explained to you yet how to use this
я вам ещё не объяснил как применять эту
pain but we will talk about this on
боль но об этом мы с вами поговорим на
second lesson And why the first one so fast
втором занятии А что первая так быстро
so the academic hour ended
закончилось так академический час то
It's only been 15 minutes, well
прошло всего минут 15 ну
academic yes fortunately for you I
академических да к счастью для вас я
I can conduct the second lesson right now
могу провести второе занятие прямо
now of course it will be paid 5,000
сейчас конечно оно будет платное 5.000 с
listen to everyone before you count
каждого слушайте прежде чем подсчитывать
your losses you will understand in fact that
свои убытки вы поймите на самом деле что
for you it is
для вас это
Benefit school tihomir stroganova is
Выгода школа тихомир строганова - это
community of talented people you know
сообщество талантливых людей знаете
here are not only actors but also
здесь не только актёры но здесь и
directors and producers of all their
режиссёры и продюсеры всех своих
We arrange serious training for students
студентов мы устраиваем серьёзные
[music]
[музыка]
projects sold Cherry Orchard
проекты продан Вишнёвый сад
sold Who bought I
продан Кто купил Я
[music]
[музыка]
bought Excellent Excellent Excellent Excellent a
купил Отлично Отлично Отлично Отлично а
Now apply yours to this
теперь А теперь примените к этому свою
the pain you told me about Here
боль о которой вы мне рассказывали Вот
Here you are, Sveta, asking about the garden, you are like
вот вы Света спрашивая про сад вы как бы
You ask me what I have to do
у меня спрашиваете мне что придётся до
end of life as you said suck
конца жизни Как вы там говорили сосать
suck suck another producer Yes
сосать сосать у очередного продюсера Да
ok Oleg, you say sold, you are like
хорошо Олег вы говоря продан вы как бы
You say yes I starred in Game of Thrones
говорите да я снимался в игре престолов
but only with the ass and not with the face. Got it. Yeah.
но только жопой а не лицом Понятно Угу
So, Arina, when you throw the keys, you seem to be
Так а вы Арина бросая ключи вы как бы
do you think that for the rest of your life you
думаете что до конца своей жизни Вы
you will play the Snow Queen in
будете играть Снежную королеву в
Perm theater Penza Penza
Пермском театре пензенском пензенском
penza I understand perfectly Well what
пензенском Понятно отлично Ну что
let's go 3 2
поехали 3 2
let's go sold Cherry Orchard I will sell Who
поехали продан Вишнёвый сад продам Кто
I bought it
купил Я
[music]
[музыка]
bought Well, well, it's brilliant, it's brilliant
купил Ну вот ну Гениально же а гениально
nothing has changed at all How can it?
вообще ничего не изменилось Да как может
change the throw of keys I think here
измениться бросок ключей Мне кажется тут
It's not me who plays, it's the force of gravity guys Guys you
не я играю а сила тяжести ребят Ребят вы
you just don't see yourself from the outside
просто не видите себя со стороны Вы
you know i should congratulate you
знаете я Вас должен поздравить вы
successfully improved their qualifications in
успешно повысили свою квалификацию в
school of acting tihomir
школе актёрского мастерства тихомир
stroganova Yes diplomas you can
строганова Да дипломы Вы можете
print on exit And now the most
распечатать на выходе А теперь самое
the main thing for me while we were working together
главное пока мы с вами работали мне
one familiar producer wrote there are three
написал один знакомый продюсер есть три
roles in the new blockbuster you know we
роли в новом блокбастере вы знаете мы с
him Old friends and I could him
ним Старые друзья и я мог бы ему
recommend you as the best
посоветовать вас в качестве лучших
graduates Wow We are the best graduates So
выпускников Ого Мы лучшие выпускники Так
we've only known each other for an hour, forget it, Tikhomir
мы же знакомым всего час забей тихомир
Let's put it simply, you want to sell to us
Давай по-простому ты хочешь продать нам
I am ready to buy roles.
роли я готова купить Я
me too, three hundred from each Oh well
тоже я да три сотни с каждого Да ладно
No, don't listen, this is fantasy.
Нет не послушайте это это фантастика
will take out the second attraction at the box office Well
вынесет второе притяжение в прокате Ну
how easy it is to do
как нефиг делать
where are you looking for an ATM I'm with you and I
ты куда банкомат искать я с тобой и я
Great
отлично
[music]
[музыка]
great until it all burns with fire
отлично до Гори оно всё огнём
to be honest I miss ours
если честно А я у соскучился по нашим
this night
этим ночным
filming when I am free in creativity
съёмочная когда я свободен в творчестве
Yeah, I have nowhere to go because of your debts.
Ага свободн некуда из-за ваших Долгов
Valera, this is the freedom we have now
Валера вот этой свободой мы теперь
we'll find enough, guys, it's small
найдем се доста короче ребят небольшая
the problem of the same masons that we have
проблема тех же самых масонов что у нас
I was filming before but I couldn't get it
до этого снимались я достать не смогла
Lika went on vacation with her husband and those two
Лика уехала с мужем отдыхать а те двое
The guys got jobs as cashiers at Shestyorochka
устроились кассирами в шестёрочка ребята
they're cutting the trick Yeah, so they'll be there today
рубят фишку Угу поэтому сегодня будут
other
другие
for what they said at my institute
за то как говорили в моём институте на
plywood is this And what does this mean with bubble
фанере это И что это значит при бабле
We have a lot of money and I counted Valerian
нам оло нехило и я посчитала валерин
We'll get the loan in a couple of months Oh
кредит мы погам за пару месяцев Ой
Thank you guys Thank you
спасибо ребята Спасибо вам
huge Mashenka you know Natasha daughter
огромное Машенька ты знаешь Наташа дочка
called today, sorry for everything, she says
звонила сегодня Извиняй за всё говорит
to work
на работу
she finally got settled, everything worked out for her
устроилась наконец-то у неё ВС сложилось
by whom
кем
got something going in the restaurant business
устроилось что-то в ресторанном бизнесе
Speak There is a certain career growth up there
Говори Там сверху урочный карьерный рост
says Now she will give me money
говорит Теперь она мне будет деньгами
help I'm so glad Guys I'm so glad And I
помогать Я так рад Ребята так рад А я-то
so glad And what do we do with the Masons?
так рада А что с масонами делаем не
It's confusing that the other lines are the same, yes or no
смущает что другие алиния та же да нет
Well, what are you saying? Well, we can come up with something like that.
ну что ты Ну мы можем придумать например
such that when a person is captured by corgis
такое что когда человек захвачен коргов
With the alien korgovs with the skim yes forgive
Ским пришельцем коргов скими да прости
that's when he
вот когда он
captured by his mind changes
захвачен уме него меняется
face
лицо
Brilliant Lich
Гениально Лич
and here are our actors
а вот и наши актёр
ki we're running we're running Valera we're running Let's go I
ки бежим бежим Валера бежим Пошли я
then raska and ta da nothing faster [ __ ]
потом раска а та да ничего быстрее [__]
us
нам
car What happened it's a car
машинка А что случилось тачка это же
Sveta's car actress of ours I am to all
машина Света актрисы нашей Я же всем
I work in transport, I know how to [ __ ] her, yes
транспортом занимаюсь знаю её [__] да
the whole gang is here because they are here
тут вся кодла что они здесь
Stroganov is a bastard that Tisha
делают Строганов паскуда что Тиша
Stroganov, a [ __ ] [ __ ], was our Mason
Строганов [__] сраный у нас был масоном
on the show and then acting school
на передаче а потом шко актёрского
the skill of the OTC tone adjusted them They
мастерства ОТК тон их подогнал Они
bought the role from us
купили роль у нас
listen they don't recognize your cars
слушайте они Не узнают ваши машины не
they have never seen her in their life, what's your left side
они её с роду не видели твою налево что
do something
делать-то
now and this
теперь а это ещё
who oh
кто ой
and what are you doing here? So what are we doing?
а вы что тут делаете Так мы что
it's happening You told me you're taking me to see
происходит Ты мне сказал везёшь смотреть
cool fantasy what
крутую фантастику что
this is a quieter [ __ ] who is quiet
это вот тише [__] кто да тихомир
Stroganov, he was in his father's crowd scene
Строганов он снимался у отца в массовке
in the return of the Tushino rose He
в возвращении Тушинской розочки Он
said that it's fantastic here
сказал что здесь фантастический
blockbuster Well, here's the technique It seems
блокбастер Ну вот техника Вроде
the filming is going on and we saw it from afar
съёмочная стоит и мы так издалека видели
there are such and such people here but they ran away
тут таких-то людей но они убежали
It is clear what you are doing here. Yes, we are.
Понятно вы что здесь делаете Да мы
actually Yes, we actually have 900 pieces
собственно Да мы собственно 900 штук
they [ __ ] it up. That was the entire fee for
просрали капец Это был весь гонорар за
first month of filming Wait a minute
первый съёмочный месяц Подождите вы
then you what did you pay someone to
то вы что Вы кому-то заплатили чтобы
no one of your [ __ ] is filming here
сниматься здесь ни кому-то твоему сраной
Stroganovo we are its best graduates Yes
Строганово мы его лучшие выпускники Да
Quiet you. Don't you understand that we
тихо ты Ты что не понял что нас
deceived In general Vlad I'm afraid that today
обманули В общем Влад боюсь что сегодня
I won't be able to show you what it is
мне не удастся вам показать что такое
real cinema is completely the opposite of pulp I
настоящее кино совсем наоборот жмых Я
I just realized that this is a real movie
только что понял что настоящее кино это
circular
круговое
scam Well, this is a fiasco Bros. How are you?
наебалово Так ну это фиаско Братаны как
these two ended up here and maybe they recognized
эти двое здесь оказались может узнали
about us and decided to punish not stupid
про нас и решили наказать не тупой
the method seems to me to be the same as usual in the movies. Everything
способ мне кажется как обычно в кино Всё
the thing is in the circle [ __ ] up Maybe you
дело в круговом наебал Возможно ты
In general, you only filmed the wedding
вообще только свадьбе снимал ты-то
how do you know? Okay, let's go quietly
откуда знаешь Ладно по-тихому валим
from here we will leave by taxi car equipment
отсюда уедем на такси машину технику
We'll pick it up in the morning
утром заберём
like repost
лайк репост
How did you get here?
Как вы сюда
we've passed this now it's not important at all
прошли это сейчас совсем не главный
Father the main thing is that you violated our
отец главное что ты нарушил наш
contract it's not my fault it worked out that way
договор я не виноват так сложились
circumstances then give me back my
обстоятельства тогда давай назад мои
money 5
деньги 5
I have a million of them
млн у меня их
no What should we do then?
нет Что же нам тогда
I don't know what to do
делать я не знаю
this is very
это очень
bad but fortunately I know
плохо но к счастью знаю
[music]
[музыка]
I
я
children in the next
дете в следующей
series clo it is a known fact great
серии кло это известный факт прекрасно
we know but the question is now
знаем но вопрос сейчас
more important
важнее
friends do you understand anything
друзей ты что-нибудь понимаешь
The series You Promised Me will air soon
Скоро эфир сериала Вы обещали мне
position if the series turns out bad
должность если сериал получится плохим
And here it is, this nest of TV [ __ ] has arrived
А вот оно это гнездо телепидоров пришли
bloody ratings
рейтинги кровавых
[ __ ] are very bad yes
шлюх очень плохо да
earlier in the series And I 2 months ago on
ранее в сериале А я 2 месяца назад на
refueling
заправке
hose who will i become the CEO
шланг кем я стану генеральным директором
tsv channel I want the series Poneslas
телеканала тсв Я хочу сериал Понеслась
[ __ ] by
[__] по
bumps you hired him to fail
кочкам вы наняли его для провала
Komandan rewrites the script a little
командан немножко переписывает сценарий
I hear you taking this
я чу что ты взя э де
someone has discovered my plan and wants to tell me
кто-то раскрыл мой план и хочет мне
The owners of everything sent me to interfere
помешать меня послали владельцы всего
you must follow this holiday
этого праздника ты должна проследить
so that no one interferes with this idiot Vlad
чтобы никто не мешал этому идиоту Владу
to destroy the channel and devalue the shares
разваливать канал и обесценивать акции
now we'll work [ __ ] real movie
сейчас поработаем [__] настоящее кино
This is a total scam. I like it.
это круговое наебалово А мне нравится
when I am free in creativity then
когда я свободен в творчестве тогда
give me back my money I have it
давай назад мои деньги у меня их
no Guys what are you doing guys
нету Ребят вы что делаете ребята
[music]
[музыка]
Well
Ну что
there's nothing good there Valery No
там ну ничего хорошего Валеры Нет в
I mean he is no longer alive with us
смысле его уже нет с нами живого
no date on products from the day before yesterday
никакого даты на продуктах позавчерашние
And Valera loves fresh cottage cheese every day
А Валера любит свежий творожок каждый
the day follows him
день за ним ходит
there are very deep marks on the site itself
на самом участке глубокие следы очень
wide treads seem heavy
широких протекторов кажется тяжёлая
car
машина
SUV I opened with a spare key
внедорожник Я открыла запасным ключом
what he gave me but the lock is fresh
что он мне дал но на замке свежие
scratches Valera has not been an alcoholic for a long time and his hands
царапины Валера давно не [__] и руки у
it doesn't shake, it looks like the lock was picked
него не трясутся похоже замок вскрывали
Wow And how did you understand everything so much? Yes, before tsv
Вау И как ты всё так поняла да Перед тсв
I worked as a clapperboard for a year, then Legacy
я работала год хлопушкой Наследие потом
2 years second on the har So why do you want to
2 года вторым на харе Так что зач сжи а
No
Нет
[music]
[музыка]
exactly Igor
точно Игорь
dried up I'm careful this is different things a
высохло я осторожен это Вещи разные а
Was he robbed or something? No, he wasn't.
его что ограбили что ли Да нет у него
always such a mess yes And where is it then
всегда такой срач да А где он тогда не
I know Well this has clearly not been here before
знаю Ну вот этого здесь явно раньше не
it was [ __ ] Oh how scary what is this
было бля Ой как страшно что это такое
the script is good
сценарий это Хорош
scary Oh and here
стрема Ой а тут
note from Valera's kidnappers Lord [ __ ]
записка похитителей Валеры Господи посру
now what
сейчас что
there reshoot according to these scripts Otherwise
там переснимать по этим сценариям Иначе
you won't see grandpa anymore what does this mean
дедулю больше не увидите Что это значит
this means we need to reshoot according to these
это значит нужно переснимать по этим
scenarios Otherwise we will not see it again
сценариям Иначе мы больше не увидим
grandpa what a [ __ ] Valera what a yes
дедулю какого да ёб Валеру какого А да
exactly but
точно но
Wait
подожди
pos Delhi show money ran out as
пос Дели показа деньги кончились как
Vladislav Well, it's Valera Well, maybe
Владислав Ну это же Валера А ну может
tell the cops No they said if
ментовку сообщить Нет они сказали если
we will inform the cops that they will kill us all
мы сообщим ментовку нас всех убьют
there was no such thing in the note, yes, that's it
такого в записке не было не было да это
I must have imagined this tension
мне Видимо померещилось это напряжение
tension Yes you sent Masha well cake
напряжение Да вы переслали Маша ну жмых
clo it's a known fact we all do this
кло это известный факт мы все это
We know very well But the question now is
прекрасно знаем Но вопрос сейчас в
friend How can we save
другом Как нам спасти
Valera
Валеру
I listen as here already yes yes I run everything
слушаю как здесь уже да да бегу всё
arrived So what should we do Valera
приехал Так а нам-то что делать Валеру
save as every cricket knows its own
спасать как всяк сверчок знае свой
six Right now What did he mean by that?
шесток Вот сейчас Что он имел в виду ни
horseradish
хрена
Okay, we need to collect it.
Ладно надо собрать
Advice yes no
Совет да не
grazing soon broadcast
пася скоро эфир
Are you aware of the series?
сериала ты вкурсе сза
The first d series is almost finished
первы д серий уже практически завершён
It is we who put all the rest in.
именно Именно мы вкладываем все остав То
there you are, investing all the remaining
есть ты вкладываешь все оставшиеся
I put money into advertising this masterpiece
деньги в рекламу этого шедевра я
I'm investing Well, it's not me, you're the channel director
вкладываю Ну не я же ты директор канала
you signed everything, don't worry about it within the framework
ты всё подписал уже не волнуйся в рамках
advertising campaign you will go on TV
рекламной кампании поедешь на ТВ
talk about the series like on TV Well, so
рассказывать про сериал как на ТВ Ну так
on TV you go to the remains of knowledge to the studio
на ТВ едешь в останки знан иь на студию
write down everything in chocolate what kind of diya
записываешь всё в шоколаде какую дию
and this is a beautiful woman I'm on
а это красивая баба я на
her
неё
signed see how everything coincided she herself
подписан видишь как всё совпало она сама
asked to call you The thing is
попросила тебя позвать Дело в том
What
что
who fell for you rgl saw on
запала кто ргл на тебя увидела на
presentations and everything blew the girl's head off
презентации и всё снесло голову девчонки
completely
напрочь
but I didn't notice, so she did you
а же я е не заметил так она тебя
I noticed, in short, my assistant will pass it on
заметила короче ассистентка моя передаст
Where
куда
How much? Come on, just don't get lost there.
сколько Давай ты там только не теряйся
You dont need to grab the ass right away, but I
прям сразу за жопу хватать не надо но я
don't skid, those are the TV girls they are like that
не буксуй я те теле девочки они такие
you know they like to break down but for show
знаешь любят поломаться но для вида для
view So you go ahead and step on the gas No
вида Так что ты давай газуй Не
be afraid coffee is shitty re
боись кофе дерьмовый ре
tea in general
чай вобще
[ __ ] hell, as Valera has stated many times
[__] как Валера много раз заявляла он
retrograde
ретроград
Cheburashka's grandmother Another grandmother
бабушка чебураши ещ Один бабушка
Cheburashi is a gerontophile and a retrograde is
чебураши геронтофил а ретроград - это
opponents of progress Well, yeah, like him
противники прогресса Ну да типа он
I've never used computers and all that stuff
никогда не пользовался компами всё такое
Yes, and here's what I found from him
Да а вот что нашла у него
home Wait this is when we went you
дома Подожди это когда мы ездили ты
took from his house Well, yes, Masha, it's terrible
забрала из его дома Ну да Маша это ужас
some what if there is an evil spirit in the board
какой-то а вдруг там Злой дух в плате
nothing can be taken from the house of the deceased
ничего нельзя забирать из дома покойника
Igor Valera is alive Yes, but the sun is early
Игорь Валера жив Да но ВС рано су
scary
страшно
Valera Why did you buy a tablet I'm there
Валера Зачем ты купил планшет я там пола
and I saw that he only went to the post office and
и увидела что ходил он только на почту и
I was talking to one
общался с одним
addressee and how did you get into his mail
адресатом а как ты зашла в его почту
I found the password
подобрала пароль
Coconut is the contact of that very one
Кокос это контакт того самого
business lady than to fulfill his demands
бизнес-леди чем выполнять его требования
we need to find out if everything is okay with Valera
нам нужно узнать всё ли с Валерой в
okay he answered answered simply
порядке он ответил ответил ть просто
joke I'll meet you today I won't go and I
шуть встречу сегодня я не пойду а я
I'll go and smash a couple of mouths
пойду разнесу пару хлебальник
they will become like silk, am I a fool or what, should I go?
станут как шёлковые дурак что ли пойду я
yes yes this is correct correct necessary
да да это Правильно правильно нужно
talk to Valera and find out where he is
поговорить с Валерой и узнать где его
hold on and then we'll decide what to do next Well
держит а там решим что делать дальше Ну
such
такое
And here it is, this nest of TV [ __ ]. Well
А вот оно это гнездо телепидоров Ну
nothing I will smash you all I will smash you
ничего Я вас я вас всех разъебу я вам
I'll show you what real television is
покажу что такое настоящее телевидение
I'd love to hit you in the head
на здоровье башкой бы тебя уебать об
wall That would be great Oh you
стену Вот это было бы на здоровье Ой вы
you know, I fart not only with my butt but also
знаете я пукаю не только попой но ещё и
vagina [ __ ] on the Central channel
влагалищем [__] по Центральному каналу
Central [ __ ] Yes if you were like that
по Центральному [__] Да если бы ты такое
in the Soviet Union I would have [ __ ] up
в Советском Союзе пизданула бы на
the next day you would be led
следующий день тебя бы вели по
basement corridor with one door in
подвального коридору с одной дверью в
pardon denied Bach yoptyt and that's it A
помиловании отказано Бах ёптыть и всё А
well news hello news little
ну новости Здравствуйте новости мало
what are you talking about? You are also depressed.
того что вы пиздите Вы же ещё и депрес
catches up no so that there somehow in the process
нагоняет нет чтобы там как-то в процессе
maybe some funny joke
может быть анекдоти какой-нибудь прохват
The heads of three met in Davos
в давосе встретились главы трёх
Pinocchio jerked off and burned but
государств Буратино дрочил и сгорел но
Also
так же
cooler
прикольнее
o It seems like a TV channel has arrived
о Кажись пришёл телеканал
ass Hello decide
задница Здравствуйте решите
Thank you, I am
Спасибо я к
Yegor Chief, a red-haired girl came to see you
Егору Шеф к вам пришли девушка рыжие
bob hair height about 170
волосы каре рост примерно 170
body type athletic eyes
телосложение спортивное глаза
bob on the right shoulder blade birthmark ved
каре на право лопатки родимое пятно вед
rolling
перекатка
Let
Пусть
And we are just getting to know each other
проходит А мы как раз знакомимся с
Valera's creativity by the way is a good series
творчеством Валера кстати хорошая серия
Yeah, this is the Jubilee hundredth coconut in the kingdom.
Ага это Юбилейная сотая кокос в царстве
dogs Valera How are you in
собак Валера Как вы в
ok Yes, it seems so, but I'm nowhere
порядке Да вроде да только меня никуда
they won't let me go and they won't let me call
не отпускают и и не дают Позвонить
let my daughter go, we'll find the money, and
дочке отпустите мы найдём деньги а
I don't need money anymore, I need it
деньги мне уже не нужны мне нужно
another remake of the series
другое переснять сериал
impossible Well then let Valera go too
невозможно Ну значит и Валеру отпустить
Same
тоже
impossible and it will take you a long time to collect it from
невозможно И долго вы его собирать из
hold until we see the whole cat
держать пока не посмотрим всего кота
how much coconut is there 500 episodes Yeah
кокоса там сколько 500 серий Угу
500 and at the end of each
500 и в конце каждого
episode Valera will receive an award
эпизода Валера будет получать награду
not even
даже не
included in the next
включил в следующий
once in general convinced that about life Zdorov A
раз в общем убедил что о жи Здоров А
now go and do your job while you're at it
теперь иди и делай дело пока делаешь
think how many episodes of the cartoon
думай Сколько эпизодов мультфильма
Valera will be able to watch until the first
Валера сможет посмотреть до первого
heart attack [ __ ] you he is va Godi
инфаркта [__] вы он же ва Годи
will help sell the first cosik on this
поможет продай первого ко косика на эту
the figurine will be found right away
фигурку сразу найдётся
[music]
[музыка]
buyer A Hello Hello
покупатель А здравствуйте Здравствуйте
Valeria already recognized Vlad, but listen Vlad
Валерия уже узнал Влад а слушайте Влад
I came here specifically to talk to you
специально зашла поговорить просто вы
the guest is of course not quite in our format
гость конечно не совсем в формате нашего
show yes yes asked to do with you
шоу да да попросила сделать с вами
issue Well, yes, that's how I understand it as
выпуск Ну да так понимаю в качестве
promo of some of your series Okay, Ler, well
промо какого-то вашего сери Ладно Лер ну
what are you doing come on this same thing here alone
что ты давай же это самое же здесь одни
Well, accept the IR, you can not understand Well, that's all
Ну Прими ИК можно не поняла Ну я всё
I know what it's about
знаю о чём о
I doubt you in general I am with almost everyone
тебе сомневаюсь в общем я со всеми почти
broke up, only actress Ulka remained there
расстался осталась там одна актрис улька
on the suction
на подсосе
there
там
in short, I'm open
что короче я открыт
To be honest, I didn't know you were empty-handed.
Если честно я не знал что ты порожняком
you go in the sense Well in the sense that vagina
ты идёшь в смысле Ну в смысле что вагина
free
свободна
and [ __ ]
а хуя
you like it rougher for yourself
себе пожёстче любишь
[music]
[музыка]
Yes
да
baby I'm going to [ __ ] you right now try it
детка а я же тебя сейчас уебу попробуй
[music]
[музыка]
Make-up artist Good
гримёра Доброе
morning what's going on
утро Что происходит
And what's in the bag? Oh, there's a dismembered one there.
А что в сумке А ай там расчленённый
Valera, [ __ ], I knew it, [ __ ], Igor
Валера [__] Я так и знал [__] Игорь
Calm down
Успокойтесь
[ __ ] what the [ __ ] is this
[__] какого хера что это такое Это
dollars Thanks Cap last night I
доллары Спасибо Кэп вчера ночью я
I finally decided to go get the figurine
всё-таки решила съездить за фигуркой
cat coconut number one as he said
кота кокоса номер один как говорил
Valera is really a number one figurine
Валера это действительно фигурка номер
one made after success
один изготовленная после успеха
cartoon personally for
мультфильма лично для
Valery surprised me how expensive they are
Валеры меня удивило Как дорого стоят
the first batch of figurines are kind of rich
фигурки первой партии какие-то богатые
fans were falling off
фанаты отваливались
But the very first Coconut Million
Но самый-самый первый Кокос миллион
some top oilman grew up in dollars
долларов какой-то топ из нефтянки вырос
on
на
coconut Well, I mean on this coconut, and
кокосе Ну в смысле на вот этом кокосе а
not on that one, although probably on that one too
не на том хотя на том наверное тоже
In short, his personal brought these yesterday
короче его личник вчера привёз вот эти
he took the money
деньги и забрал
figurine We are rich You are a fool rynok What are you
фигурку Мы богаты Ты дурак ринок Что ты
what are you talking about?
такое несёшь
we are fabulously rich Yes Igor this money
мы сказочно богаты Да Игорь э эти деньги
- the chance that was given to us
- шанс который нам дала
fate is sure they are here for a reason
судьба уверена они у нас не просто так
they are there to save
они для того чтобы спасти
Valera buy him out
Валеру выкупить его
Oh well, it's unlikely that this money is big for
Ой ну это вряд ли эти деньги большие для
us But not for those who want
нас Но никак не для тех кто хочет
get hold of
заполучить
channel we have to tear it out of their
канал мы должны вырвать его из их
paw Igor Well it's like a movie, you know A
лап Игорь Ну это как кино понимаете А
this is our budget
это наш бюджет а
the three of us must do this
мы втроём должны это
unfortunately no we have to do what
сделать к сожалению нет мы должны Что
make save Valera Yes, this is some kind of
сделать спасти Валеру Да это какой-то
quest I love quests No [ __ ] it's not
квест Я люблю квесты Да ни хрена это не
quest Valera in big trouble and besides us
квест Валера в большой беде и кроме нас
everyone on him
всем на него
I don't care I'm sorry maybe someone already
наплевать Я извиняюсь может кто-то уже
I suggested but you didn't think about it
предлагал но вы не думали над тем чтобы
just share
просто поделить
no money
деньги нет
money is not in life
деньги в жизни не
the main thing after I got into the turn
главное после того как я попал в доворот
tele
теле
Svetka's intrigues were crushing my bull for me
интриг Светка давила мне бычка за
role I almost got divorced by my ex-wife
роль меня чуть не развела бывшая жена
Arina tried to throw it over her dick and I
Арина пыталась кинуть через хер и я
got a hot beating from the host
отхватил Жарких пиздюлей от ведущей с
Friday TV channel I understood something No
телеканала пятницы я кое-что понял Нет
nothing is more important than friends
ничего важнее друзей
Vladislav And how did you understand from all this?
Владислав А как из всего этого вы поняли
about the importance of friends well somehow somehow I understood
о важности друзей ну как-то как-то понял
and that's it Well, well, what are you getting at?
и всё Ну что ну что ты докопалась до
me Tanya joke I remember that you are Masha
меня Тань шутка Я помню что ты Маша
I remember and now I will never talk about it again
помню и теперь больше никогда об этом не
I'll forget Oh my god I'm going to cry now
забуду [__] сейчас расплачусь
In short, we have a lot of money and we need it.
Короче у нас [__] денег и Нам нужен
super plan I'll come up with a plan I'll take it
супер план Я придумаю план возьму на
itself administrative function of the market
себя административной функции ринок
the technical side of the issue guys
техническую сторону вопроса ребята
actors play out a cool story Igor
актёры разыграйте крутую историю Игорь
you will take care of the production You are with us
займётесь постановкой Вы же у нас
director Guys, here's a question, what
режиссёр Ребята а вот такой вопрос а что
what will I do in this whole story?
же во всей этой истории буду делать я а
you as usual Vladislav are [ __ ] great
вы как обычно Владислав ни хрена отлично
forward
вперёд
[music]
[музыка]
[ __ ]
[__]
open up open up [ __ ] I know what you are
открывай открывай шлюшка Я знаю что ты
there with that woodpecker
там с этим дятлом
protein open about nya I have
протеиновым открывай про ня у меня ж
the key is the same
ключ же
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
there is a little noise here
есть тут небольшой шум на
On the floor a man caught his wife with her lover
этаже мужик жену с любовником застал
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music]
[музыка]
it looks like you can't help
похоже не поможешь
step aside I'm at work and
отойдите Я на работе а
protocol
протокол
sure why why did you kill him e in
уверен зачем зачем ты Убил его е в
stegney he was so young what the hell
стегней он был так молод Какого хрена
calmly our fun was so innocent we
спокойно наши забавы были так невинны Мы
just trying to drown out the pain
всего лишь пытались заглушить Боль Боль
loneliness
одиночества
I won't lie, money is dirt to me
не буду врать деньги для меня грязь
if you help me get rid of him I'll throw in some more
поможешь от него избавиться накину ещё
[music]
[музыка]
ten Wow That was really cool Even
десятку Вау Вот это было прям Круто Даже
I believed that they killed me, now they're going to kill you
я поверил что меня убили вот тебя убить
was
было
sino true such natural cost M 200
сино тру такой натурали стоил М 200
Arinochka, regarding the last remark, here
Ариночка по поводу последней реплики вот
a little bit about the pain
по поводу боли немножечко
Don't start again Please, your this I
пере не начинай Ну пожалуйста свою эту И
in general Mash you said that I do nothing
вообще Маш ты сказал что я ничего делать
I won't Well, sorry, a script appeared
не буду Ну извините появился сценарий
new roles have appeared But who else can
появились новые роли Но кто ещё может
play rich
сыграть богатого
I'm making a move
Мачу я
I can finish you are a magnet for obra
смогу заканчивай ты магнит для обре
Machu has only one here Mashka is right I'm
у Мачу здесь только один Машка права я
you are a talking [ __ ], I work part-time for ta
ты говорящая срака подрабатываю на та
Men, you are all awesome and I am awesome too.
мужчины вы все заебись а я Ты тоже
awesome let's focus on
заебись Давайте сосредоточимся на
Valera's rescue This is only the first
спасение Валеры Вот это только первый
our show act still has a lot of work to do
акт нашего шоу ещё работать и работать
What's wrong with his radio?
вперёд раци у него села что
Excuse me please, my door is number
Извините пожалуйста у меня дверь номер
slammed shut can I call you on
захлопнулась можно от вас позвонить на
reception Where is it?
ресепшен А где
Maxim Maxim Oh here I stood and went to the toilet
Максим Максим О тут Стоял в туалет пошёл
So can I call? I'm cold.
Так что можно позвонить А то мне холодно
I just got out of the shower and there's nothing under my robe
я только из душа а под халатом ничего
stand she touched someone you put down
стоять она кого-нибудь трогала ты Опусти
How did you get the gun in here? You keep quiet.
пушку как ты пронёс е сюда молчите вы
you don't understand anything, it's not her anymore, it's a virus
ничего не понимаете это уже не она вирус
penetrated her brain do not approach razo
проник её мозг не подходим разо
stand Well guys for me it's all over
стоять Ну что ж ребят для меня уже всё
too much
слишком
late she bit me when she ran away from
поздно она укусила меня когда сбежала из
laboratories but you can still be saved
лаборатории но вы ещ можете спастись
Burn our bodies
сожгите Наши тела
what the hell is going on here Grandpa
какого хера здесь происходит Дед ты
do you understand anything?
что-нибудь понимаешь
Hello, sorry. The neighbors complained.
Здравствуйте извините Соседи жаловались
to the noise of the external independent evaluation you have here
на шум ВНО какого у вас тут
[music]
[музыка]
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
infected people are not so easy to kill How long ago
заражённых так просто не убить Как давно
They were zombies, they were zombies like
Они зомба нулись что зомба нулись как
long time ago 10 minutes Half an hour an hour a minute somewhere
давно 10 минут Полчаса час минуту где-то
Help me
Помогите меня
you were hurt, bitten, yes, everything is back, not everything
ранили вас кусали Да все назад не всё
what is needed there is no medicine
что надо лекарства нет
you were bitten no no no no no no no no no no no
вас кусали не не не не никто не кусал
No, take gas masks and put them on.
Нет бы Возьмите противогазы и наденьте
we sprayed tactical gas which
мы распыляли тактический газ который
hits all infected we will get you out of
бьёт всех заражённых мы вас выведем из
[music]
[музыка]
buildings fell into disrepair, they say
здания вырубились на глух говорят с
this gas 5 hours in
этого газа 5 часов в
disconnected Well that's all
отключке Ну что всё а
Valera We are you
Валера Мы тебя
saved the boys girls And what is all this
спасли ребята девочки А что всё это
This was my best production.
такое Это была моя лучшая постановка
which unfortunately no one filmed Well we
которую к сожалению никто не снял Ну мы
we are saving you Valery How how yes Very
тебя спасаем Валер Как как да Очень
your coconut figurine just cost
просто ваша фигурка кокоса стоила
million dollars that we spent on
миллион долларов что мы потратили на
costumes and pyrotechnics another 100 on
костюмы и пиротехнику ещ 100 на
rehearsals of the whole show to make it work
репетиции всего шоу чтобы работало
Ideally another 100 for police bribes
идеально ещ 100 на взятки полиции чтобы
they didn't come on call if anything 200 me
не приезжали по вызовам если что 200 я
spent to close all your loans
потратила чтобы закрыть все ваши кредиты
By the way
кстати
Awesome Thank you Thank you friends you you
Обалдеть Спасибо Спасибо друзья вы вы
You are just like that
такие вы просто
incredible so that means it remains
невероятны так значит осталось
half a million isn't even half a million yet
полмиллиона ещё даже нет полмиллиона
I had to spend money to evict everyone
пришлось потратить чтобы выселить всю
this hotel, although I said that for
вот эту гостиницу хотя я говорила что за
ten could have been hired thugs
десятку можно было нанять отморозков
who would Zaga these three and we calmly
которые бы Зага этих троих и мы спокойно
they would have taken Valera away
бы увели Валеру
But it would be like this
Но это было бы так
beautiful I'll bite you now and you'll be a zombie A
красиво я сейчас вас укушу и вы зомба А
you Svetka before
тебя Светка раньше
[laughter]
[смех]
shoot the guys guys Guys where
пристрелит ребят ребят Ребят а где
renok
ренок
understood Please note that in addition to 10
поняты Обратите внимание что помимо 10
kg of cocaine and several units of weapons in
кг кокаина и нескольких единиц оружия в
were found in the suspect's apartment
квартире у подозреваемого обнаружены
funds of an unknown person
денежные средства неизвестного
origin and
происхождения и
most likely with child porn What
скорее всего с детским порно Какое
porn that crazy that gone What 10
порно что с ума что сошли Какие 10
kilograms I don't even smoke zazo
килограммов Я вообще зазо даже не курю
it's all a setup you burst in the middle
это всё Подстава вы врывается посреди
nights with unauthorized searches they
ночи с обыском несанкционированным они
everything was thrown quieter young man
всё подбросили тише молодой человек
the investigator will explain everything to you now
следователь вам сейчас всё объяснит
Let's go So, young man
Пойдёмте Значит так молодой человек
I won't do it to you for a long time in the brain. We
долго мозге я тебе делать не буду Мы
we know perfectly well who you are and what you are
прекрасно знаем кто ты и чем ты
you are doing I am a consultant You are an [ __ ] You
занимаешься Я консультант Ты [__] Ты
Raider you are business Killer You are black
Рейдер ты бизнес Киллер Ты чёрный
PR man And now the people you made
пиарщик А теперь люди которым ты сделал
[ __ ] decided to order you Big people
[__] решили тебя заказать Большие люди
Well when I say big I mean
Ну когда я говорю большие Я имею в виду
very big you understand about the World Cup I don't You
очень большие понимаешь о ЧМ Я нет Ты
did a lot of bad things to Valery
сделал очень много нехорошего Валерию
Kiselev the author of the cat kaks
киселёву автору кота какс
is it all because of him?
это что всё из-за него что
Are you crazy? Yes, like Coconut was created in
ли спятили Да как вот Кокос создавался в
early nineties at the animation studio
начале девяностых на анимационной студии
in St. Petersburg under personal control
в Петербурге под личным контролем
some people in Petersburg and some
некоторых людей в Петербурге и некоторые
People from Saint Petersburg know this cartoon
люди из Петербурга знают этот мультфильм
by heart and Valeria Kiseleva is also good
наизусть и Валерия Киселёва тоже хорошо
know
знают
I don't mean I don't mean
я я же не
I knew it wasn't me
знал мне же не
they said I didn't know Yes no one knew Yes and
сказали я не знал Да никто не знал Да и
I shouldn't know, but for all the nasty things that
знать не должен а за все гадости которые
you did you need to disappear by the way i
ты сделал тебе нужно исчезнуть Кстати я
I won't hide how, well, when trying to
не буду скрывать как ну при попытке к
escape
бегству
I have a new star medal but I
всё у меня новая звёздочка медаль но я
good you will disappear differently
добрый ты исчезнешь по-другому
uh for gram passport with photo under new name
ээ за грам паспорт с фото на новое имя
a ticket for a flight to Caracas and money for
билет на рейс до каракаса и деньги на
at first A you sit in Venezuela and dont
первое время А сядешь в Венесуэле и не
come back in the next 5 years
возвращайся в Ближайшие 5 лет в
Venezuela
Венесуэле
What am I going to do there? Well, what am I going to do?
что ж там делать-то буду Ну то что не
you can here
сможешь здесь
live Oh, what are you saying?
жить Ну что ты
[music]
[музыка]
I agree, partridge
согласен куропатка
here you go, bloody [ __ ] in the pit
вот пожалуйста кровавые [__] в яме
master copies the whole series are ready
мастер копии весь сериал готовы
tomorrow's broadcast as
завтрашнему эфиру как
standard [ __ ] is great you promised
эталонное говнище прекрасно Вы обещали
I'll get the job if the series works out
мне должность если сериал получится
bad Maria who do you think I am my
плохим Мария за кого ты меня держишь моё
word iron tomorrow and I will not
слово железо Завтра же и я её не
I'll take it that I don't need your position
возьму что мне не нужна ваша должность
the series turned out this way not because of me
сериал получился таким не благодаря мне
I, like everyone else, tried to fix it
я как и все старалась его исправить
just apparently we I Valera Vlad chicken
просто видимо мы я Валера Влад курино
Marina Sveta Oleg we are shitty filmmakers
Марина Света Олег мы говённый киношники
but we are good people and you are Andrey Sergeevich
но мы хорошие люди а вы Андрей Сергеевич
I'm so bad I feel so ashamed
плохой мне прямо так Стыдно стало
of course it did I can see it in your eyes While we
конечно стало Я по глазам вижу Пока мы
we did this we became friends we are friends
это делали мы стали друзьями мы друг
a friend was rescued saved helped already Vlad
друга выручали спасали помогали уж Влад
what are you an [ __ ] and he became more or less A
ты на что [__] и тот стал более-менее А
You can't play us like chess
вы в нас как в шахматы играете нельзя
treat people like you do my dear
так с людьми поступать как вы дорогая
girl
девочка
This is the world of business and big money, you or
Это мир бизнеса и больших денег ты или
shark or
акула или
shrimp Choose who you will be shrimp
креветка Выбирай кем будешь креветка
I swam to my mom's to watch the premiere
поплыла к мамке смотреть премьеру
do you want a series
сериала хотите
fire wait do you think this is for me
увольнять подожди ты думаешь мне это
I like all the touchy ones
нравится все обидчивые
I began to hear a voice from the Beautiful Far Away
стали слышу голос из Прекрасного дал
morning voice in silver
голос утренний в серебряной
I hear the voices of the race, beckoning
расе слышу голосы манящая
the road makes your head spin like in childhood
дорога кружит голову как в детстве
carousel Beautiful far away don't be me
карусель Прекрасное далёко не будька ме
don't be cruel, don't be cruel
жестоко не будька ме жестока
cruel from the pure Source
жестока небудь от чистого Исток
Beautiful far away Beautiful far away I
Прекрасное далёко Прекрасное далёко Я
I'm starting
начинаю
I hear a voice from the Beautiful
путь слышу голос из Прекрасного
far away he calls me into the magic
далёка он зовёт меня в волшебные
I hear a voice from the edge, a voice asks
края слышу голос голос спрашивает
strictly And what did you do for ra today?
строго А сегодня что для ра сделал
I am Beautiful far away don't come to me
Я Прекрасное далёко не будь ко мне
don't be cruel to me, ...
жестока не будь ко мне жестоко жестока
not from pure source Andrey Sergeevich
не буд от чистого исто Андрей Сергеевич
the bloody [ __ ] ratings have arrived I'm shocked
пришли рейтинги кровавых шлюх Я в шоке
Nobody expected such numbers Well, Oksana didn't
никто не ожидал таких цифр Ну Оксан не
always win
всегда же побеждать
that's very bad yes bad Yes what are you talking about
что очень плохо да плохо Да вы что это
super hit we exceeded all indicators
суперхит мы превысили все показатели
our main
наших основных
competitors Andrey Sergeevich I you
конкурентов Андрей Сергеевич я вас
Congratulations
поздравляю
And how?
А как
how why Well all critics as one
как почему Ну все критики как один
They say this is the most daring comedy
говорят что это самая смелая комедия
season comedy [ __ ] melodrama
сезона комедия [__] это мелодрама
Oksana What the [ __ ] comedy? Well, I don't know.
Оксана Какая нахуй комедия Ну я не знаю
Well, that's what they write Andrey
Ну так пишут Андрей
Sergeevich, what are we going to do now?
Сергеевич что мы теперь будем
probably make a second season
делать видимо второй сезон
With
с